<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?><items><item><airline_id>2</airline_id><name>Lufthansa</name><title>Flights with Lufthansa</title><sub_title>Best Deals On Cheap Business Class Flights tickets to Lufthansa</sub_title><alias>lufthansa</alias><summary>Exclusive discounted business cheap tickets with lufthansa, spacious seating, extra-long in-flight beds and delectable dishes are just a few of Lufthansa&#38;#39;s notable amenities. Luxuriate in Lufthansa&#38;#39;s magnificent first class seats and business class fares with unparalleled discounts from IFlyFirstClass. You&#38;#39;ll save thousands of dollars on Lufthansa&#38;#39;s last minute first class deals and premium flights so that you can roam the world in ultimate luxury.
</summary><bodyColumn_1>&#60;p&#62;Exclusive airport terminals, spacious seating, extra-long in-flight beds and delectable dishes are just a few of Lufthansa&#38;#39;s notable amenities. Luxuriate in Lufthansa&#38;#39;s magnificent first class seats and business class fares with unparalleled discounts from IFlyFirstClass. You&#38;#39;ll save thousands of dollars on Lufthansa&#38;#39;s last minute first class deals and premium flights so that you can roam the world in ultimate luxury.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h3&#62;Lufthansa: &#38;quot;Nonstop You&#38;quot;&#60;/h3&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Seasoned travelers know all about the benefits of traveling amid the vast Lufthansa network. The world&#38;#39;s fourth largest airline, Lufthansa serves nearly 200 international destinations. Offering unrivaled service and an exclusive premium passenger terminal at its Frankfurt Airport hub, Lufthansa is repeatedly named Europe&#38;#39;s best airline by the World Travel Awards and the World Airline Awards.&#38;#160;&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    Travelers appreciate the airline&#38;#39;s legendary services, from first class and business class seats that recline to a spacious horizontal position to a robust in-flight entertainment system. The airline&#38;#39;s exquisite services are noted by airline and travel industry groups, as well, earning Lufthansa a coveted five-star designation from industry reviewer SkyTrax.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h3&#62;Relish the Luxury of Lufthansa At the Airport&#60;/h3&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;With an entire terminal reserved for Lufthansa&#38;#39;s first class passengers traveling through Frankfurt Airport, it&#38;#39;s no surprise that the airline earned the No. 1 First Class Lounge Award at the 2013 World Airline Awards. The exclusive 19,375 square foot terminal helps you make the most of a layover with delights such as:&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;ul&#62;
    &#60;li&#62;An extensive wine bar,&#60;/li&#62;
    &#60;li&#62;Quiet rooms with plush daybeds,&#60;/li&#62;
    &#60;li&#62;A cozy cigar lounge,&#60;/li&#62;
    &#60;li&#62;Designer toiletries and&#60;/li&#62;
    &#60;li&#62;Many high-end dining options.&#60;/li&#62;
    &#60;/ul&#62;
</bodyColumn_1><bodyColumn_2>&#60;p&#62;Best of all, your time and comfort is maximized with the aid of an on-site personal assistant, reserved security queues and limousine service to your airplane.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h3&#62;Enjoy Lufthansa&#38;#39;s Award-Winning First Class Flights&#60;/h3&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;In the air, Lufthansa&#38;#39;s trademark service continues with lavish caviar service on European flights, an ever-changing &#38;quot;Culinary Delights&#38;quot; menu served on the very best linens and ergonomic seats that stretch to 6.5 feet when reclined. Aboard Lufthansa&#38;#39;s first class seats, you&#38;#39;ll dine, work, rest and slumber in unmatched comfort and style. With a world-wide ranking of No. 5 for first class cabins, Lufthansa faithfully delivers on its promise for stellar service and first class on-board amenities.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h3&#62;Revel in Spacious Business Class Seats&#60;/h3&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;With the space afforded to business class travelers, you won&#38;#39;t have to decide between in-flight working and eating. Dine on fresh fare served on fine china, work in privacy, enjoy broadband Internet service or watch movies on personal entertainment systems. Passengers aboard Lufthansa&#38;#39;s international business class flights can even use their own smart phones to adjust seat angles for maximum comfort.&#38;#160;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h3&#62;Luxury For Less&#60;/h3&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;IFlyFirstClass gives you the freedom to enjoy all of the luxury you deserve on your travels. With savings in the thousands, you can appreciate all of the joys of discounted Lufthansa business class fares, first class seats and last minute first class flights so that you arrive at your destination ready to achieve your best.&#60;/p&#62;
</bodyColumn_2><browserTitle>Lufthansa First and Business Class Flights | Book Lufthansa Flight - I Fly First Class</browserTitle><seo><description>Book tickets for Lufthansa first and business class flight at I Fly First Class. Luxury flights to wide range of destinations in Europe, Asia and other continents.
</description><keywords>flight, lufthansa, first class, business class, i fly first class</keywords></seo><images><image><alias>ddfcbc7f691d4e99aaace01941307716.jpg</alias><content_id>2</content_id><title>discounted business cheap tickets lufthansa</title><queue>0</queue></image><image><alias>841c21d99faa472f9aa866c36165418e.jpg</alias><content_id>2</content_id><title>last minute first class tickets </title><queue>1</queue></image><image><alias>27a0f3cf4c714a6eb787d236fb5ef76e.jpg</alias><content_id>2</content_id><title>cheap business class to asia</title><queue>2</queue></image></images></item><item><airline_id>3</airline_id><name>United</name><title>Flights with United</title><sub_title>The Cheapest Business &#38; United Airlines First Class Tickets. Last Minute Business Class. </sub_title><alias>united</alias><summary>Make your experience&#38;#160;count with&#38;#160;last minute first class with airline united.&#38;#160;Experience the joy of premium travel with IFlyFirstClass&#38;#39; remarkable discounts on first class flights and business class deals aboard United Airlines. You&#38;#39;ll enjoy all the luxuries of top-of-the-line domestic and international travel while saving thousands of dollars.
</summary><bodyColumn_1>&#60;p&#62;Experience the joy of premium travel with IFlyFirstClass&#38;#39; remarkable discounts on first class flights and business class deals aboard United Airlines. You&#38;#39;ll enjoy all the luxuries of top-of-the-line domestic and international travel while saving thousands of dollars.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h3&#62;United Airlines: &#38;quot;It&#38;#39;s Time to Fly&#38;quot;&#60;/h3&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;With the largest destination network and the biggest fleet in the world, United is a great choice for those seeking travel flexibility and choice. Traveling to 800-plus cities in more than 60 countries, United transports 140 million passengers to all six inhabited continents and offers one-stop and non-stop flights from nearly everywhere in the United States.&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    An industry titan, United&#38;#39;s environmental efforts earned the title of 2013 &#38;quot;Eco-Airline of the Year&#38;quot; by EcoAviation and, in 2011, operated the first commercial flight using advanced biofuel. With a variety of environmentally friendly measures and initiatives in place, passengers can feel positive about traveling on United&#38;#39;s fuel-efficient aircraft.&#38;#160;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h3&#62;The vast Chicago-based airline also earns other accolades, including:&#60;/h3&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;- 2013 and 2012 Best Airline for North American Travel by&#38;#160;Business Traveler&#38;#160;magazine,&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;- North America Lounge of the Year, Priority Pass,&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;- Best Place to Work Award, Human Rights Campaign Foundation and&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;- Best Transatlantic Airline, Scottish Passenger Agents&#38;#39; Association.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h3&#62;Relax in United&#38;#39;s Airport Lounges&#60;/h3&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;With nearly 50 United Clubs in 38 domestic and international airports, those with United first class tickets and business class seats can enjoy a multitude of luxuries. From complimentary business services and high-speed Internet to refreshing showers and dining options, United First&#38;reg; and United Business&#38;reg; travelers can make the most of time spent at the airport. At your exclusive lounge, sip on legendary Napa Valley wines, re-fuel with complimentary snacks and save time with Premier Access check-in.&#60;/p&#62;
</bodyColumn_1><bodyColumn_2>&#60;h3&#62;Relish United&#38;#39;s First Class Flights&#60;/h3&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Settle in and relax in United&#38;#39;s over-sized leather first class seats. On international flights, stretch out your legs and enjoy a back massage, dine on delicious meals, convert your seat to a spacious bed and snuggle up in a sumptuous duvet.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h3&#62;Even those flying within the U.S. delight in extra benefits, such as:&#60;/h3&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;- Comprehensive personal on-demand entertainment systems,&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;- Adjustable headrests,&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;- iPod adapters,&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;- Power outlets and&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;- Expedited check-in, security and boarding queues.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h3&#62;Relax in United&#38;#39;s Business Class Seats&#60;/h3&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Extra-wide seats cushion you for a restful and productive flight in business class. Multi-course meals, personal entertainment systems and a variety of other useful services are offered to business class passengers. Those enjoying the airline&#38;#39;s international business class fares revel in complimentary toiletry kits, touch-screen seat recliners and electronic connectivity.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;With IFlyFirstClass, you can enjoy all of United&#38;#39;s numerous services and benefits&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;at a fraction of the published prices. From a broad range of travel connections and choice of itineraries to countless pampering services, you can indulge in all the luxury you deserve with amazingly discounted first class flights, business class deals and last minute first class fares from IFlyFirstClass.&#60;/p&#62;
</bodyColumn_2><browserTitle>United Airline Flights | Tickets for First and Business Class | I Fly First Class</browserTitle><seo><description>Best prices for United Airline first and business class flights. Discounted offers. Send request to I Fly First Class for more information.
</description><keywords>flight, united, first class, business class, i fly first class</keywords></seo><images><image><alias>c33f68fa21d84c81b8bc21a64068cb0d.jpg</alias><content_id>3</content_id><title>last minute first class with airline united</title><queue>0</queue></image><image><alias>c39bfbfca72a41e28e06739df3fef665.jpg</alias><content_id>3</content_id><title>last minute business class flight</title><queue>1</queue></image><image><alias>7b39aceb96d4450796052644863a8dcf.jpg</alias><content_id>3</content_id><title>first class discounted price</title><queue>2</queue></image></images></item><item><airline_id>4</airline_id><name>Delta</name><title>Flights with Delta</title><sub_title>Delta International Business Class Fares, Cheap Discounted First Class Airline.</sub_title><alias>delta</alias><summary>Finally! Your&#38;#160;business class deals delta are here.&#38;#160;

    Travel across the nation and around the world in consummate style aboard the vast U.S.-based Delta Air Lines. You can save hundreds, if not thousands, of dollars on Delta&#38;#39;s luxurious first class fares, last minute first class seats and business class flights with IFlyFirstClass&#38;#39; extraordinary discounts. With our tremendous savings and Delta&#38;#39;s extensive network and deluxe accommodations, you can traipse across the globe anytime, from just about anywhere.
</summary><bodyColumn_1>&#60;p&#62;Travel across the nation and around the world in consummate style aboard the vast U.S.-based Delta Air Lines. You can save hundreds, if not thousands, of dollars on Delta&#38;#39;s luxurious first class fares, last minute first class seats and business class flights with IFlyFirstClass&#38;#39; extraordinary discounts. With our tremendous savings and Delta&#38;#39;s extensive network and deluxe accommodations, you can traipse across the globe anytime, from just about anywhere.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h3&#62;Delta Air Lines: &#38;quot;Keep Climbing&#38;quot;&#60;/h3&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Serving more than 160 million passengers each year, Delta operates one of the world&#38;#39;s biggest fleets of 722 aircraft. Flying to six continents, 65 countries and an impressive 330 destinations, Delta is widely known and respected. The official airline for the Grammy Awards, New York&#38;#39;s Whitney Museum of American Art and Madison Square Garden&#38;#39;s professional athletic teams, Delta&#38;#39;s support of the National Guard and reserve employees led to its receipt of the Secretary of Defense Freedom Award.&#60;br /&#62;
    Delta&#38;#39;s signature service earns the airline dozens of awards annually, including:&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;ul&#62;
    &#60;li&#62;&#38;quot;Most Admired Airline Worldwide,&#38;quot;&#38;#160;Fortune&#38;#160;magazine&#60;/li&#62;
    &#60;li&#62;No. 1 Holistic World Safety Awards, Air Transport Rating Agency&#60;/li&#62;
    &#60;li&#62;Best Domestic Airline,&#38;#160;TravelAge West&#60;/li&#62;
    &#60;/ul&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h3&#62;Enjoy Delta Service At Airports Around the World&#60;/h3&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Earning a Five-Star Diamond Award from the American Academy of Hospitality Sciences for its participation on the $1.3 billion expansion of JFK Airport&#38;#39;s Terminal 4, Delta is dedicated to providing state-pf-the-art services at airports around the globe. With complimentary access to Sky Club airport lounges, Delta&#38;#39;s passengers with first class seats and international business class flights are thoroughly pampered. Services include:&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;ul&#62;
    &#60;li&#62;Complimentary cocktails, snacks and beverages;&#60;/li&#62;
    &#60;li&#62;Private showers;&#60;/li&#62;
    &#60;li&#62;Inviting armchairs and&#60;/li&#62;
    &#60;li&#62;Business and meeting services.&#60;/li&#62;
    &#60;/ul&#62;
</bodyColumn_1><bodyColumn_2>&#60;h3&#62;Indulge in Delta&#38;#39;s Deluxe First Class Seats&#60;/h3&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Lengthy flights are enjoyable in the incomparable accommodations of Delta&#38;#39;s first class fares. Savor the warmth of Delta&#38;#39;s Westin Heavenly&#38;reg; in-flight bedding. Maximize productivity with wireless high-speed Internet, multiple power and USB outlets and expedited check-in and boarding queues. Dine on dishes creatively designed by celebrity chefs. Enjoy your in-flight time with hundreds of movies, live satellite television and thousands of music selections.&#38;#160;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h3&#62;Bask in Business Class Seats&#60;/h3&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Whether you are traveling to international destinations or between New York and San Francisco or Los Angeles, DeltaElite offers the ultimate in premium services. On board your flight, you can relax with exquisite wines selected by a master sommelier, abundant entertainment choices and Westin Heavenly&#38;reg; bedding of plump comforters and large down-alternative pillows. Those heading for international destinations dine on renowned chef Michael Chiarello&#38;#39;s creations, and intercontinental travelers relish seasonal, five-course meals.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Regardless of your destination or choice of business class seats or first class tickets, Delta&#38;#39;s extensive network of routes and services offer the ultimate in flexibility. Even better, flying in the magnificent comfort of Delta&#38;#39;s premium cabins is affordable with IFlyFirstClass&#38;#39; deals on Delta business class flights, first class fares and last minute first class seats.&#60;/p&#62;
</bodyColumn_2><browserTitle>Delta Airline Flights - First and Business Class Tickets - I Fly First Class</browserTitle><seo><description>Fly luxuriously with Delta Airline and I Fly First Class. Discounted First and Business class flights all over the world. Contact us for more information.
</description><keywords>flight, delta, first class, business class, i fly first class</keywords></seo><images><image><alias>3719e123d4e940b482aa3b81dec4378a.jpg</alias><content_id>4</content_id><title>business class deals delta</title><queue>0</queue></image><image><alias>db77492db2fb43949d7b32a41611a2d5.jpg</alias><content_id>4</content_id><title>discounted first class fares</title><queue>1</queue></image><image><alias>90dc65d4071d46b1aac7251fd42e19d8.jpg</alias><content_id>4</content_id><title>last minute flights</title><queue>2</queue></image></images></item><item><airline_id>5</airline_id><name>Air france</name><title>Flights with Air france</title><sub_title>Discounted First Class Specials Air France, Cheap Last Minute First Class</sub_title><alias>air-france</alias><summary>Congratulation! Your first class specials air france are here.&#38;#160;Get one today.

    Relish the fabulous cuisine and incomparable luxury of Air France&#38;#39;s business class fares, first class tickets and last minute first class deals through IFlyFirstClass. With discounts as high as 70 percent on premium airfare, IFlyFirstClass&#38;#39; outstanding service encourages you to enjoy all of the magnificent amenities of Air France at a fraction of the usual cost.
</summary><bodyColumn_1>&#60;p&#62;Relish the fabulous cuisine and incomparable luxury of Air France&#38;#39;s business class fares, first class tickets and last minute first class deals through IFlyFirstClass. With discounts as high as 70 percent on premium airfare, IFlyFirstClass&#38;#39; outstanding service encourages you to enjoy all of the magnificent amenities of Air France at a fraction of the usual cost.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h3&#62;Air France: &#38;quot;Making the Sky the Best Place on Earth&#38;quot;&#60;/h3&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Serving more than 59 million passengers each year, Air France offers an extensive network of routes to 163 destinations in 92 countries. With a global hub at Paris&#38;#39; Charles de Gaulle Airport, the 80-year-old airline also serves secondary hubs at Orly, Lyon-Saint Exup&#38;eacute;ry, Marseille Provence, Nice C&#38;ocirc;te d&#38;#39;Azur and Toulouse-Blagnac airports. Air France merged with KLM in 2004 and maintains three subsidiaries:&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;- CityJet,&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;- Hop! and&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;- Trasavia.com France.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;&#60;br /&#62;
    Devoted to re-claiming its place among the leaders of luxury travel, Air France committed several hundred million Euros to re-imagining its first class La Premi&#38;egrave;re service and establishing its new &#38;quot;feel at home&#38;quot; direction. The newly designed premium service offers La Premi&#38;egrave;re class only on long-haul flights and Business Class and lesser cabins on remaining flights.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h3&#62;Luxuriate in Lavish Lounges&#60;/h3&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Through its many partnerships, Air France offers more than 300 exclusive airport lounges showcasing extraordinary rest areas, business services, delectable meals and a variety of other upscale amenities.&#38;#160;Its new SkyPriority program features consistent services at all airports so that passengers are always greeted with familiar amenities.&#38;#160;&#60;/p&#62;
</bodyColumn_1><bodyColumn_2>&#60;p&#62;Special check-in services, priority baggage drop-off and reserved immigration and security queues help premium passengers move through the airport expeditiously.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h3&#62;Revel in the Opulence of First Class Fares&#60;/h3&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;First class passengers aboard Air France revel in the privileged welcome services, personal attendants and spacious seating nooks with direct access to aisles. At the push of a button, over-sized supple leather seats recline to flat beds. Covered with a plush mattress, duvet and feather pillow, the beds encourage restful slumber and a productive use of flight time. When not resting, dine on gastronomic masterpieces designed by world-renowned chefs or sample the wines selected by one of the most respected sommeliers in the world. Whatever your pleasure, you&#38;#39;ll most likely find it aboard Air France&#38;#39;s La Premi&#38;egrave;re Class.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h3&#62;Fly Productively in Spacious Business Class Seats&#60;/h3&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Travelers aboard Air France&#38;#39;s business class flights relish a culinary journey that begins with an oshibori and an aperitif. For passengers aboard medium-haul flights, the culinary adventure continues with a main course and scrumptious dessert.&#38;#160;&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    Aside from the sensory delights of business class fares, Air France treats its premium passengers to expedited security, check-in and boarding lines on the ground and ample work space, comfortable reclining seats and attentive service in the air.&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    Whether you choose first class tickets, business class fares or last minute first class deals from IFlyFirstClass, you&#38;#39;ll enjoy the perfect blend of luxury and productivity aboard Air France.&#60;/p&#62;
</bodyColumn_2><browserTitle>Air France First and Business Class Flights | I Fly First Class</browserTitle><seo><description>Book tickets for Air France first and business class flight at I Fly First Class. Luxury flights to wide range of destinations in Europe, Asia and other continents. </description><keywords>flight, air france, first class, business class, i fly first class</keywords></seo><images><image><alias>e9ce679057aa4269a2d2b5607c86eb5d.jpg</alias><content_id>5</content_id><title>first class specials air france </title><queue>0</queue></image><image><alias>26d15fefa4364bb5b608d7653654eb9d.jpg</alias><content_id>5</content_id><title>Last Minute Business Class fares</title><queue>1</queue></image><image><alias>330cfbfba74f459e89628ec8e264f571.jpg</alias><content_id>5</content_id><title>Discounted First Class Tickets</title><queue>2</queue></image></images></item><item><airline_id>6</airline_id><name>Singapore Air</name><title>Flights with Singapore Air</title><sub_title>Best Business Class Flights to Singapore, Call Us Now and Save Thousands.</sub_title><alias>singapore-air</alias><summary>Get your best deals business class singapore air today!

    IFlyFirstClass offers cheap Business Class flights to Asia, save thousands on last minute Business Class tickets. Best deals on Business Class. &#38;#160;Special fares on Business and First Class tickets. Discounted First &#38;amp; Business Class airline tickets. First Class &#38;amp; Business Class travel deals.&#38;#160; &#38;#160; &#38;#160;
</summary><bodyColumn_1>&#60;p&#62;First class seats and business class flights with legendary gracious service and sumptuous accommodations distinguish Singapore Airlines as one of the world&#38;#39;s leading airlines. Experience all of Singapore Airlines&#38;#39; many delights for a fraction of the cost with IFlyFirstClass&#38;#39; incredible discounts on all luxury flights, including last minute first class tickets and last minute business class fares.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h3&#62;Singapore Airlines: &#38;quot;A Great Way to Fly&#38;quot;&#60;/h3&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Embracing its top five-star rating from SkyTrax, Singapore Airlines recently was named the No. 3 airline in the world by the World Airline Awards. Over the past decade, consistently ranked in the top 10 airlines.&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    Annually, more than 18 million passengers experience Singapore Airlines&#38;#39; trademark service, traveling to more than 60 destinations in 35 countries. In addition to its main brand, the renowned air carrier maintains several subsidiaries, including SilkAir and Scoot.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h3&#62;Sample the Sumptuous Airport Delights&#60;/h3&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Premium travelers enjoy Singapore Airlines&#38;#39; numerous amenities at the air carrier&#38;#39;s famed 16 SilverKris lounges. Bountiful buffets, rejuvenating showers, relaxing arm chairs, serene settings and plentiful business services are just the beginning of Singapore Airlines&#38;#39; exclusive airport lounge services. The air carrier&#38;#39;s celebrated main airport lounge at Singapore&#38;#39;s Changi Airport is a serene oasis away from the hubbub of the busy airport. With all of the airline&#38;#39;s many plush lounges, it&#38;#39;s unsurprising that Singapore Airlines ranked in the worldwide top 10 best first and business class lounges at the 2013 World Airline Awards.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h3&#62;Experience Fabulous First Class Flights And Beyond&#60;/h3&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Serving the ultra-affluent, Singapore Airlines Suites are considered a step above first class and feature incomparable privacy and luxury.&#38;#160;&#60;/p&#62;
</bodyColumn_1><bodyColumn_2>&#60;p&#62;Sumptuous beds, ample storage and plentiful entertainment create a secluded retreat for suite passengers.&#38;#160;&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    You don&#38;#39;t have to travel in the airlines&#38;#39; suites to indulge in incredible service though. The company&#38;#39;s regular first class fares are equally delightful. The company&#38;#39;s newest aircraft offer some of the widest seats in the industry, deluxe bed-turn down service, divine culinary treasures, exceptional skin care products and a comprehensive electronics panel. To further accommodate passengers, the airline presents its Book the Cook service so that passengers can select their meals at the same time reservations are made.&#38;#160;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h3&#62;Enjoy Spacious Business Class Seats&#60;/h3&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;With three business class categories, Singapore Airlines tailors its services to best suit its routes and passengers. Flights between Los Angeles and New York offer all-business class aircraft with over-sized seats arranged so that every passenger can directly access the aisle. An in-cabin snack corner is open throughout the flight and passengers can pre-arrange meals through the Book the Cook service.&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    Passengers on long-haul business class flights relish leather seats that recline completely flat, in-seat electrical outlets and USB ports and an extensive on-demand entertainment system. On board medium-haul flights, travelers control the seat recline to suit personal comfort and enjoy personal entertainment systems.&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    Regardless of your chosen cabins, serenity and savings unite with IFlyFirstClass&#38;#39; extraordinary discounts on Singapore Airlines&#38;#39; consummate first class seats and business class flights.&#60;/p&#62;
</bodyColumn_2><browserTitle>Singapore Air First and Business Class Flights - I Fly First Class</browserTitle><seo><description>Best prices for Singapore Air first and business class flights. Discounted offers. Send request to I Fly First Class for more information.
</description><keywords>flight, singapore air, first class, business class, i fly first class</keywords></seo><images><image><alias>e851e6676a5e4f70b5b2cbb818e60658.jpg</alias><content_id>6</content_id><title>best deals business class singapore air</title><queue>0</queue></image><image><alias>e0d63d48f0464b7c9af27196a7f240b8.jpg</alias><content_id>6</content_id><title>Last Minute First Class Airfares</title><queue>1</queue></image><image><alias>588b2d08216042e6afbfa21c4dface4e.jpg</alias><content_id>6</content_id><title>Cheap Last Minute to Asia</title><queue>2</queue></image></images></item><item><airline_id>7</airline_id><name>Japan Air</name><title>Flights with Japan Air</title><sub_title>Best Deals On Cheap Business Class Flights to Japan, Discounted Last Minute Fares</sub_title><alias>japan-air</alias><summary>Enjoy Cheap Business Class Airfare by Japan Air.&#38;#160;

    IFlyFirstClass offers cheap Business Class flights to Asia, save thousands on last minute Business Class tickets. Best deals on Business Class. &#38;#160;Special fares on Business and First Class tickets. Discounted First &#38;amp; Business Class airline tickets. First Class &#38;amp; Business Class travel deals.&#38;#160; &#38;#160; &#38;#160;
</summary><bodyColumn_1>&#60;p&#62;Relish award-winning first class cabins and hospitable service on Japan Airlines&#38;#39; domestic and international flights. IFlyFirstClass helps you save thousands of dollars on Japan Airlines&#38;#39; premium first class tickets, business class deals and last minute first class fares so that you can travel the world at affordable prices.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h3&#62;Japan Airlines: &#38;quot;Fly Into Tomorrow&#38;quot;&#60;/h3&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Based in Tokyo, Japan Airlines (JAL) was established in 1951 and now operates five subsidiaries, including JAL Express, J-Air and JALways. Together with its subsidiaries, JAL serves 52 million passengers annually and offers routes to 220 destinations in 40 countries. Combined, the air carrier and its subsidiaries create the sixth largest airline in the world.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h3&#62;Indulgent Service Distinguishes JAL Airport Lounges&#60;/h3&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Known for gracious Japanese hospitality, JAL lounges are a world apart. Signature Sakura Lounges are plush, gorgeous and tranquil settings to relax, dine, refresh and pass the time productively. Unwind in a massage chair, enjoy a cocktail at the bar and let kids entertain themselves in play and entertainment areas. Around the world, the air carrier maintains first class lounges and JAL lounges in a variety of airports, supplying peaceful retreats for passengers to make the most of their time before and between flights.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h3&#62;Relish Award-Winning First Class Seats&#60;/h3&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Abundant, seasonal dining options are the hallmark of JAL first class flights. Japanese menus and Western menus offer travelers a range of options and all of the delightful creativity one expects from famed Chef Fumiko Kono. At any time during the flight, passengers who want a little extra snack can choose items from an a la carte menu.&#60;/p&#62;
</bodyColumn_1><bodyColumn_2>&#60;p&#62;JAL&#38;#39;s MAGIC personal on-demand entertainment system keeps passengers entertained, while complimentary toiletry bags and pajamas encourage travelers to relax and enjoy the flight.&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    New JAL Suites up the ante on the airlines&#38;#39; unparalleled service. Seclusion and luxury are assured with plush Tempur&#38;reg; bedding and Symphony pillows, privacy partitions, an extra-wide 23-inch LCD screen and gracious attendants.&#38;#160;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h3&#62;Cruise the Skies in Comfortable Business Class Seats&#60;/h3&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Committed to staying ahead of developments in premium travel, JAL is upgrading its business class seats to create more privacy, comfort and style. More of the airlines&#38;#39; international flights are reconfigured to give passengers direct aisle access on routes between Tokyo and Vancouver and particular Hawaii and Southeast Asia flights.&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    As with first class, JAL&#38;#39;s business class passengers choose from seasonally fresh Japanese and Western menus, snack on Japanese cheeses and designer chocolates, and enjoy freshly steamed Minami-Uonuma rice.&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    Whether you prefer to fly in secluded JAL suites, indulgent first class flights or capacious business class seats, IFlyFirstClass&#38;#160;brings you JAL luxury for a fraction of the published fares. Across Japan and around the globe, you can&#38;#39;t beat the savings and indulgence of IFlyFirstClass&#38;#39; deeply discounted JAL first class tickets, business class deals and last minute first class fares.&#60;/p&#62;
</bodyColumn_2><browserTitle>Air Japan Flights - First and Business Class Tickets - I Fly First Class</browserTitle><seo><description>Fly luxuriously with Air Japan and I Fly First Class. Discounted First and Business class flights all over the world. Contact us for more information.
</description><keywords>flight, japan air, first class, business class, i fly first class</keywords></seo><images><image><alias>44a0509278964dcdacbb6bb889f6deba.jpg</alias><content_id>7</content_id><title>Cheap Business Class Airfare Japan Air</title><queue>0</queue></image><image><alias>3d54084e1d7d479585503adcaafef948.jpg</alias><content_id>7</content_id><title>last minute flights to asia</title><queue>1</queue></image><image><alias>2c4e38720a394b5a8ef5d09367c02a81.jpg</alias><content_id>7</content_id><title>first class cheap tickets</title><queue>2</queue></image></images></item><item><airline_id>8</airline_id><name>China Eastern</name><title>Flights with China Eastern</title><sub_title>China Eastern Last Minute Business Class</sub_title><alias>china-eastern</alias><summary>Get the best from Last Minute Business Class by China Eastern.

    IFlyFirstClass offers cheap Business Class flights to Asia, save thousands on last minute Business Class tickets. Best deals on Business Class. &#38;#160;Special fares on Business and First Class tickets. Discounted First &#38;amp; Business Class airline tickets. First Class &#38;amp; Business Class travel deals.
</summary><bodyColumn_1>&#60;p&#62;First class flights and business class tickets are more affordable than ever with IFlyFirstClass&#38;#39; newly released discounts on China Easter Airlines. Travelers save thousands of dollars on premium flights to hundreds of destinations around the globe, all while enjoying the many lavish amenities and services of acclaimed China Eastern Airlines.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h3&#62;Deluxe Airport Lounges&#60;/h3&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Premium travel accommodations begin at the airport with China Eastern&#38;#39;s inviting airport lounges reserved for travelers holding first class tickets and business class fares. China Eastern&#38;#39;s exclusive lounges are available at its larger destination airports, including Shanghai, Beijing and Los Angeles. The lounges offer a wide range of Asian and Western hot and cold meals, snacks, business services, power outlets, entertainment options, alcoholic and non-alcoholic beverages, high-speed Internet and personalized service.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h3&#62;First Class Seats Offering Serene Comfort&#60;/h3&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;China Eastern&#38;#39;s first class cabins are known for their privacy and comfort, with over-sized seats that recline to various positions to optimize personal comfort. Most of the company&#38;#39;s first class seats recline to a completely flat position for sleeping and are enhanced with a cozy duvet, fluffy pillows and other sumptuous bed turn-down services. China Eastern&#38;#39;s unique media panel presents myriad entertainment options, from language courses and video games to movies and musical selections.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h3&#62;Business Class Seats Encourage In-flight Productivity&#60;/h3&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;The airline&#38;#39;s Business Class Kingbed is the largest business class seat in the industry. Those with business class tickets enjoy countless other amenities that allow passengers to make the most of their flight time. Roomy workstations are made even more spacious with seat arms that fold down. Retractable privacy screens provide more shoulder space, and personal on-demand entertainment systems are loaded with more then 150 movies, games and tunes.&#38;#160;&#60;/p&#62;
</bodyColumn_1><bodyColumn_2>&#60;h3&#62;China Eastern Airlines: &#38;quot;World-class Hospitality with Eastern Charm&#38;quot;&#60;/h3&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Serving nearly 80 million passengers a year, China Eastern Airlines is China&#38;#39;s second largest air carrier by passenger volume. The airline operates routes to 993 domestic and international cities in 187 countries with a fleet of 430 short-haul and long-haul air craft. Fifty-eight new Next-Generation Boeing 737 and 50 Airbus 320 airplanes are joining the fleet over the next several years.&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    Shanghai-based China Eastern also operates numerous subsidiaries, including Shanghai Airlines, Joy Air, China United Airlines and China Cargo Airlines. Together with Qantas Airlines, the air carrier jointly owns Jetstar Hong Kong. More than 63,000 people are employed by the air carrier that was recognized by the 2012 SkyTrax World Airline Awards as the world&#38;#39;s most improved airline. Celebrated for its service standards and breadth, the company earned several other awards, including:&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;- 2012 Best Corporation Award, China Corporate Social Responsibility Annual Meeting;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;- Most Innovative Company in China 2011,&#38;#160;Fortune&#38;#160;Magazine;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;- 2012 Golden Ting Award, China Capital Market and&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;- Top 50 most valuable Chinese brands, WPP.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Whether travelers choose first class flights or business class tickets, China Eastern Airlines&#38;#39; premium cabins are a luxurious travel option made most affordable by IFlyFirstClass, the leading luxury travel service.&#60;/p&#62;
</bodyColumn_2><browserTitle>China Eastern Business and First Class Flights | Ticket booking - I Fly First Class</browserTitle><seo><description>I Fly First Class offers China Eastern business and first class flights to a wide range of destinations all over the world. Send request for more information.
</description><keywords>flight, china eastern, first class, business class, i fly first class</keywords></seo><images><image><alias>b1fad77c0f31415a81863fda22d8c194.jpg</alias><content_id>8</content_id><title>Last Minute Business Class China Eastern</title><queue>0</queue></image><image><alias>3e704796dcf94a4d9aa9c77b947818bc.jpg</alias><content_id>8</content_id><title>last minute business class fares</title><queue>1</queue></image><image><alias>62bbfa0cf6ed4d84893cbcc3e601e629.jpg</alias><content_id>8</content_id><title>disounted business class to asia</title><queue>2</queue></image></images></item><item><airline_id>9</airline_id><name>Air China</name><title>Flights with Air China</title><sub_title>Special Deals to Asia, Save Up to 70% on Your Cheap First Class Airline Tickets</sub_title><alias>air-china</alias><summary>Get your&#38;#160;first class cheap tickets by&#38;#160;air china today.&#38;#160;World travelers enjoy Air China&#38;#39;s spectacular service at discount rates with IFlyFirstClass&#38;#39; newly released deals. Priced to save travelers thousands of dollars on first class fares and business class flights, these reduced-fare luxury flights are available on all categories of first class, business class and last minute first class tickets. IFlyFirstClass deals aboard Air China are available for a limited time only.
</summary><bodyColumn_1>&#60;p&#62;World travelers enjoy Air China&#38;#39;s spectacular service at discount rates with IFlyFirstClass&#38;#39; newly released deals. Priced to save travelers thousands of dollars on first class fares and business class flights, these reduced-fare luxury flights are available on all categories of first class, business class and last minute first class tickets. IFlyFirstClass deals aboard Air China are available for a limited time only.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h3&#62;Luxury Travel Begins on the Ground&#60;/h3&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;IFlyFirstClass&#38;#39; deeply discounted Air China fares give passengers access to exclusive airport lounges around the world. Air China&#38;#39;s premium passengers can expect to indulge in:&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;- Western and Asian dishes;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;- A wide range of beverages, wine, beer and cocktails;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;- Shower facilities and&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;- Business amenities.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;&#60;br /&#62;
    Some of the air carrier&#38;#39;s lounges also offer live jazz music, play areas, conference rooms and napping rooms. Special BMW ground transfer service is available to certain first and business class passengers arriving at Beijing, Shanghai, Shenzhen, Guangzhou and Chengdu.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h3&#62;Relish the Luxury of First Class Fares&#60;/h3&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Air China provides its &#38;quot;Forbidden Pavilion&#38;quot; service on medium-to-long-distance flights. Here, first class seats lie flat for restful slumber, and travelers are treated to pampering service, incomparable dining options and ample work space. On many Air China first class flights, seats swivel, sport adjustable headrests, offer power outlets and include a roomy folding work table. Individual entertainment systems hold hundreds of movies, music and games. Seven-course meals feature caviar and choices of balsamic salmon, lobster medallion, beef tenderloin or roasted duck. Travelers headed to Beijing from New York, Houston and Los Angeles may sip on 2005 vintage Ch&#38;acirc;teau Brane-Cantenac Margaux Bordeaux for the ultimate experience.&#60;/p&#62;
</bodyColumn_1><bodyColumn_2>&#60;h3&#62;Work or Rest in Spacious Air China Business Class Seats&#60;/h3&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;The elite services of Air China&#38;#39;s &#38;quot;Capital Pavilion&#38;quot; business class seats offer extraordinary comfort and space on medium- and long-distance flights, with seats that convert to flat beds, indulgent meals and consummate service. Adjustable headrests offer enhanced comfort, personal on-demand entertainment systems help travelers pass the time and ample power outlets allow passengers to stay connected.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h3&#62;Air China: &#38;quot;Serving the World with A Warm Heart and Guiding The Future by Innovation&#38;quot;&#60;/h3&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;With the world&#38;#39;s 10th largest airline fleet, Air China transports 60 million passengers to 185 destinations annually. The airline operates seven subsidiaries, including Air Macau, Air China Cargo, Beijing Airlines, Shandong Airlines and Tibet Airlines. The official airline for the 2008 Beijing Olympic Games, the air carrier consistently earns recognition for its service, including:&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;- 2012 Fast Travel Gold Award, International Air Transport Association;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;- Medal of Honor, International Civil Aviation Organization;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;- Best Chinese Airline Award, TTG Asia and&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;- Outstanding Enterprise Award-Bronze Prize, Canada China Business Council.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;&#60;br /&#62;
    With IFlyFirstClass&#38;#39; new travel deals, business class flights, first class fares and last minute first class tickets are an affordable option aboard Air China. For more information about these and other special discounts, contact IFlyFirstClass at (888) 347-7817.&#60;/p&#62;
</bodyColumn_2><browserTitle>Air China First and Business Class Flights - I Fly First Class</browserTitle><seo><description>Discounted Air China first and business class flights with I Fly First Class. Best prices for luxurious flights. Send request for more information.
</description><keywords>flight, air china, first class, business class, i fly first class</keywords></seo><images><image><alias>cba74e28a3cb4cd988d2d29b5f40cf9e.jpg</alias><content_id>9</content_id><title>first class cheap tickets air china</title><queue>0</queue></image><image><alias>df3636ff1c024c6da570a838c4ceee4a.jpg</alias><content_id>9</content_id><title>Last Minute Business Class Fares</title><queue>1</queue></image><image><alias>05cce346fe5d4285afc0746d307eb591.jpg</alias><content_id>9</content_id><title>discounted airline flights</title><queue>2</queue></image></images></item><item><airline_id>10</airline_id><name>Qatar Airways</name><title>Flights with Qatar Airways</title><sub_title>Qatar Discounted Business Class Flights, Call Us Today &#38; Save Thousands.</sub_title><alias>qatar-airways</alias><summary>Save big on &#38;#160;business class discount airline qatar airways

    Today&#38;#39;s globetrotters can indulge in the incomparable luxury of Qatar Airways without breaking the bank, thanks to IFlyFirstClass&#38;trade; new discounts on business class fares, first class deals and last minute first class seats. Renowned for its stellar service and lavish cabins, Qatar Airways offers the ultimate in luxury travel. For a limited time only, these newly released deals from IFlyFirstClass&#38;trade;&#38;#160;provide spectacular Qatar Airways seats at thousands less than published fares.
</summary><bodyColumn_1>&#60;p&#62;Today&#38;#39;s globetrotters can indulge in the incomparable luxury of Qatar Airways without breaking the bank, thanks to IFlyFirstClass&#38;trade; new discounts on business class fares, first class deals and last minute first class seats. Renowned for its stellar service and lavish cabins, Qatar Airways offers the ultimate in luxury travel. For a limited time only, these newly released deals from IFlyFirstClass&#38;trade; provide spectacular Qatar Airways seats at thousands less than published fares.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h3&#62;Qatar&#38;#39;s Airport Lounges Astound&#60;/h3&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;With IFlyFirstClass&#38;trade; discounts, passengers can appreciate the unparalleled splendor of Qatar Airways&#38;#39; business class and first class airport lounges. With the world&#38;#39;s best business class lounge and the No. 3 first class lounge, Qatar Airways&#38;#39; and IFlyFirstClass&#38;trade; deals on premium flights are even more valuable.&#38;#160;&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    The airline&#38;#39;s Premium Terminal at Doha International Airport is a prime example of the airline&#38;#39;s amenities. Passengers are transported to the aircraft in chauffeur-driven luxury vehicles. Culinary delights range from casual and delicatessen fare to hand-rolled sushi and fine dining options. Massage therapy, spa services, high tea and private lounge areas create a refined retreat one expects in a five-star resort.&#38;#160;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h3&#62;Passengers Flourish in Premium First Class Seats&#60;/h3&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Even while saving thousands of dollars with IFlyFirstClass&#38;trade;, passengers can enjoy all of Qatar Airways&#38;#39; notable first class services. Comfortable, capacious seats convert to flat beds covered in exquisite Italian Frette linens and a cozy duvet. Gastronomic delights are designed by four celebrity chefs to please the palate and satisfy savory cravings. The finest wines, ambrosial champagnes and Christian Dior amenity kits enhance the luxurious setting. These sumptuous services are just some of the reasons Qatar Airways recently ranked in the World Airline Awards&#38;#39; top 10 best first class cabins.&#60;/p&#62;
</bodyColumn_1><bodyColumn_2>&#60;h3&#62;&#60;span style=&#34;line-height: 1.6em;&#34;&#62;Qatar Airways Delights with Deluxe Business Class Seats&#60;/span&#62;&#60;/h3&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Voted the No. 1 business class cabin at the World Airline Awards, Qatar offers its passengers choice accommodations, from high-end wines and meals created by world-famous chefs to Ferragamo Attimo amenity kits and in-air mobile service. Just as with first class, discount tickets don&#38;#39;t translate into skimpy services. Business class passengers enjoy first-rate seats that recline to a flat bed clad in fine linen.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h3&#62;Qatar Airways: The World&#38;#39;s Five-Star Airline&#60;/h3&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Based in Doha, Qatar, the airline&#38;#39;s quality is considered among the world&#38;#39;s best, ranking No. 1 in 2011 and 2012 and No. 2 in 2013. Serving more than 120 destinations, Qatar Airways is frequently honored, most recently earning a number of accolades at the SkyTrax World Airline Awards:&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;- Top 10 cabin staff,&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;- Top 5 best in-flight entertainment,&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;- No. 3 best business class seats and&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;- No. 2 best business class catering.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Whether passengers prefer the spacious cabins of business class fares or the lavish appointments of last minute first class seats and regular first class deals, IFlyFirstClass&#38;trade; can save travelers thousands with its new Qatar Airways deals. For more information about these and other discounts, call (888) 347-7817.&#60;/p&#62;
</bodyColumn_2><browserTitle>Qatar Airways Business and First Class Flights - I Fly First Class</browserTitle><seo><description>Fly luxuriously with Qatar Airways and I Fly First Class to any destination all over the world. Discounted First and Business class flights all over the world. Contact us for more information.</description><keywords>flight, qatar airways, first class, business class, i fly first class</keywords></seo><images><image><alias>5967b650584c40b9ac305b954dca97a9.jpg</alias><content_id>10</content_id><title>business class discount airline qatar airways</title><queue>0</queue></image><image><alias>836088d444554b11a90d256bfde8294f.jpg</alias><content_id>10</content_id><title>Last Minute First Class Airfares</title><queue>1</queue></image><image><alias>497b2550e417462c987e29a300705579.jpg</alias><content_id>10</content_id><title>Cheap Business Class</title><queue>2</queue></image></images></item><item><airline_id>11</airline_id><name>Korean Air</name><title>Flights with Korean Air</title><sub_title>Korean Air First Class Price, Call Us to Save Thousands</sub_title><alias>korean-air</alias><summary>Get your first class tickets by korean air.&#38;#160;Travelers can traipse around the world in style with special discounts just released by I Fly First First Class, the leading premium travel service. First class seats, business class fares and last minute first class deals aboard acclaimed Korean Air are now thousands of dollars cheaper than published fares with I Fly First Class&#38;#39; deals.
</summary><bodyColumn_1>&#60;p&#62;Travelers can traipse around the world in style with special discounts just released by I Fly First First Class, the leading premium travel service. First class seats, business class fares and last minute first class deals aboard acclaimed Korean Air are now thousands of dollars cheaper than published fares with IFlyFirstClass&#38;#39; deals.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h3&#62;Exclusive Service At The Airport&#60;/h3&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Korean Air&#38;#39;s first class passengers enjoy personal assistance and reserved first class check-in counters with KAL Premium Service. Prestige Class, Korean Air&#38;#39;s version of business class, joins first class at Korean Air&#38;#39;s special KAL airport lounges around the world. Overcoat storage, snack and beverage service, priority boarding, baggage wrapping and a host of other exclusive services are available to both classes at the airport. Best of all, even though IFlyFirstClass customers pay thousands less for their Korean Air premium seats, they can access all of these full-price airport amenities.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h3&#62;Passengers Revel in Korean Air&#38;#39;s First Class&#60;/h3&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;With several aircraft configurations, Korean Air presents three types of first class seating, all designed to maximize comfort and luxury for travelers. First Class Kosmo Suites are the ultimate in tranquil privacy, and its First Class Kosmo Sleeper Seats offer a plush retreat from in-flight activity. Both Kosmo seats are ergonomically designed seats ensconced in private cubicles. On some of its aircraft, Korean Air also presents its First Class Sleeper Seats, supple seats that recline to a completely flat position to encourage restful sleep. All seats provide personal on-demand entertainment systems, exquisite meal service and a variety of pampering amenities.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h3&#62;Travelers Delight in Korean Air Business Class Seats&#60;/h3&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Prestige class travelers enjoy either the Prestige Sleeper Suite or the Prestige Plus seat. The Prestige Sleeper Suite offers seats that recline completely flat for relaxing slumber, and the Prestige Plus seat reclines for in-flight comfort. Both feature ample storage and work space, individual reading lamps and personal on-demand entertainment systems.&#60;/p&#62;
</bodyColumn_1><bodyColumn_2>&#60;p&#62;Prestige class travelers delight in a wide range of culinary treasures, from Korean and Japanese fare to Chinese and Western dishes, all created by a first-class chef. Prestige and first class passengers on Korean Air&#38;#39;s A380-800 aircraft may indulge at the in-flight Celestial Bar and lounge, featuring Absolut Vodka cocktails.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h3&#62;Korean Air: &#38;quot;Excellence In Flight&#38;quot;&#60;/h3&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;With all of its many first and Prestige class services, there are plenty of reasons to travel with Korean Air. With a main hub at Incheon International Airport, Korean Air transports 24.2 million passengers to 125 cities in 45 countries each year. Named as Asia&#38;#39;s best airline in 2012 by&#38;#160;Business Traveler, the airline&#38;#39;s accolades include:&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;ul&#62;
    &#60;li&#62;Grand Final World&#38;#39;s Most Innovative Airline, 2012 World Travel Awards;&#60;/li&#62;
    &#60;li&#62;Most Preferred Airline in China,&#38;#160;Travel+Leisure&#38;#160;magazine and&#60;/li&#62;
    &#60;li&#62;Best Asian Airline,&#38;#160;Voyage Magazine, 2011.&#60;/li&#62;
    &#60;/ul&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;With splendor provided by Korean Air, there is every reason to take advantage of IFlyFirstClass&#38;#39; spectacular deals on first class seats, business class fares and last minute first class flights.&#60;/p&#62;
</bodyColumn_2><browserTitle>Korean Air Business and First Class Flights | Tickets and prices - I Fly First Class</browserTitle><seo><description>I Fly First Class offers Korean Air business and first class flights to a wide range of destinations all over the world. Send request for more information.
</description><keywords>flight, korean air, first class, business class, i fly first class</keywords></seo><images><image><alias>739e11f542524324ac9d6be1f6bd577b.jpg</alias><content_id>11</content_id><title>first class tickets by korean air</title><queue>0</queue></image><image><alias>4adb76ba77f8476e88efab41924f6afb.jpg</alias><content_id>11</content_id><title>Last Minute Business Class Flights</title><queue>1</queue></image><image><alias>b1c87d54790b4373b1e271e53e5cd0a7.jpg</alias><content_id>11</content_id><title>Cheap Business Class Airline </title><queue>2</queue></image></images></item><item><airline_id>12</airline_id><name>American Airlines</name><title>Flights with American Airlines</title><sub_title>Discounted Business Class Tickets on American Airlines, Save Up to 70% on Your Last Minute Flight.</sub_title><alias>american-airlines</alias><summary>Travel in Luxury with best deals business class by american airlines

    &#38;#160;

    Jaunt across the globe in style with IFlyFirstClass&#38;#39; discounted American Airlines business class fares, first class tickets and last minute first class seats. You&#38;#39;ll save thousands on first class flights and hundreds on business class flights so that you can arrive at your thrilling destination feeling pampered and ready to go
</summary><bodyColumn_1>&#60;p&#62;Jaunt across the globe in style with IFlyFirstClass&#38;#39; discounted American Airlines business class fares, first class tickets and last minute first class seats. You&#38;#39;ll save thousands on first class flights and hundreds on business class flights so that you can arrive at your thrilling destination feeling pampered and ready to go.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h3&#62;American Airlines: &#38;quot;The New American is Arriving&#38;quot;&#60;/h3&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Already a significant presence in U.S. aviation, Fort Worth-based American Airlines will become the world&#38;#39;s largest airline if the proposed merger between American Airlines and US Airways Group is approved. Currently, American&#38;#39;s fleet of 900 aircraft flies to 260 airports in 50 countries with 3,500 daily departures. More than 500 new aircraft will soon join the existing fleet, making American&#38;#39;s fleet the most modern and up-to-date in North America.&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    Recognized for its current service standards and capabilities, the airline earned notable recognition in 2012:&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;- &#38;quot;World&#38;#39;s Leading Airline to North America,&#38;quot; 2012 World Airline Awards;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;- &#38;quot;Airline Program of the Year,&#38;quot; Freddie Awards;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;- &#38;quot;Best Elite Program,&#38;quot; Freddie Awards;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;- &#38;quot;Best Customer Service,&#38;quot; Freddie Awards;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;- &#38;quot;Best Domestic First Class Airline,&#38;quot;&#38;#160;Global Traveler&#38;#160;magazine and&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;- Three gold medals, North American Travel Journalists Association Awards.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h3&#62;&#60;br /&#62;
    Delight in Comfort at the Airport&#60;/h3&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;For passengers with American&#38;#39;s first class seats and business class tickets, the pampering begins at the airport. American welcomes its premium travelers to a number of exclusive airport lounges designed to help passengers relax and make the most of their time waiting for flights to begin.&#38;#160;&#60;/p&#62;
</bodyColumn_1><bodyColumn_2>&#60;p&#62;International first class ticket holders are welcomed into the air carrier&#38;#39;s Flagship Lounges at New York&#38;#39;s JFK, Los Angeles, London&#38;#39;s Heathrow and Chicago airports. The stunning Flagship Lounges present bountiful culinary options, premium cocktails and beverages, serene relaxation areas and helpful business facilities.&#38;#160;&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    First class and business class passengers traveling to or through London&#38;#39;s Heathrow Airport are treated to the luxurious accommodations of American&#38;#39;s Arrivals Lounge. There, you&#38;#39;ll find refreshing showers, clothes-pressing services, complimentary beverages and a breakfast bar.&#38;#160;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h3&#62;Relish the Luxury of First Class Seats&#60;/h3&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;International travelers are pampered with a gracious bed turn-down service that features a comfortable bed topper, plush duvet, fresh pajamas and Dermalogica&#38;reg; skincare amenity kits. Many first class flights also offer passengers a tablet computer loaded with 70 movies, delectable meals designed by renowned chef Richard Sandoval and ample leg room. Some flights feature capacious seats that swivel to face a work station and dining area more comfortably.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h3&#62;Relax in Business Class Seats&#60;/h3&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;International business class passengers are nearly as pampered as first class travelers with stellar bed turn-down service, Dermologica&#38;reg; skin care amenity kits, reclining seats and savory snacks.&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    Whether you prefer spacious business class fares or discounted luxurious last minute first class tickets, IFlyFirstClass will deliver you to your destination in style for less. With IFlyFirstClass and American Airlines, your trip across the nation or around the world is relaxing and affordable with our special first class tickets.&#60;/p&#62;
</bodyColumn_2><browserTitle>American Airlines Flights - First and Business Class Tickets - I Fly First Class</browserTitle><seo><description>Discounted American Airlines first and business class flights with I Fly First Class. Best prices for luxurious flights. Send request for more information.
</description><keywords>flight, amerian airlines, first class, business class, i fly first class</keywords></seo><images><image><alias>7543de88d1d94393bf91feca2ca0debe.jpg</alias><content_id>12</content_id><title>best deals business class by american airlines</title><queue>0</queue></image><image><alias>193bbb24cab54885befaaf82ef4595c7.jpg</alias><content_id>12</content_id><title>cheap business class to hong kong</title><queue>1</queue></image><image><alias>b67e3af3ef6544dbb4ded3db302a3d28.jpg</alias><content_id>12</content_id><title>first class airline tickets</title><queue>2</queue></image></images></item></items>