<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?><items><item><continent_id>1</continent_id><name>Europe</name><title>Flights to Europe</title><sub_title>Cheap Business Class To Europe</sub_title><alias>to-europe</alias><summary>Enjoy your own present-day Grand Tour of the &#38;quot;Continent&#38;quot; by exploring balmy Mediterranean beaches, breathtaking Alpine adventures and the many cultural delights of Europe. Save thousands on first class seats, business class fares and last minute first class flights to dozens of European destinations with IFlyFirstClass&#38;#39; magnificent discounts.&#38;#160;
</summary><bodyColumn_1>&#60;h3&#62;Why Visit Europe?&#60;/h3&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Europe has always been a light for the world, a center of learning, development, of the fine arts and of philosophy. From the incomparable ancient cities of Athens and Rome to the evergreen beacons of London and Paris to the far reaches of Eastern Europe where ancient traditions still thrive, the continent is a wonder of discovery, of learning and of humanity.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;The northern reaches of Europe stretch to the Arctic Circle where the wondrous phenomenon of the Northern Lights has transfixed Man&#38;#8217;s eyes for time immemorial. The beaches and clubs of Ibiza and other resplendent international party destinations show that Europe is as fun-loving as she is proud of her past.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h3&#62;Airlines that fly to Europe&#60;/h3&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;There are hundreds of airlines that service the European sector. In fact, there is no world-class international airline that would be considered a real contender in the industry if it was unable to fly to Europe. Almost every European country has its own airline and they fly hundreds of routes between the United States and Europe. There are direct flights between virtually every major European city and the American mainland every day.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Aside from large carriers, a number of smaller budget airlines also fly the United States to Europe route.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h3&#62;Flight characteristics&#60;/h3&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Just as there is such a diverse range of airlines that fly between destinations in the United States and Europe, there are countless flight choices as well.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;The best services and amenities are available on routes to major European cities like:&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;ul&#62;
    &#60;li&#62;London;&#60;/li&#62;
    &#60;li&#62;Paris;&#60;/li&#62;
    &#60;li&#62;Madrid;&#60;/li&#62;
    &#60;li&#62;Berlin;&#60;/li&#62;
    &#60;li&#62;Rome.&#60;/li&#62;
    &#60;/ul&#62;
</bodyColumn_1><bodyColumn_2>&#60;p&#62;First class and &#60;a href=&#34;https://www.iflyfirstclass.com/service/one-way-business-class-tickets&#34;&#62;business class services&#60;/a&#62; offer the very best in in-flight entertainment choices, noise-cancelling earphones, customized amenity kits, gourmet dining choices, in-flight buffets, personal turn-down service and lie-flat beds.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Most airlines offer the premium range of services on the routes to and from the airport, city or country that they are based. For that reason, it is advisable to fly the national carriers of the respective European nations when traveling to Europe.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h3&#62;Why buy tickets with I Fly First Class?&#60;/h3&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Our clients choose us because our services deliver premium flight experiences for the lowest prices available anywhere.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;I Fly First Class is much more than just a travel service &#38;ndash; we provide a personal travel concierge facility that gives you complete ease of mind before you even make your air travel reservations.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;We have an established network that allows us access to book first class and business class tickets with last minute offers, cheap deals, fare sales and airfare discounts at very low cost. Whether you are looking for a domestic or international flight, one-way or round trip, we can put you on the plane you want tomorrow.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h3&#62;How to find ticket on I Fly First Class&#60;/h3&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;If you like simplicity, you will love I Fly First Class. Our three prong system makes looking for and finding the lowest prices to travel to Europe easier than it has ever been.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;If you want to speak to our travel experts right now or at any other time, simply pick up the phone and call us toll-free in the U.S.A. at &#60;span style=&#34;color:#0000FF;&#34;&#62;1-800- 385-1359&#60;/span&#62;.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;If you would rather leave your details and requirements and have us contact you with the best deals, you can either email us at &#60;span style=&#34;color:#0000FF;&#34;&#62;info@flyfirst.com&#60;/span&#62; or complete the online form at www.iflyfirstclass.com.&#60;/p&#62;
</bodyColumn_2><browserTitle>Cheap First and Business Class Flights - Last Minute Flights to Europe | I Fly First Class</browserTitle><first_class_price>3760</first_class_price><first_class_old_price>6890</first_class_old_price><business_class_price>2870</business_class_price><business_class_old_price>3740</business_class_old_price><seo><description>Last minute first and business class flights to Europe at I Fly First Class. Best airfare deals and the most comfortable flights! Send your request and we will find air ticket to Europe just for you!</description><keywords>flight, europe, first, business, class, i fly first class</keywords></seo><images><image><alias>8d96621d9db04585942655e9323aa278.jpg</alias><content_id>1</content_id><title>Discounted flight tickets to Europe​</title><queue>0</queue></image><image><alias>d039276a7e1141b5a713b3859ebb84d7.jpg</alias><content_id>1</content_id><title>Business Class Discounted Flight to Europe​</title><queue>1</queue></image><image><alias>82fe9c3d2faf4989a76cd5454655a5f9.jpg</alias><content_id>1</content_id><title>First Class Airline Tickets to Europe​</title><queue>2</queue></image></images></item><item><continent_id>2</continent_id><name>Asia</name><title>Flights to Asia</title><sub_title>Cheap Business and First class to Asia</sub_title><alias>to-asia</alias><summary>Enjoy cheap business class to Acheap business class to asiasia.&#38;#160;The mysteries of the Orient are just waiting to be explored, from the mountaintops of Nepal to the treasured temples of Thailand and India. Create an unforgettable adventure to Asia with IFlyFirstClass&#38;#39;&#38;#160;unbeatable discounts&#38;#160;on luxury first class fares,&#38;#160;business class seats&#38;#160;and&#38;#160;last minute first class deals. Thousands of dollars less than other premium airfare, these luxury flights will pamper and delight you as you travel to the mystical land of&#38;#160;Asia.
</summary><bodyColumn_1>&#60;h3&#62;Why Visit Asia?&#60;/h3&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;The world&#38;#8217;s largest continent covers almost 45 million square miles and is called home by over 4 billion people spread across almost 50 countries. The land, the people, the culture and the heritage is so diverse that a visit to Asia is an introduction to virtually the entire world.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Asia was an exotic place, well out of reach of any but the hardiest travelers, merchants and adventurers for millennia. This allowed it to flourish as a center of learning, of philosophy and of religion. The world&#38;#8217;s greatest religions all had their genesis in Asia.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Today, the Asian nations have harnessed their vast land, huge populations and rich resources to create an unmissable feast for the eyes, the palate and the mind. No world traveler is truly a world traveler if they have not set foot in Asia.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h3&#62;Airlines that fly to Asia&#60;/h3&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Apart from small regional airways, there are very few airlines that do not fly to Asia. It is the biggest tourism destination and air travel has made it cheap and easy for people the world over to discover its hidden treasures.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Not only does practically every international airline fly to the Asian continent, many of the world&#38;#8217;s largest airlines are now based in Asia.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Because it is such a large mass of land and separated by significant water bodies, not many airlines service every single part of Asia. Some of the best ones for a direct flight from the United States to Asia are:&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;ul&#62;
    &#60;li&#62;Air India;&#60;/li&#62;
    &#60;li&#62;American Airlines;&#60;/li&#62;
    &#60;li&#62;ANA;&#60;/li&#62;
    &#60;li&#62;China Airlines;&#60;/li&#62;
    &#60;li&#62;Delta;&#60;/li&#62;
    &#60;li&#62;El Al;&#60;/li&#62;
    &#60;li&#62;Japan Airlines;&#60;/li&#62;
    &#60;li&#62;Korean Air;&#60;/li&#62;
    &#60;li&#62;Singapore Airlines;&#60;/li&#62;
    &#60;li&#62;&#60;a href=&#34;https://www.iflyfirstclass.com/airline/united&#34; title=&#34;First class flights with United&#34;&#62;United&#60;/a&#62;.&#60;/li&#62;
    &#60;/ul&#62;
</bodyColumn_1><bodyColumn_2>&#60;h3&#62;Flight characteristics&#60;/h3&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;A flight from the United States to Asia is vary variable; the shortest flights are very short and the longest could take over a day of flying to complete.&#38;#160;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Russia is considered part of the Asian continent. Hence, the shortest cross-continental flight from the U.S to Asia is from Anchorage, Alaska to Petropavlovsk-Kamchatsky in Russia. This international flight will take 4 hours 42 minutes.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Flights east between the U.S. and the furthest reaches of Asia take over 18 hours to complete.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;The flight duration is also affected by the fact that geodesic routes are seldom taken; the preferred routes minimize time over water and stick to safe zones in friendly skies.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h3&#62;Why buy tickets with I Fly First Class?&#60;/h3&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;I Fly First Class is not your regular travel agency, nor are we simply a travel agency that specializes in premium air travel. No, what sets us apart is that we are intimately connected to airlines and are able to procure the best deals for the cheapest flights to any city in Asia.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Our system allows us to get last minute specials when others might tell you sets are no longer available. We can obtain special deals at discount rates to which no one else has access.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;If you are looking to travel to Asia and fly in style for a cheap price, then I Fly First Class should be your first choice.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h3&#62;How to find tickets on I Fly First Class&#60;/h3&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;I Fly First Class has made the process of finding the best deals very simple &#38;ndash; we do all the work. You simply have to tell us what you require and we will find the best deals and best prices for you. The three options you can use are:&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;ul&#62;
    &#60;li&#62;Our toll-free helpline in the U.S.: &#60;span style=&#34;color:#0000FF;&#34;&#62;1-800-385-1359&#60;/span&#62; &#38;ndash; call us and speak to our friendly travel concierge staff immediately.&#60;/li&#62;
    &#60;li&#62;Email us at &#60;span style=&#34;color:#0000FF;&#34;&#62;info@flyfirst.com&#60;/span&#62; &#38;ndash; we will contact you with your best options.&#60;/li&#62;
    &#60;li&#62;Visit our website, www.iflyfirstclass.com, and fill in the online form &#38;ndash; the detailed choices will be delivered to you how you choose.&#60;/li&#62;
    &#60;/ul&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;I Fly First Class is committed to ensuring &#60;a href=&#34;https://www.iflyfirstclass.com/service/first-class-specials&#34;&#62;cheap first class&#60;/a&#62; and business class travel to people just like you. Use one of those three options to contact us and discover why we are considered the best.&#60;/p&#62;
</bodyColumn_2><browserTitle>First and Business class Flights to Asia | Prices, Airfares | I Fly First Class</browserTitle><first_class_price>4870</first_class_price><first_class_old_price>6340</first_class_old_price><business_class_price>3280</business_class_price><business_class_old_price>4640</business_class_old_price><seo><description>Best airfare offers to Asia are here. I Fly First Class guarantees top-quality service and best prices on first and business class flights to Asia.</description><keywords>cheap business class to asia, cheap first class flights, cheapest business class flights to asia, cheap business class tickets to asia, cheap business class flights to asia, cheap business class to asia</keywords></seo><images><image><alias>decc726232cd45e691a9e8cd69d748b6.jpg</alias><content_id>2</content_id><title>Discounted flight tickets to Asia</title><queue>0</queue></image><image><alias>53510f32475343a89c10a3ea0f44f85f.jpg</alias><content_id>2</content_id><title>Business Class Discounted Flight to Asia</title><queue>1</queue></image><image><alias>18256cbc11c4469bb1e9b09b6c2407fa.jpg</alias><content_id>2</content_id><title>First Class Airline Tickets to Asia</title><queue>2</queue></image></images></item><item><continent_id>3</continent_id><name>Australia</name><title>Flights to Australia</title><sub_title>Cheap business class to Australia</sub_title><alias>to-australia</alias><summary>Cheerful vineyards, glamorous coastal cities and a vast Outback invite you to explore the wonder of gorgeous&#38;#160;Australia. Make the journey delightful with outstanding&#38;#160;first class deals&#38;#160;and&#38;#160;reduced business class tickets&#38;#160;from IFlyFirstClass. You&#38;#39;ll make the long flight to the land of Oz in affordable splendor, leaving you plenty of energy and budget to fully appreciate the country&#38;#39;s numerous treasures.
</summary><bodyColumn_1>&#60;div&#62;Cheerful vineyards, glamorous coastal cities and a vast Outback invite you to explore the wonder of gorgeous Australia. Make the journey delightful with outstanding first class deals and reduced business class tickets from IFlyFirstClass. You&#38;#39;ll make the long flight to the land of Oz in affordable splendor, leaving you plenty of energy and budget to fully appreciate the country&#38;#39;s numerous treasures.&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;h3&#62;Wining, Diving and Roaming&#60;/h3&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;Australian wineries are taking the international stage as the world&#38;#39;s fourth largest wine exporter. Hundreds of vineyards and tasting rooms stretch across the country, from Swan Valley on the western side of the country east to The Barossa, Yarra Valley and Hunter Valley. Wine tastings, festivals and prolific farms offer fanciful entertainment and feasts for palates of all persuasions.&#38;#160;Cheap Business Class to Australia&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;Bounded on all sides by several oceans, Australia&#38;#39;s coastlines create one-of-a-kind playgrounds with diverse activities and features. Scuba divers and snorkelers delight in the Great Barrier Reef&#38;#39;s teeming sea life on the country&#38;#39;s northeast side. Australia&#38;#39;s surf culture is legendary, with world-class waves and surfing spots from the country&#38;#39;s eastern shores to its western beaches. Relaxing ocean baths or &#38;quot;bogey holes&#38;quot; carved into the cliffs of New South Wales in the early 1800s create rejuvenating swimming holes near charming beach towns and communities. With all of the attractions in store for visitors to the country&#38;#39;s shores, you&#38;#39;ll appreciate the value of traveling to the ponderous country in the tranquility of discount business class tickets and fantastic first class deals.&#60;/div&#62;
</bodyColumn_1><bodyColumn_2>&#60;div&#62;Thrill-seekers revel in Australia&#38;#39;s many activities, including scaling the towering Sydney Harbor Bridge, hiking the Overland Trail and marveling at the crocodiles and exotic wildlife at Daintree Village. Fascinating days can be spent hiking the Blue Mountains and ascending its steep peaks on the the Scenic Cableway, exploring the indigenous wildlife at the Lone Pine Koala Sanctuary and checking out the many rare fossils at Riversleigh.&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    Cosmopolitan cities rim the country&#38;#39;s surface. On the east, beautiful Sydney is known for its white-roofed Opera House and iconic harbor bridge. Culturally rich Melbourne to the south overflows with trendy shops, sporting events, a vibrant film industry and museums. Parks, beaches, performance halls and heritage sites lure visitors to Perth on the west, while beach sunset markets, rousing festivals and extensive parks entertain tourists and locals in Darwin to the north.&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;h3&#62;The IFlyFirstClass Advantage&#60;/h3&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;Luxury and comfort are the hallmarks of premium flights, and IFlyFirstClass offers fabulous&#38;#160;first class deals&#38;#160;and&#38;#160;business class seats&#38;#160;to many Australian destinations so that you can enjoy your trip from start to finish. Exclusive airport lounges and spacious airplane cabins provide the ultimate in service and amenities to pamper you throughout your trip.&#38;#160;&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    With IFlyFirstClass, you save thousands of dollars on luxury travel, but receive all of the full-price splendor. Make the most of your time and money with IFlyFirstClass&#38;#39; unrivaled discounts on business class seats, last minute flights and first class deals to sunny&#38;#160;Australia.&#60;/div&#62;
</bodyColumn_2><browserTitle>Cheap Flight Deals to Australia with IFlyFirstClass</browserTitle><first_class_price>5640</first_class_price><first_class_old_price>9780</first_class_old_price><business_class_price>4390</business_class_price><business_class_old_price>5270</business_class_old_price><seo><description>Best deals and low prices on first and business class flights to Australia. Great fares only at IFlyFirstClass.</description><keywords>cheap business class to Australia, Cheap flights to Australia</keywords></seo><images><image><alias>4a1c5fc7ff03465c8a4e8ea3e749a98f.jpg</alias><content_id>3</content_id><title>Discounted flight tickets to Australia</title><queue>0</queue></image><image><alias>78f3a2b68aae4691bb0267a04c1796d2.jpg</alias><content_id>3</content_id><title>Business Class Discounted Flight to Australia</title><queue>1</queue></image><image><alias>cc461a50538b4c7c8dcdcb3cfeec55ce.jpg</alias><content_id>3</content_id><title>First Class Airline Tickets to Australia</title><queue>2</queue></image></images></item></items>