<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?><items><item><travel_tips_id>1</travel_tips_id><title>Adelaide Adventures Begin with a Business Class Flight to Adelaide</title><alias>business-class-flight-to-adelaide</alias><summary>The party is on at Adelaide’s festivals, scenic beaches and wildlife adventures. Discover the city’s top attractions, and prepare for a trip of a lifetime.

    At its heart, Adelaide is a city that celebrates nature, art, people and culture. Welcoming boulevards and colorfully landscaped parks here are as entrancing as the city&#39;s rich history and trendy food and wine scenes. Adelaide’s early openness to all religions gave it its nickname, “The City of Churches.” Today, that broad-minded spirit and hospitality live on in Adelaide’s fondness for festivals celebrating art, lifestyle, food, wine and international culture. Now more commonly known as “The Festival City,” Adelaide buzzes with activity. Its Adelaide Fringe Festival alone is a month-long celebration of cabaret, film, music, visual art, dance and design. The party in Adelaide’s clean streets continues with other festivals like WOMADelaide, Adelaide Cabaret Festival, Adelaide Festival of Ideas, FEAST, Tasting Australia and Adelaide Film Festival. So many events are held in March that locals refer to the season as Mad March.

    The city and its residents are also inspired by its unique location on the appealing Gulf of St. Vincent. If you’re enjoying a business class flight to Adelaide, you’ll probably get a good look at the scenic gulf as well as a peek at the picturesque River Torrens meandering through the city. The gulf’s beaches and the River Torrens provide countless recreation options for locals and visitors. Your last minute business class tickets to Adelaide are waiting! </summary><browserTitle>Adelaide Adventures Begin with a Business Class Flight | IFlyFirstClass Travel Tips</browserTitle><created_date>2/6/2016 7:05:49 AM</created_date><seo><description>Adelaide Adventures Begin with a Business Class Flight to Adelaide. More interesting information and travel tips at IFlyFirstClass.</description><keywords>Business Class Flight to Adelaide</keywords></seo><images><image><alias>de68dd29b93f4c64aec7378f801f2347.png</alias><content_id>1</content_id><title>Cheapest Business Class Flight to Adelaide </title><queue>0</queue></image></images></item><item><travel_tips_id>2</travel_tips_id><title>Relish the Art, History and Beauty of Barcelona. Thanks to First Class Flights to Barcelona</title><alias>memorable-first-class-flights-to-barcelona</alias><summary>
    On the surface, Barcelona is cosmopolitan and sophisticated. As your first class flight to Barcelona descends into the city, you’ll notice glitzy high-rise buildings, abundant street traffic and the activity of 1.6 million people.

    Once you explore the city at street level, though, Barcelona’s unique culture, plentiful art and historical importance become evident. From Gaudi’s intriguing architecture to Pablo Picasso’s paintings, ceramics and local restaurant menus, many ground-breaking artists over the centuries have made Barcelona their home.

    As part of the distinct Catalonia region, Barcelona is also unique for its culture. Sant Jordi is the patron saint of Catalonia and inspires one of Barcelona’s most festive and romantic days. If you’re in Barcelona on April 23, you’ll enjoy the combined Sant Jordi celebration and the city’s festival of books. You’ll see men giving women red roses, women giving men books and well-known authors hosting book-signings on the streets. You might also catch sight of another Catalan tradition: teams of castellers forming human towers reaching as tall as 45 feet.

    Barcelona is full of adventures and experiences you’re unlikely to find anywhere else. Take advantage of deals on premium flights to Barcelona so you can discover the beauty of the city.</summary><browserTitle>Relish the Art, History and Beauty of Barcelona. | IFlyFirstClass Travel Tips</browserTitle><created_date>2/29/2016 3:13:26 PM</created_date><seo><description>Relish the Art, History and Beauty of Barcelona. Thanks to First Class Flights to Barcelona. More interesting information and travel tips at IFlyFirstClass.</description><keywords>First Class Flights to Barcelona</keywords></seo><images><image><alias>fd180a8750ea46ecacd0ae0647eda8d1.png</alias><content_id>2</content_id><title>Incredable First Class Flights to Barcelona</title><queue>0</queue></image></images></item><item><travel_tips_id>3</travel_tips_id><title>History, Food and Humor Delight with Business Class Flights to Brussels</title><alias>amazing-business-class-flights-to-brussels</alias><summary>Brussels has been a bastion of economic success, history and whimsy for centuries, and it’s the ideal business and pleasure destination. Its historic wealth gained from the merchant trade is evident in many of its public buildings and squares, including La Grand-Place and Hôtel de Ville. The capital of Belgium, Brussels is sophisticated but doesn’t take itself too seriously. Its playful sense of humor and rebellious spirit is evident in the Manneken Pis statue/fountain and his never-ending rotation of costumes.

    Brussels is also home to many of the European Union’s most important offices. The European Quarter’s European Parliament building, European Commission and Council of the European Union determine important issues for the EU’s 500 million residents.

    Above all, Brussels is a gastronomic delight. Begin the day with the city’s legendary Liege waffles, grab a delectable pastry or nibble on a speculoo cookie. Lunches and dinners are rich with delicious stews, rich beers and filling sausages. The Belgians have mastered the potato as evidenced by its creamy stoemp and out-of-this-world french fries. Of course, every meal should be topped off with a bit of sumptuous Belgian chocolate. If you’re lucky, you might even be able to sample the chocolate delicacy on your business class flight to Brussels; the perfect way to begin a Belgian adventure.</summary><browserTitle>History, Food and Humor Delight with Business Class Flights | IFlyFirstClass Travel Tips</browserTitle><created_date>3/2/2016 7:03:49 PM</created_date><seo><description>History, Food and Humor Delight with Business Class Flights to Brussels. More interesting information and travel tips at IFlyFirstClass.</description><keywords>Business Class Flights to Brussels</keywords></seo><images><image><alias>5d88f3113c72425b8b7df88e4e9a5778.png</alias><content_id>3</content_id><title>Amazing aBusiness Class Flights to Brussels</title><queue>0</queue></image></images></item><item><travel_tips_id>4</travel_tips_id><title>Glamour and Excitement Are at the End of a First Class Flight to Dubai</title><alias>glamour-first-class-flight-to-dubai</alias><summary>Thriving industries, an ever-expanding tourism market and exclusive amenities make first class flights to Dubai a prime service. No city is better suited to the glamour of first class than glossy Dubai. The desert seaside oasis is known for its modern developments and sophisticated wealth, and a trip here never disappoints.

    Its resorts are legendary for their luxury and service, offering their guests everything from golden iPads to roaming belly dancers and henna artists. The most visually iconic resort, the Burj al Arab, is an emblem of the city’s cosmopolitan and nearly over-the-top prosperity. Everything is immense here, and nothing is done in half measures. Dubai is home to seven of the 10 tallest hotels in the world, with its JW Marriott Marquis topping the list. It has the world’s biggest shopping mall, the best Gold Souk bazaar, the biggest fireworks display, the highest base jump, the biggest man-made dive site and the longest luxury car parade.

    In spite of this sleek, modern attitude, Dubai never forgets its roots as a seaside desert community with a rich history. Its traditional souks remain a valued part of everyday life. It works to preserve its rich desert flora and fauna. Its many spectacular mosques honor the country’s religious and architectural heritage. With all this in store, Dubai is a place like no other.</summary><browserTitle>Glamour and Excitement Are at the End of a First Class | IFlyFirstClass Travel Tips</browserTitle><created_date>3/4/2016 11:42:32 AM</created_date><seo><description>Glamour and Excitement Are at the End of a First Class Flight to Dubai. More interesting information and travel tips at IFlyFirstClass.</description><keywords>a First Class Flight to Dubai</keywords></seo><images><image><alias>030ecef912ee40eaa0f81f64e110c0aa.png</alias><content_id>4</content_id><title>Excitement of a First Class Flight to Dubai</title><queue>0</queue></image></images></item><item><travel_tips_id>5</travel_tips_id><title>South African Adventures with First Class Flights to Johannesburg</title><alias>amazing-first-class-flights-to-johannesburg</alias><summary>A relatively young city, Johannesburg is nevertheless the art and fashion heart of South Africa. The gold rush of the late 1800s spurred the city’s development, and it became central to South Africa’s path to equality and reconciliation in the ensuing years. The city is big, accommodating 3.2 million residents. It is cosmopolitan with a Central Business District that sports a number of high-rise buildings and a Braamfontein university area known for its nightlife. There are dozens of sites you’ll want to visit while you’re in town, including Constitution Hill, Johannesburg Art Gallery, Sci-Bono Discovery Centre and the Origins Centre. The Soweto district also offers fascinating attractions, from the Mandela Family Museum to the Apartheid Museum.

    Many visitors enjoy staying in the northern suburbs where they can easily enjoy the planetarium, spend the morning in Nelson Mandela Square or cheer on a cricket game at Wanderers Stadium. Traveling even farther afield you’ll find other enjoyable pursuits. The Lesedi Cultural Village, in particular, is an excellent place to learn authentic Africa villages, culture, dance and food. Sophiatown tours and visits to the Suikerbosrand Nature Reserve are also well worth your time following a first class flight to Johannesburg.</summary><browserTitle>South African Adventures with First Class Flights to Johannesburg | IFlyFirstClass Travel Tips</browserTitle><created_date>3/7/2016 5:45:59 PM</created_date><seo><description>South African Adventures with First Class Flights to Johannesburg. More interesting information and travel tips at IFlyFirstClass.</description><keywords>First Class Flights to Johannesburg</keywords></seo><images><image><alias>7dd8b8bc30df48c09af07f3995a33507.png</alias><content_id>5</content_id><title>Best Todays First Class Flights to Johannesburg</title><queue>0</queue></image></images></item><item><travel_tips_id>6</travel_tips_id><title>First Class Flights to Milan Lead to First Class Experiences</title><alias>first-class-flights-to-milan-experiences</alias><summary>Vibrant Milan is the heart of Italy’s fashion, business and banking activity and a beautifully historic city. The third largest European Union economy, Milan is a common destination for business and pleasure travel. Whether you’re taking a business class flight to Milan to advance your career or simply enjoying a holiday, Milan will delight you with its energy.

    It’s easier to understand the depth of Milan’s history when you consider that it was the capital of the Western Roman Empire from the 3rd to the 5th centuries. Various countries ruled over Milan in the ensuing 1600 years, each leaving its mark on the city. The Colonne di San Lorenzo is one of the few remnants of Milan’s Western Roman Empire days, and it’s a treasure. There are dozens of other historic sites that are worth a visit and dozens of other museums and attractions to see while you’re in Milan.

    You’ll get a better sense of the city’s personality, though, if you visit a mix of historic and modern cultural sites. Tour places like the Castello Sforzesco but be sure to take in a performance at Teatro alla Scala or a world-class soccer game at San Siro Stadium. By mixing your trip up a little, you’ll get a chance to mingle with locals and benefit from their knowledge of the city.
</summary><browserTitle>First Class Flights to Milan Lead to First Class Experiences | IFlyFirstClass Travel Tips</browserTitle><created_date>3/7/2016 7:21:25 PM</created_date><seo><description>First Class Flights to Milan Lead to First Class Experiences. More interesting information and travel tips at IFlyFirstClass.</description><keywords>First Class Flights to Milan </keywords></seo><images><image><alias>f42bbe482d9340efad72805ff1c1b692.png</alias><content_id>6</content_id><title>Unique First Class Flight to Milan</title><queue>0</queue></image></images></item><item><travel_tips_id>7</travel_tips_id><title>Enjoy Business and Pleasure with First Class Flights to Osaka</title><alias>pleasure-to-fly-business-and-first-class-flights-to-osaka</alias><summary>
    The bustling bayside metropolis of Osaka has 2.5 million residents within its boundaries but nearly 9 million people within its expansive region. The downtown Kita area and the Nakanoshima district gleam with most of Osaka’s skyscrapers, while the central Minami district is the older vibrant business district. Osaka Bay is on the city’s west side, offering a variety of visitor-oriented attractions and activities like Tempozan Harbour Village and Universal Studios.

    With the city’s many thriving industries, first class flights to Osaka are plentiful and widely available yearround. If you can choose your time to travel to Osaka, though, opt for spring. Visitng in spring allows you to enjoy the city’s gorgeous and abundant displays of sakura, or cherry blossoms. June, July and September are the rainiest months in Osaka. That shouldn&#39;t be a problem if you&#39;re staying or working in the Kita area’s Umeda District though. The area has many underground malls, restaurants and provisions. As a result, it’s possible to avoid the rain much of the time.

    Cosmopolitan Osaka actually has a rich history stretching back to the 5th century B.C.E. This long, varied past combines with Osaka&#39;s sophisticated, modern present to offer a diverse and enchanting mix of attractions and activities. </summary><browserTitle>Enjoy Business and Pleasure with First Class Flights to Osaka | IFlyFirstClass Travel Tips</browserTitle><created_date>3/10/2016 12:31:20 PM</created_date><seo><description>Enjoy Business and Pleasure with First Class Flights to Osaka. More interesting information and travel tips at IFlyFirstClass.</description><keywords> Visit the city in style with business class flights to Osaka.</keywords></seo><images><image><alias>435f224cfe2e4bf6acc3251ea6bd2be7.png</alias><content_id>7</content_id><title>First Class Flights to Osaka are the Ultimate in Relaxation</title><queue>0</queue></image></images></item><item><travel_tips_id>8</travel_tips_id><title>San Francisco: First Class Flights to A First Class City</title><alias>san-francisco-first-class-flights</alias><summary>The City By the Bay is one of the country’s most scenic cities. Perched at the northernmost point of the San Francisco Peninsula, the city is home to highly respected financial, high-tech and medical institutions and renowned urban parks. It was California’s biggest city during the Gold Rush, and it remains a top destination for world travelers. The city’s skyline is instantly recognizable with landmarks like Coit Tower, the Transamerica Building, Alcatraz and the Golden Gate Bridge. It is beloved for its inescapable fog, delectable foodie scene, upscale shopping and world-class arts.

    Its neighborhoods are historic and delightful. San Francisco’s Chinatown is the oldest in the nation and remains a vibrant center of history, food, culture and shopping. North Beach is a haven for Italian food fans. Alamo Square is teeming with colorful Painted Ladies Victorian homes. The Castro is known for its LGBT activism; Russia Hill is famous for its stately mansions and the appealingly crooked Lombard Street, and Haight-Ashbury is relished for its funky shops and counterculture history. San Francisco may be a compact city, but it holds a wealth of fascinating cultures, enriching institutions and delightful attractions.</summary><browserTitle>San Francisco: First Class Flights to A First Class City | IFlyFirstClass Travel Tips</browserTitle><created_date>3/15/2016 1:42:45 PM</created_date><seo><description>San Francisco: First Class Flights to A First Class City. More interesting information and travel tips at IFlyFirstClass.</description><keywords>San Francisco First Class Flights</keywords></seo><images><image><alias>c012dc5e670041baa988979da1a3c4d8.png</alias><content_id>8</content_id><title>First Class Flights to San Francisco city</title><queue>0</queue></image></images></item><item><travel_tips_id>9</travel_tips_id><title>Business and First Class to Dusseldorf </title><alias>business-class-flight-dusseldorf</alias><summary>It’s true that Düsseldorf is a bustling city of commerce, but it’s also a fun-loving, historic city with dozens of appealing attractions. Situated on the Rhine River and the River Düssel, Düsseldorf is often named one of the most livable cities in the world. The features that make it eminently livable also make it an ideal destination for business and holiday travel.

    The city is the country’s center of telecommunications, advertising, publishing and technology, and it sports one of Germany’s most lauded shopping areas. If you’ve traveled on a first class flight to Düsseldorf, you’ll likely end up at The Kö, or Königsallee, at some point. The high-end shopping district brims with fashion house boutiques, upscale shopping malls and posh hotels.

    Düsseldorf is also deeply historic. Over the city&#39;s many centuries, it has been home to dukes, emperors, well-heeled art patrons and innovative artists. Cartwheelers play an important role in the city’s folklore, and travelers will notice Cartwheelers incorporated into Düsseldorf&#39;s public art, fountains and souvenirs. Perhaps Düsseldorf&#39;s most famous tradition, though, is its Altbier, or old-style beer. This heritage of art, food, beer and history lead to some of Düsseldorf&#39;s most captivating sites. Here are just a few of the city’s most popular attractions:</summary><browserTitle>Business and First Class to Dusseldorf | IFlyFirstClass Travel Tips</browserTitle><created_date>3/16/2016 8:07:45 AM</created_date><seo><description>Business and First Class to Dusseldorf. More interesting information and travel tips at IFlyFirstClass.</description><keywords>Cheap business and last minute first class ticket to dusseldorf </keywords></seo><images><image><alias>1d118e0d09634cd1b86eabfbbc98020c.jpg</alias><content_id>9</content_id><title>Dusseldorf</title><queue>0</queue></image></images></item><item><travel_tips_id>10</travel_tips_id><title>Title: Looking for a Thrill? Book a First Class Flight to Sydney</title><alias>booking-a-first-class-flight-to-sydney</alias><summary>Sydney is one of the most picturesque cities in the world. The capital of Australia’s New South Wales, Sydney is also one of the country’s most vibrant metropolitan areas. Known for its beaches, thriving businesses and incredible harbors, Sydney is always entertaining and dynamic. It’s home to colorful festivals, friendly residents, fun markets and countless museums, galleries, shops and attractions. Whether you take the historic self-guided walk along The Rocks or learn to surf at Palm Beach, there are dozens of attractions that make the Sydney experience unique and memorable.

    If you’re traveling with kids, there are a host of family-friendly activities in store. Ferry over to Taronga Zoo from Sydney’s Circular Quay for a chance to see the zoo’s 2,900 exotic animals, or gaze at the 700 sea creatures at SEA LIFE Aquarium. Families of all ages also enjoy the fun atmosphere in Darling Harbour, where shopping, dining and entertainment are plentiful. If you’re looking for a romantic trip, enjoy sunset sails and trips into the nearby Blue Mountains to visit local wineries.
</summary><browserTitle>Title: Looking for a Thrill? Book a First Class Flight to Sydney | IFlyFirstClass Travel Tips</browserTitle><created_date>3/19/2016 11:41:44 AM</created_date><seo><description>Title: Looking for a Thrill? Book a First Class Flight to Sydney. More interesting information and travel tips at IFlyFirstClass.</description><keywords> Looking for a Thrill? Book a First Class Flight to Sydney</keywords></seo><images><image><alias>48c99e0a1a704470bad42da498b73d46.png</alias><content_id>10</content_id><title> Book a First Class Flight to Sydney Today Formidable Price </title><queue>0</queue></image></images></item><item><travel_tips_id>11</travel_tips_id><title>Glamour and History Await Your First Class Flight to Zurich</title><alias>your-first-class-flight-to-zurich</alias><summary>Located in northern Switzerland, Zurich is a glamorous and important European city known for its global financial enterprises and international corporate headquarters. Excellent rail transportation, a thriving culinary scene and dozens of historic sites make visiting Zurich a joy. One of best ways to get there is to fly with first class.

    The city’s landscape is world-class, too, from its Romanesque Grossmunster spires to its enticing Lake Zurich. The Limmat and Sihl rivers meander through town, providing Zurich with a tranquil, picturesque ambiance that invites visitors and locals to gather. The city is only about 20 miles north of the Alps, and you can enjoy some glorious views of the mountains from the city center.

    Some of Zurich’s most legendary attractions, though, are its culinary delights and high-end products. You haven’t truly experienced Zurich until you&#39;ve tasted its famous chocolates; Zurich is the home of Lindt after all. Other must-try dishes include the sauteed veal and mushroom dish, Zürcher Geschnetzelte, and the country&#39;s infamously rich fondue. Given Switzerland’s renown as a capital for fine watchmaking, it’s no surprise that Zurich’s streets are filled with luxury watch boutiques. Several iconic high-end watch brands operate flagship stores here in Zurich, and it’s the perfect, albeit pricey, souvenir of your trip.

    With all of Zurich&#39;s thriving corporations, business class flights to the city are abundant. Occasional deals on these flights give you ample reason to visit this world-class city.</summary><browserTitle>Glamour and History Await Your First Class Flight to Zurich | IFlyFirstClass Travel Tips</browserTitle><created_date>3/21/2016 9:56:26 PM</created_date><seo><description>Glamour and History Await Your First Class Flight to Zurich. More interesting information and travel tips at IFlyFirstClass.</description><keywords>First Class Flight to Zurich</keywords></seo><images><image><alias>dbb805ab3100479885b906c6b4f1d438.png</alias><content_id>11</content_id><title>Last minute First Class Flight to Zurich Today</title><queue>0</queue></image></images></item><item><travel_tips_id>12</travel_tips_id><title>Amsterdam Is a First Class City of Fun, History, Culture</title><alias>cheapest-first-class-flights-to-amsterdam</alias><summary>Amsterdam may be famous for its lax attitudes about marijuana and prostitution, but the charming, picturesque city is so much more than its Red Light District. It is cultured, prosperous and historic, and it’s full of fascinating attractions and thought-provoking sites.Get the cheapest first class flights to Amsterdam today.

    Getting around Amsterdam is convenient. If your business class flight lands at Amsterdam’s Airport Schiphol, you can use the rail station under the passenger terminal to travel directly into the city. Once you’re in Amsterdam, join the city&#39;s robust bike culture and pedal around town. Ferries and trains can also deliver you to various local sites.

    Amsterdam has a number of interesting neighborhoods and attractions to keep you entertained throughout your stay. Vondelpark is the place to go for a relaxing afternoon of rollerblading and outdoor concerts. For a fun night of club- or casino-hopping, head to the Leidseplein. For a little culture, visit the Rijksmuseum art museum or take a canal cruise. From the Amsterdam Heineken Experience to tours of colorful tulip fields, Amsterdam offers dozens of unique attractions.</summary><browserTitle>Amsterdam Is a First Class City of Fun, History, Culture | IFlyFirstClass Travel Tips</browserTitle><created_date>3/22/2016 2:15:17 PM</created_date><seo><description>Amsterdam Is a First Class City of Fun, History, Culture. More interesting information and travel tips at IFlyFirstClass.</description><keywords>null</keywords></seo><images><image><alias>ba9611057e264f65b79cc8daa4cbf82d.png</alias><content_id>12</content_id><title>the cheapest first class flights to Amsterdam today</title><queue>0</queue></image></images></item><item><travel_tips_id>13</travel_tips_id><title>Take a First Class Flight Through History In Beijing</title><alias>first-class-flight-through-history-in-beijing</alias><summary>With 21 million people, Beijing is the world’s third most populous city. It is big and historic, ant it’s a fascinating destination, whether you’re hopping on a business class flight to take care of business or enjoying a pleasure trip. You’ll see historic imperial palaces, amazing ancient walls and grand architecture as well as tributes to China’s revolutionary and Communist history.

    There are dozens of one-of-a-kind landmarks and attractions here, and it can be tough to narrow down your “to-see.” list. From the Beijing National Stadium and Olympic Village to Yonghe Temple, Summer Palace and Beihai Park, you can stay busy all day and all night. The city is home to seven World Heritage Sites, countless modern attractions and incredible archeological parks. One of our favorite sites for putting China’s incredibly long history into perspective is Zhoukoudian, These caves are the discovery sites of Peking Man’s remains, animal bones dating back 690,000 years and tools dating back 530,000 years.

    With its entrancing history, gorgeous ancient architecture and bustling streets, Beijing is an experience like no other. Pace yourself, leave some time for restful pursuits and be sure to sample the city’s delicious cuisine so you can fuel your continued exploration of first class flight to Beijing.</summary><browserTitle>Take a First Class Flight Through History In Beijing  | IFlyFirstClass Travel Tips</browserTitle><created_date>3/23/2016 10:25:44 PM</created_date><seo><description>Take a First Class Flight Through History In Beijing. More interesting information and travel tips at IFlyFirstClass.</description><keywords>First Class Flight Through History In Beijing</keywords></seo><images><image><alias>c71cc4dd5a9b42b98deb34784a5efdce.png</alias><content_id>13</content_id><title>Book our cheap first class flights for an unforgettable journey.</title><queue>0</queue></image></images></item><item><travel_tips_id>14</travel_tips_id><title>Take a First Class Flight Through History In Dusseldorf</title><alias>get-a-first-class-flight-to-dusseldorf</alias><summary>It’s true that Düsseldorf is a bustling city of commerce, but it’s also a fun-loving, historic city with dozens of appealing attractions. Situated on the Rhine River and the River Düssel, Düsseldorf is often named one of the most livable cities in the world. The features that make it eminently livable also make it an ideal destination for business and holiday travel.

    The city is the country’s center of telecommunications, advertising, publishing and technology, and it sports one of Germany’s most lauded shopping areas. If you’ve traveled on a first class flight to Düsseldorf, you’ll likely end up at The Kö, or Königsallee, at some point. The high-end shopping district brims with fashion house boutiques, upscale shopping malls and posh hotels.

    Düsseldorf is also deeply historic. Over the city&#39;s many centuries, it has been home to dukes, emperors, well-heeled art patrons and innovative artists. Cartwheelers play an important role in the city’s folklore, and travelers will notice Cartwheelers incorporated into Düsseldorf&#39;s public art, fountains and souvenirs. Perhaps Düsseldorf&#39;s most famous tradition, though, is its Altbier, or old-style beer. This heritage of art, food, beer and history lead to some of Düsseldorf&#39;s most captivating sites. Here are just a few of the city’s most popular attractions:
</summary><browserTitle>Take a First Class Flight Through History In Dusseldorf | IFlyFirstClass Travel Tips</browserTitle><created_date>3/25/2016 4:18:36 PM</created_date><seo><description>Take a First Class Flight Through History In Dusseldorf. More interesting information and travel tips at IFlyFirstClass.</description><keywords>Take a First Class Flight Through History In Dusseldorf</keywords></seo><images><image><alias>8214abfe651447a88ef6fe3047bdc5a0.png</alias><content_id>14</content_id><title>Great   First Class Flight To Dusseldorf</title><queue>0</queue></image></images></item><item><travel_tips_id>15</travel_tips_id><title>First Class Flights to First Class Sights in London</title><alias>the-best-first-class-tickets-to-london</alias><summary>Pulsing with life, London is a wonderland of historic sites, modern attractions and captivating districts. With a history that dates back to early settlements 2,000 years ago, London overflows with character. It is the capital of the United Kingdom, a thriving financial hub and a renowned center of higher education. London boasts centuries-old landmarks and structures that lure millions of visitors each year, making cheap business class flights to the region plentiful. It has a busy river that attracts countless pleasure and commercial boaters and creates compelling business and tourism districts like the Docklands. London also hosts immense international sporting events, chic shopping areas along Regent and Jermyn streets and blockbuster theatrical performances in the West End.

    Although the Greater London area encompasses more than 600 square miles, getting around town is relatively easy. Whether you’re visiting St. Paul’s Cathedral in The City or catching a concert at the O2 Arena in Greenwich, the Tube’s trains are convenient and easy to navigate. The city’s iconic black taxi cabs are equally identifiable and convenient, and visitor shuttles and tour buses help you get to outlying areas like Stonehenge and Southampton cruise terminals. You could spend weeks exploring London and its environs, but if you only have a few days, here are four of our favorite sites:
</summary><browserTitle>First Class Flights to First Class Sights in London | IFlyFirstClass Travel Tips</browserTitle><created_date>4/4/2016 11:09:20 PM</created_date><seo><description>First Class Flights to First Class Sights in London. More interesting information and travel tips at IFlyFirstClass.</description><keywords>First Class Flights to London</keywords></seo><images><image><alias>97e2d9d791554956bc48110be6dda132.png</alias><content_id>15</content_id><title>Cheapest First Class Flight To London Today</title><queue>0</queue></image></images></item><item><travel_tips_id>16</travel_tips_id><title>Create First Class Memories in the City of Light</title><alias>deals-on-first-class-flights-to-paris-city</alias><summary>Often seen as the heart of Western culture, food, drink, fashion, romance and art, Paris is a thriving modern city. This City of Light is home to some of the most iconic landmarks, including the Eiffel Tower, the Arch of Triumph, Notre-Dame de Paris, the Louvre and Versailles. Its districts, or arrondissements, are distinctive and delightful, from the 1st Arrondissement’s Tuillerie Gardens and Palais Royal to the 8th Arrondissement’s high-end hotels, Champs-Élysées boutiques and Place de la Concorde.

    Understandably, Paris is one of the top international destinations in the world, attracting 22.4 million visitors each year. This popularity ensures that deals on business class flights to Paris are abundant. Paris museums and landmarks welcomed more than 70 million visits last year, with Notre Dame receiving 14 million and the Louvre taking in more than 9 million. While those numbers may seem daunting, Paris is so filled with enchanting attractions and activities that there are always plenty of comfortable, satisfying ways to spend your time. If you can’t travel to the city during the off or shoulder seasons, enjoy some of Paris’ slightly less crowded sites. We’ve compiled a list of four of our favorite Paris attractions that are popular and interesting but generally accessible, even at the peak of travel season.</summary><browserTitle>Create First Class Memories in the City of Light | IFlyFirstClass Travel Tips </browserTitle><created_date>4/4/2016 11:43:29 PM</created_date><seo><description>Create First Class Memories in the City of Light. More interesting information and travel tips at IFlyFirstClass.</description><keywords>Deals on first class flights to Paris</keywords></seo><images><image><alias>c269b0b100924a79bf83be7ac7e9d26e.png</alias><content_id>16</content_id><title>Cheapest Business Class To Paris Today</title><queue>0</queue></image></images></item><item><travel_tips_id>17</travel_tips_id><title> Taipei Abounds in First Class Pleasures</title><alias>increadably-cheap-business-class-fligh-to-taipei</alias><summary>Taipei is the perfect place to immerse yourself in Taiwan’s Chinese culture. Its restaurants serve delectable and affordable Chinese dishes, it historic temples are fascinating and its night markets will keep you entertained all night long.

    The city is the capital of Taiwan, officially the Republic of china, and it’s the educational and cultural center of the country too. Taipei is known for its high-tech industries, textile and apparel enterprises and electronic components. With these booming business sectors, business travel to the global city is abundant. For savvy traveler, that abundance also means that there are often excellent deals on business class flights to the city.

    There are host of landmarks and attractions you should experience while you’re in Taipei, including the observation deck at the 1,667-foot-tall skyscraper Taipei 101. The Sun Yat-sen Memorial Hall is a lively place to learn about Taiwan’s history before Chiang Kai-shek and enjoy a concert. You can browse contemporary art at the Taipei Fine Arts Museum, admire the wildlife at the Taipei Zoo and discover Spanish colonial history in Formosa at Fort San Domingo. Here are a few other sites we enjoy in Taipei:
</summary><browserTitle> Taipei Abounds in First Class Pleasures | IFlyFirstClass Travel Tips</browserTitle><created_date>4/5/2016 12:21:48 AM</created_date><seo><description> Taipei Abounds in First Class Pleasures. More interesting information and travel tips at IFlyFirstClass.</description><keywords>Cheap Business Class Fligh to Taipei</keywords></seo><images><image><alias>d965f7b206614f1592434c534dc5d70d.png</alias><content_id>17</content_id><title>Increadably Cheap Business Class Fligh to Taipei</title><queue>0</queue></image></images></item><item><travel_tips_id>18</travel_tips_id><title>Technology and Tradition Coexist in First Class Seoul</title><alias>traveling-to-seoul-first-class</alias><summary>The capital of South Korea and one of the world’s largest metropolitan areas, Seoul is glitzy, cosmopolitan and bustling. It also has a deeply traditional side, having served as the nation’s capital for more than 700 years. A first class flight to Seoul leads you to a delightful city that mixes the modern with the traditional beautifully, from high-tech corridors to ancient markets and royal burial grounds.

    You can see traditional wooden Korean homes in the city’s Bukchon Hanok Village, find traditional clothing in Insadong and visit an authentic Confucian royal shrine at Jongmyo. In the same day, you can play at the massive Everland theme park, find entertainment on the Some Sevit Floating Islands or buy high-tech gadgets and appliances in the Yongsan Electronics Market area. You can see both the traditional and modern districts of the city from the 60th sky deck of 63 Building or from the observation decks of N Seoul Tower.

    Whether you’re in town for business or pleasure, you can easily get around to all of Seoul’s amazing attractions using its large subway system. Known for its cleanliness and easy use, Seoul’s subway system is regarded as one of the world’s best.</summary><browserTitle>Technology and Tradition Coexist in First Class Seoul | IFlyFirstClass Travel Tips</browserTitle><created_date>4/7/2016 4:16:30 PM</created_date><seo><description>Technology and Tradition Coexist in First Class Seoul. More interesting information and travel tips at IFlyFirstClass.</description><keywords>First Class Seoul</keywords></seo><images><image><alias>f39fe4c27a8145e2bfcd6c2a5285d568.png</alias><content_id>18</content_id><title>Get the Cheapest First Class To Seoul Today</title><queue>0</queue></image></images></item><item><travel_tips_id>19</travel_tips_id><title>Auckland Offers First Class Views, Experiences</title><alias>auckland-offers-first-class-flight</alias><summary>Beautifully located on New Zealand&#39;s North Island, Auckland is the country&#39;s largest city. As your business class flight to Auckland approaches the airport, you&#39;ll see that Auckland is a harbor town. On its northeastern border is Waitemata Harbour on Hauraki Gulf, and on its southwestern border is Manukau Harbour on the Tasman Sea. This aptly named City of Sails is cosmopolitan yet down-to-earth. You&#39;ll find friendly people who treasure the country&#39;s Māori heritage and its unique and magnificent location.

    The best way to experience Auckland is to get out and explore the city and its surrounding countryside. Its stunning mountains, captivating beaches and peaceful hillsides make for an unforgettable experience. Visits to Auckland Domain, Mt. Eden, Auckland Harbour Bridge, Rangitoto Island and Aotea Square are must-see sites while you’re in town.

    If you have time to explore outlying areas, there are several memorable locales. The area’s volcanic remnants account for many of the most exciting sites. Extinct lava tubes form a network of underground caves and rivers you can explore a couple of hours outside the city at Waipu Caves and Waitomo Caves. You can rappel down the caves and “blackwater” raft along their subterranean rivers while enjoying the light emitted by millions of glowworms.

    Overall, Auckland is an exciting and welcoming city that’s perfect for a business or pleasure trip to the heart of the South Pacific.</summary><browserTitle>Auckland Offers First Class Views, Experiences | IFlyFirstClass Travel Tips</browserTitle><created_date>4/15/2016 7:44:45 PM</created_date><seo><description>Auckland Offers First Class Views, Experiences. More interesting information and travel tips at IFlyFirstClass.</description><keywords>Auckland Offers First Class</keywords></seo><images><image><alias>547f60e57e6e483e8c5c079236cf155a.png</alias><content_id>19</content_id><title>Buy First Class Seats to Auckland and  Experiences</title><queue>0</queue></image></images></item><item><travel_tips_id>20</travel_tips_id><title>Take a First Class Flight Through World History in Cairo</title><alias>get-the-first-class-flight-to-cairo-today</alias><summary>Located on the Nile River, bustling Cairo is the capital of Egypt. This immense city of 10 million people is a modern haven for business and culture. In spite of its cosmopolitan luxuries, Cairo retains its sense of heritage and history. It has some of Africa’s oldest settled regions, including Coptic Cairo and Islamic Cairo, and it’s near the magnificent pyramids of Egypt.

    There’s so much to explore in Cairo that you could easily spend a few weeks taking in all of the sights. If your business class flight to Cairo is taking you there for business, though, you will need to fit sightseeing in between meetings or conferences. While we list some of our favorite sites to visit in town, keep in mind that there is so much more to Cairo than what we’ve listed here. Take a few hours to explore the Egyptian Museum, where you’ll view 5,000 years of history. Shop at the Khan el-Khalili bazaar, then relax with a stroll through Al-Azhar Park. Visit Tahrir Square to see the site of the recent Arab Spring demonstrations, marvel at the ancient city gates of Bab Zuweila and enjoy a late-night snack in one of the many night-owl cafes. </summary><browserTitle>Take a First Class Flight Through World History in Cairo | IFlyFirstClass Travel Tips</browserTitle><created_date>4/17/2016 7:57:37 AM</created_date><seo><description>Take a First Class Flight Through World History in Cairo. More interesting information and travel tips at IFlyFirstClass.</description><keywords>Take a First Class Flight Through World History in Cairo</keywords></seo><images><image><alias>870548713c9b4c7a831ae6a89cc3f5da.png</alias><content_id>20</content_id><title>Take a First Class Flight Through World History in Cairo</title><queue>0</queue></image></images></item><item><travel_tips_id>21</travel_tips_id><title>First Class Sites Await in Colorful Moscow</title><alias>fly-with-first-class-seats-to-colorful-moscow</alias><summary>The capital city of Moscow has a long and fascinating history. Founded in 1147, the city has been a European center of culture, art, architecture, dance, literature, politics and business for centuries, and it remains so today. Some North Americans may only know the city for its role in the Russian revolution and Soviet-era military displays. In truth, Moscow has nine centuries of history wrapped up in its many sites, and you can explore them all with a last minute business class flight to Moscow.

    In addition to some of Moscow’s famous sites discussed on our site, we suggest you explore the city in other ways too. While you&#39;re in town, try a few Georgian and Russian dishes. There are several cafes featuring Georgian favorites such as the Sulguni-cheese-stuffed bread khachapuri and Russian delights such as pelmeni dumplings, syrniki fried cheese cakes and crepe-like blini. If you can find the time, you should also catch an opera or ballet at the Bolshoi Theatre and revel in the beautiful Russian art at the Tretyakov.

    Moscow is a large, vibrant city, and it boasts many world-class attractions and landmarks. Take the time to visit some of the city’s lesser-known sites so you can experience the true flavor of the city.</summary><browserTitle>First Class Sites Await in Colorful Moscow | IFlyFirstClass Travel Tips</browserTitle><created_date>4/17/2016 12:03:37 PM</created_date><seo><description>First Class Sites Await in Colorful Moscow. More interesting information and travel tips at IFlyFirstClass.</description><keywords>First Class Sites Await in Colorful Moscow</keywords></seo><images><image><alias>6670d60a72c14af7b1f582cd306b316c.png</alias><content_id>21</content_id><title>Cheapest First Class Sites Await in Colorful Moscow</title><queue>0</queue></image></images></item><item><travel_tips_id>22</travel_tips_id><title> Snag a Last Minute Flight to Berlin to See the Latest Attractions</title><alias>get-last-minute-flight-to-berlin-to-see-attractions</alias><summary>The atmosphere in Berlin buzzes with an inviting energy. Business leaders, artists, students and scientists give this city its eclectic, dynamic ambiance. This diverse populace also makes Berlin one of the most compelling European cities to visit.

    One of the best ways to get a feel for Berlin after your business class flight lands is to take a cruise along the Spree River. You’ll pass by many scenic spots, including the Märkischer Platz, Berlin Cathedral and beautiful Museum Island.

    This lively city is the capital of Germany and home to 3.5 million people. It boasts incredibly successful corporations, plentiful recreation and a thriving cultural scene. Its lively verve, however, doesn’t try to mask the city’s troubled past. Since German reunification in 1990, dozens of landmarks and attractions have opened to honor, commemorate and understand some of Germany’s most difficult realities. Some of these unforgettable memorials and attractions are the Memorial to the Murdered Jews of Europe, remnants of the Berlin Wall and Checkpoint Charlie, the Stasi Museum and the Jewish Museum. You can even tour the remnants of the concentration camp at Sachsenhausen.</summary><browserTitle> Snag a Last Minute Flight to Berlin | IFlyFirstClass Travel Tips</browserTitle><created_date>4/20/2016 2:05:13 PM</created_date><seo><description>Snag a Last Minute Flight to Berlin to See the Latest Attractions. More interesting information and travel tips at IFlyFirstClass.</description><keywords>Last Minute Flight to Berlin </keywords></seo><images><image><alias>4fef26572ade4ad28d2a0856d559a405.png</alias><content_id>22</content_id><title>Snag a Last Minute Flight to Berlin to See the Latest Attractions</title><queue>0</queue></image></images></item><item><travel_tips_id>23</travel_tips_id><title>From Palaces to Parks, Madrid Beckons Business Class Flights</title><alias>palace-parks-madrid-beckons-business-class-flights</alias><summary>Located in the central southern region of Spain, Madrid is at the heart of the country’s cultural, artistic and political scenes. It is the capital of Spain, and with 3.2 million residents, it is the European Union’s third largest metropolis. The beautiful Manzanares River runs through the city, bordered by expansive parks that provide a welcome retreat from Madrid’s bustling streets.

    That river is also the source of the city itself, luring groups of people to the area since prehistoric times. Paleolithic artifacts, Neolithic ceramics and remnants of Roman villas have all been discovered along the banks of the river. Modern-day Madrid, however, arose from 9th-century Moorish settlements. This long, treasured history gives visitors plenty to explore while in town.

    Many travelers head straight to the fabulous Plaza de Cibeles as soon as their business class flights land. The plaza is a great place to soak in the warm, welcoming ambiance of Madrid. It is also home to one of the most iconic historic sites in town, Cybele Palace, once known as the Palace of Communications. If you truly want to immerse yourself in Madrilenian culture, though, catch a Real Madrid soccer match. The team is beloved by locals and renowned for its “fútbol” prowess.
</summary><browserTitle>From Palaces to Parks, Madrid Beckons Business Class Flights | IFlyFirstClass Travel Tips</browserTitle><created_date>4/25/2016 11:29:26 AM</created_date><seo><description>From Palaces to Parks, Madrid Beckons Business Class Flights. More interesting information and travel tips at IFlyFirstClass.</description><keywords>Madrid Beckons Business Class Flights</keywords></seo><images><image><alias>59c5a09877d740898c62b6ed70d87adf.png</alias><content_id>23</content_id><title>The most and the cheapest business class flight to Madrid</title><queue>0</queue></image></images></item><item><travel_tips_id>24</travel_tips_id><title>Cape Town Thrills Are Just a Last Minute Flight Deal Away</title><alias>cape-town-thrills-last-minute-flight-deal-away</alias><summary>Exhilarating marine and land features like Cape Point, Table Mountain and Hout Bay make Cape Town an inspiring place to visit. If you love a physically active holiday, few cities offer more exciting thrills. Here, you can dive with great white sharks, swim with penguins and catch a Mount Kilimanjaro trekking tour. The city is so compelling that the New York Times named it the best place to visit in the world.

    If you’re traveling to Cape Town for business or pleasure, your business class flight will most likely land at Cape Town International Airport. The airport is just 12 miles east of the city center, and it offers all of the services and ground transportation options you’d expect at a major international airport.

    While you’re in Cape Town, take time to experience some of the pleasures that make it unique. While dining, try a few traditional dishes inspired by the country’s blend of Dutch, African and Far East residents. You can’t go wrong with some shisa nyama barbeque, biltong cured meat or the delectable sausage of a Boerewors Roll. If you have a few hours, enjoy the local sport scene. Head to Cape Town Stadium to catch an Ajax Cape Town soccer game. Go to DHL Newlands rugby stadium to see an international match featuring the Springboks. At either stadium, you’ll enjoy one a beloved national pastime and experience Cape Town like a local.</summary><browserTitle>Cape Town Thrills Are Just a Last Minute Flight | IFlyFirstClass Travel Tips</browserTitle><created_date>4/26/2016 12:28:17 PM</created_date><seo><description>Cape Town Thrills Are Just a Last Minute Flight Deal Away. More interesting information and travel tips at IFlyFirstClass.</description><keywords>Last Minute Flight Deal Away</keywords></seo><images><image><alias>e26539509a7f40fcb5fc99a38efdcc5b.png</alias><content_id>24</content_id><title>Booking the Cheapest Business Class Fligth To Cape Town</title><queue>0</queue></image></images></item><item><travel_tips_id>25</travel_tips_id><title>Explore the Green City with Last Minute Flight Deals</title><alias>explore-frankfurt-with-last-minute-flight-deals</alias><summary>Known as a financial, commercial and cultural hub of Germany, Frankfurt is wonderfully modern. It’s home to excellent shopping districts, world-famous museums and numerous high-rise towers. It also features a vast network of inviting parks. The city maintains such strict ecological building standards that it is often referred to as Europe’s Green City.

    Your last minute business class flight to Frankfurt will likely land at Frankfurt Airport, Germany’s busiest domestic and international travel airport. The airport offers a short, 12-minute train ride to Frankfurt, and it is Lufthansa’s main hub.

    There are plenty of things to do while you’re in town. Enjoy spectacular city views from Main Tower&#39;s observation deck. Visit the Holocaust Memorial. Enjoy a concert at the Old Opera Hall. Shop along the legendary Zeil, then drop into one of the city’s many apple wine pubs for a little refreshment.

    Frankfurt is considered one of Europe’s top food destinations, so you’ll have plenty of dining options while in town. If you enjoy sausage, be sure to try the city market’s beloved sausage sandwiches. Sample Handkäse mit Musik quark cheese bites or Bethmännchen cookies for a quick snack. For lunch or dinner, try beef schnitzel with Frankfurt&#39;s favorite sour cream-based Grüne Sosse, or green sauce.</summary><browserTitle>Explore the Green City with Last Minute Flight Deals | IFlyFirstClass Travel Tips</browserTitle><created_date>4/28/2016 11:39:25 AM</created_date><seo><description>Explore the Green City with Last Minute Flight Deals. More interesting information and travel tips at IFlyFirstClass.</description><keywords>Last Minute Flight Deals to Frankfurt</keywords></seo><images><image><alias>6cd09f94822e4151b732a2f7ce31025f.png</alias><content_id>25</content_id><title>Best  business class deals to Frankfurt</title><queue>0</queue></image></images></item><item><travel_tips_id>26</travel_tips_id><title>Shanghai Business Class Flights Whisk You Away to a Thriving Cultural Center</title><alias>shanghai-business-class-flights-whisk</alias><summary>For many years, Shanghai was a booming trade and financial center linking the Far East to the West. It shows this East-West influence in many ways. The legendary Bund is the city&#39;s historic European-styled waterfront. It was once home to international banks and grand diplomatic embassies. Today, it&#39;s stately architecture is a stand-out for the area. Across the Huangpu River from The Bund is the thoroughly modern Pudong District. There, the city’s thriving financial, corporate and retail centers offer hours of entertainment.

    With a history dating back to the 5th-century B.C.E., Shanghai is a fascinating mix of history, cultures and cuisine. It is also the most heavily populated city in China. As a result of this immense population, you can find every food, commodity and attraction imaginable.

    There are also many convenient transportation options here. The city’s two international airports, Shanghai Pudong and Shanghai Hongqiao, are convenient. Your business class flight likely landed at Shanghai Pudong International Airport though. That’s a good thing because Pudong gives you access to the world’s fastest train, the Maglev. The super-modern train can deliver you to the city center in mere minutes.

    This bustling metropolis also offers excellent restaurants and dining options. While you’re in town, though, be sure to sample local dishes such as xialongbao soup dumplings. Caramel strawberry skewers, drunken crab, tongzi ji chicken and grilled oysters are also local favorites.

    The shopping in Shanghai is stellar, especially along Nanjing Road and Xintiandi. You can also visit popular street markets such as Dongtai Road Antique Market and South Bund Fabric Market.</summary><browserTitle>Shanghai Business Class Flights Whisk You Away | IFlyFirstClass Travel Tips</browserTitle><created_date>5/3/2016 12:49:00 PM</created_date><seo><description>Shanghai Business Class Flights Whisk You Away to a Thriving Cultural Center. More interesting information and travel tips at IFlyFirstClass.</description><keywords>Shanghai Business Class Flights </keywords></seo><images><image><alias>5cb4d38fa3274d9ca6384be2a416b669.png</alias><content_id>26</content_id><title>Best  business class deals to Shanghai</title><queue>0</queue></image></images></item><item><travel_tips_id>27</travel_tips_id><title>Munich is a Treat with Last Minute Flight Deals</title><alias>fly-to-munich-with-last-minute-flight-deals</alias><summary>Nearly six million people make their homes in the Munich area, drawn to the city’s abundant charm. It is a thriving center of industry, art, finance, technology and Bavarian culture. Its rousing Oktoberfest activities are legendary, and its Christmas markets date back to 1642. There are dozens of museums in Munich. These institutions range from hands-on science museums to Bavarian history museums.

    Munich is also known for its stellar urban parks and gardens. Englischer Garden is one of the largest parks in Europe. Its verdant lawns and attractions are perfect places to decompress after a last minute flight. You’ll find Japanese tea gardens, peaceful streams, artificial surf spots and sunbathing gardens.

    While you’re in Munich, you must try some of the celebrated Bavarian dishes. Warm, doughy pretzels and steins of beer are just the beginning of your culinary adventure. Weisswurst is the local favorite for sausage, but Bratwurst and Knockwurst have their fans here too. Continuing the meaty theme, you can also sample Warmer Leberkäs. It’s a delectable slice of a beef-and-bacon meatloaf that’s perfect for eating while walking around town. Finish your meals or begin your day with classic Bavarian pastries. Fruit strudels and moist kuchen are easily found at nearly every local bakery.</summary><browserTitle>Munich is a Treat with Last Minute Flight Deals | IFlyFirstClass Travel Tips</browserTitle><created_date>5/7/2016 9:44:47 AM</created_date><seo><description>Munich is a Treat with Last Minute Flight Deals. More interesting information and travel tips at IFlyFirstClass.</description><keywords>Munich is a Treat with Last Minute Flight Deals</keywords></seo><images><image><alias>8501460ade1f411c8ec29150e9d078fd.png</alias><content_id>27</content_id><title>Best  business class deals to Munich</title><queue>0</queue></image></images></item><item><travel_tips_id>28</travel_tips_id><title> Adventures in Perth are Better with Business Class Deals</title><alias>perth-adventuresr-with-business-class-deals</alias><summary>On Australia’s far western coastline, Perth is a jewel on the Indian Ocean and Swan River. Its bustling central business district hums with activity along the riverfront and its port thrives. More than two million people live in Perth, making it Australia’s fourth largest city.

    Many of those residents think Perth’s locale is just about perfect. It’s close to thrilling Indian Ocean activities and wildlife on the west. The picturesque Swan River runs through the town. Acclaimed Swan Valley wineries lie just to the east, offering food, drink, scenery and activities. To top it off, the weather is comfortable for most of the year so you can enjoy all of these features.

    The Perth Cultural Centre is the place to go for the city’s art, music and theatrical scenes. There, you’ll find the Western Australian Museum and the glamorous State Theatre. You’ll also find dozens of festivals and exciting night markets.
</summary><browserTitle> Adventures in Perth are Better with Business Class | IFlyFirstClass Travel Tips</browserTitle><created_date>5/8/2016 9:33:59 AM</created_date><seo><description>Adventures in Perth are Better with Business Class Deals. More interesting information and travel tips at IFlyFirstClass.</description><keywords>Perth are Better with Business Class Deals</keywords></seo><images><image><alias>82221d48bd3e4345b0cc6f265763d35d.png</alias><content_id>28</content_id><title>Best  business class deals to Perth</title><queue>0</queue></image></images></item><item><travel_tips_id>29</travel_tips_id><title>Take Last Minute Business Class Flights to Tokyo to Shop, Hike</title><alias>shop-for-last-minute-business-class-flights-to-tokyo</alias><summary>Bustling and modern, historic and scenic, Tokyo is awash in interesting sites. The largest city in Japan, Tokyo is also part of the biggest metropolitan area in the world. With 37 million residents and nearly 20 million visitors annually, Tokyo offers many attractions. There are island entertainment districts, legendary shopping centers and dozens of skyscrapers. There are countless parks, sports arenas, casinos and zoos appealing to people of all ages. Even Disney operates a two-theme-park resort to appeal to the region’s residents and visitors.

    If you prefer to explore the history and tradition of Japanese culture, you have many options. Tokyo is home to one of the world’s largest art museums with Tokyo National Museum. Other museums showcase art, ancient culture, architecture, swords and crafts. Many shrines and temples throughout the city also offer a glimpse into local religion and tradition.

    Japan is rich in cultural trends that influence the world, and Tokyo is the epicenter. From J-pop’s trendy “idol” groups to wildly popular anime serials, you can find them all in Tokyo. Interested in youth fashion? The “cute” culture, or “kawaii,” has taken root here. It’s seen in teen clothing trends like sweet Lolita and visual kei and in dozens of other local products. Whether you prefer kawaii clothing or designer duds, shopping is big in Tokyo. Be sure to bring along an extra suitcase for your business class flight home. You’ll need that extra space to take home all of your local “finds.”</summary><browserTitle>Take Last Minute Business Class Flights to Tokyo | IFlyFirstClass Travel Tips</browserTitle><created_date>5/8/2016 9:49:21 AM</created_date><seo><description>Take Last Minute Business Class Flights to Tokyo to Shop, Hike. More interesting information and travel tips at IFlyFirstClass.</description><keywords>Take Last Minute Business Class Flights to Tokyo </keywords></seo><images><image><alias>bbb7c34f447e4904bd2f2cc94e789a8c.png</alias><content_id>29</content_id><title>Best  Last minute business class tickets to Tokyo</title><queue>0</queue></image></images></item><item><travel_tips_id>30</travel_tips_id><title> Business Class to Brisbane Leads to Adventure</title><alias>business-class-tickets-to-brisbane-to-adventure</alias><summary>Nestled between the Great Dividing Range and Moreton Bay, Brisbane is scenic and adventure-filled. The largest city in Queensland, Brisbane is also historic and chic. The city is known for its waterfront skyscrapers, vibrant gardens and unique architecture.

    More than three million people live in the greater Brisbane area, making it Australia’s third biggest city. Even with this large population, the city’s plentiful green spaces and waterways keep it natural. Brisbane’s ample water features actually provide many of its most enjoyable activities. Take a sunset cruises along the Brisbane River for a beautiful look at the illuminated skyline. Sail Moreton Bay. Feed the dolphins, and ride sand toboggans on Moreton Island. Head out to the open Pacific Ocean to see migrating whales.

    Getting around town to see some of Brisbane’s most delightful sites is relatively easy, beginning at the airport. Brisbane Airport is a major hub for Virgin Australia, Qantas and Jetstar, and it serves 23 other airlines. This variety means it’s often easy to find deals on business class flights to Brisbane. It’s also convenient to access transportation from the airport to the city center. A train can deliver you from the international terminal to Brisbane’s CBD in 24 minutes. Once in town, you can handily avoid learning to drive on the left side of the road. The city’s 10 commuter train lines with 139 stations are the ultimate in convenience. The local CityCat Ferry offers equally simple transport across waterways. Whatever you want to see or experience in Brisbane, local public transit serves you well.
</summary><browserTitle> Business Class to Brisbane Leads to Adventure | IFlyFirstClass Travel Tips</browserTitle><created_date>5/10/2016 1:45:08 AM</created_date><seo><description> Business Class to Brisbane Leads to Adventure. More interesting information and travel tips at IFlyFirstClass.</description><keywords>Business Class to Brisbane Leads to Adventure</keywords></seo><images><image><alias>aec4918fc05e4844b0827636b99b111c.png</alias><content_id>30</content_id><title>Best  business class deals to Brisbane</title><queue>0</queue></image></images></item><item><travel_tips_id>31</travel_tips_id><title>Opulent palaces, gleaming temples and bronzed Buddhas make trips to Bangkok special. Call today to book cheap business class tickets.</title><alias>call-today-to-book-cheap-business-class-tickets-to-bangkok</alias><summary>Bangkok is immense in every way. Its land covers 605 square miles on the Chao Phraya River delta. It’s home to 8 million people, with 14 million people living in the entire metro area. It has been named the most visited city in the world in recent years. “Travel + Leisure” magazine calls it the “World’s Best City.”

    Along with this sizable population comes abundant services. You have two international airports to choose from when booking your cheap business class tickets. Suvarnabhumi Airport is the main international airport, handling 53 million passengers a year. An airport rail link train connects travelers to the city. Don Mueang Airport is the airport to use for low-cost airlines.

    If you love Thai restaurants in your hometown, Bangkok’s street food will delight your tastebuds. Street vendors are everywhere, so you won’t have to walk far to find one. Stir fries with fried egg on top, grilled pork on skewers and sweet potato balls are top choices. Mango sticky rice, pad thai and pad si ew are also local favorites. For sweet treats, you have dozens of choices. Check out the crepes, fried banana pancakes and chocolate-filled mini waffles. They’re sure to give you a little sugar rush so you can head out and explore the city.</summary><browserTitle>Opulent palaces, gleaming temples and bronzed Buddhas | IFlyFirstClass Travel Tips</browserTitle><created_date>5/11/2016 12:48:30 PM</created_date><seo><description>Opulent palaces, gleaming temples and bronzed Buddhas make trips to Bangkok special. Call today to book cheap business class tickets. More interesting information and travel tips at IFlyFirstClass.</description><keywords> to book cheap business class tickets.</keywords></seo><images><image><alias>1e8194bdc2b44e3c9cc57339eb5333a2.png</alias><content_id>31</content_id><title>Best  business class deals to Bangkok</title><queue>0</queue></image></images></item><item><travel_tips_id>32</travel_tips_id><title>A Royal Copenhagen Trip Begins with Business Class Seats</title><alias>royal-copenhagen-trip-with-business-class-seats</alias><summary>Denmark is famously the happiest country on earth. Gorgeous cities like Copenhagen are part of the reason for this intense satisfaction. The lively capital city is actually located on the islands of Zealand and Amager and encompasses several other islets. The surrounding waterways and bridges create many scenic settings. Distinct and often-colorful architecture only enhances the picture-postcard look of Copenhagen.

    The vibrant city isn’t all about surface beauty though. Officials and planners have worked diligently to ensure the city is easily navigated and eminently livable. You can enjoy the city&#39;s ample transit as soon as your business class flight lands at Copenhagen Airport. The town’s Metro whisks you from the airport to the city center in just 15 minutes. There are also plenty of regional trains, buses and S-trains to help you get around the city. There is even a regular ferry taking locals and visitors across the ocean to Oslo.

    To truly experience Copenhagen, though, you need to try some of the local foods. Local favorites include Danish hotdogs, smørrebrød open-faced sandwiches and local beer. If you have a sweet tooth, sample Flødeboller cream puffs and Karamelrand custard with caramel. These local dishes are sure to sustain you while you explore all of the city&#39;s many delightful attractions.
</summary><browserTitle>A Royal Copenhagen Trip Begins with Business Class Seats | IFlyFirstClass Travel Tips</browserTitle><created_date>5/11/2016 1:30:24 PM</created_date><seo><description>A Royal Copenhagen Trip Begins with Business Class Seats. More interesting information and travel tips at IFlyFirstClass.</description><keywords>Trip Begins with Business Class Seats</keywords></seo><images><image><alias>59d7e633e38c4d7e91b0d0d54c63b368.png</alias><content_id>32</content_id><title>Best  business class deals to Copenhagen</title><queue>0</queue></image></images></item><item><travel_tips_id>33</travel_tips_id><title> Scenic and Glitzy: Hong Kong and Business Class Flights</title><alias>best-business-class-deals-to-hong-kong</alias><summary>With 7.2 million residents, Hong Kong is one of the most densely populated cities in the world. It is known for its vital financial centers, beautiful harbor and numerous skyscrapers. Business is booming in Hong Kong, and it shows in the glamorous buildings and cosmopolitan ambiance.

    There’s a deeply held cultural and historic side to Hong Kong, too, though. Many of the city’s most treasured sites have historic or religious significance. Here, you’ll find many temples and monasteries. You’ll discover world-class museums dedicated to preserving and illuminating the city’s heritage. You’ll see historic clock towers and popular markets filled with local crafts and art.

    Hong Kong is also a food lover’s paradise, from fast, local eateries to fine dining. While in town, visitors enjoy the puddings and scrambled eggs at Australian Dairy Company. It’s fast, relatively inexpensive and a local landmark. Other local favorites include milk tea, grilled pork cheek, beef brisket noodle and dim sum.

    Some of these foods are also available at Hong Kong International Airport, your business class flight’s destination. Getting from the airport on Chek Lap Kok island to the central Kowloon area is relatively easy. You can ferry over to Kowloon or take the quick, high-speed rail train. Once in Hong Kong’s central district, you can continue your food and cultural exploration.</summary><browserTitle> Scenic and Glitzy: Hong Kong and Business Class Flights  | IFlyFirstClass Travel Tips</browserTitle><created_date>5/16/2016 10:41:13 PM</created_date><seo><description> Scenic and Glitzy: Hong Kong and Business Class Flights. More interesting information and travel tips at IFlyFirstClass.</description><keywords>Best  business class deals to Hong Kong</keywords></seo><images><image><alias>50c01e47c3d64495a3e65cb0ec7b4aae.png</alias><content_id>33</content_id><title>Best  business class deals to Hong Kong</title><queue>0</queue></image></images></item><item><travel_tips_id>34</travel_tips_id><title>Book First Class Tickets for the Ultimate Trip to New York</title><alias>get-first-class-tickets-for-trip-to-new-york</alias><summary>The nation’s most populous city, New York has a vibe and a character you won’t find anywhere else in the world. It is home to the world’s leading businesses, stock markets, theaters, media outlets, museums and fashion houses. It boasts beloved ethnic and character-filled neighborhoods from Little Italy to artistic Greenwich Village. It offers some of the best and most diverse culinary options, from trendy bistros to five-star restaurants. With all that the city contains, it’s no wonder it’s often referred to as the City that Never Sleeps or the Big Apple.

    There are dozens of must-see attractions and landmarks in the city and its boroughs. With this in mind, budget your time carefully when you’re booking your business class tickets to New York. First-time visitors enjoy hitting all of the typical tourist hot-spots, including Times Square, Rockefeller Center and Statue of Liberty. Experienced New York travelers or those with more than a few days in town should explore the city more extensively. Visit the places locals go to fully experience the city. Spend a day at The Met or the American Museum of Natural History. Take an afternoon to laze or play in Central Park or stroll through High-Line Park. Shop for snacks in a neighborhood bodega. Take in a game at Yankee Stadium or a concert at Madison Square Garden. There’s no end to the enjoyment you can find if you keep an open mind.</summary><browserTitle>Book First Class Tickets for the Ultimate Trip | IFlyFirstClass Travel Tips</browserTitle><created_date>8/4/2016 11:49:38 AM</created_date><seo><description>Book First Class Tickets for the Ultimate Trip to New York. More interesting information and travel tips at IFlyFirstClass.</description><keywords>Best First class deals to  New York</keywords></seo><images><image><alias>bb66b26a5d094410a756967cb128eaf1.png</alias><content_id>34</content_id><title>Luxury  first class tickets to New York</title><queue>0</queue></image></images></item><item><travel_tips_id>35</travel_tips_id><title>Book Business Class Flight for the Unforgetable Trip to Rome </title><alias>search-for-business-class-flight-to-rome</alias><summary>Famously perched on seven hills, Rome bursts with historic and cosmopolitan delights. If you love art, fashion, religion, architecture, science or history, Rome is the place to be. The early Roman Empire is the origin of many Western civilizations and innovations. It is the birthplace of aqueducts and emperors, Western languages and highways. Visiting the bustling city is a chance to walk in the footsteps of famed popes, emperors, artists and architects.

    Your business class flight to Rome will likely land at Fiumicino Airport, about 10 miles from Rome’s city center. If you have time, spend your first day in the fishing village of Fiumicino. Fiumicino beaches are a favorite summer hangout for Roman locals, and it&#39;s close to historic Ostia Antica.

    Once in Rome’s city center, be prepared for a more hectic pace. Your biggest decision will be which of the hundreds of attractions to visit. Of course, the most popular tourist sites are Vatican City, the Roman Forum and the Colosseum. The Spanish Steps, Pantheon, Trevi Fountain and St. Peter’s Basilica are also beloved attractions. Dozens of major and minor basilicas offer up many of the world&#39;s most spectacular artwork. While in town, be sure to also visit some of the famed public squares where you can relax, mingle with locals and enjoy lunch at a cafe. There are so many other treasures to discover here that you’ll leave the city ready to book another first class ticket to Rome.</summary><browserTitle>Book Business Class Flight for the Unforgetable | IFlyFirstClass Travel Tips</browserTitle><created_date>8/8/2016 9:29:12 AM</created_date><seo><description>Book Business Class Flight for the Unforgetable Trip to Rome. More interesting information and travel tips at IFlyFirstClass.</description><keywords>Business Class Flight for the Unforgetable Trip to Rome</keywords></seo><images><image><alias>8708962ee11148f9b1c4ae98f64db70b.png</alias><content_id>35</content_id><title>Lowest price on business class flights to Rome</title><queue>0</queue></image></images></item><item><travel_tips_id>36</travel_tips_id><title>Relaxing after the long business class flight to Singapore</title><alias>book-your-deals-on-business-class-tickets-to-singapore-now</alias><summary>Perched at the southernmost tip of Malaysia’s mainland peninsula, Singapore is a tropical paradise. The city-state is known for its glamorous shops, world-class entertainment and booming financial markets. It’s also a melting pot of diverse Asian cultures that give this small country its big personality.

    Singapore is often considered one of the most expensive cities in the world. Luckily, there are many ways to enjoy the locale without straining your wallet. First, check for deals on business class flights so you can fly in physical and economic comfort. Next, check out some of Singapore’s many free and less expensive attractions. Browse through the colorful neighborhood of Kampong Glam, where you’ll find trendy fashion shops on colorful Haji Lane. Spend the day in the free Haw Par Villa theme park. There, you can lose yourself in the vibrant statues and tableaux depicting Chinese mythology. You can also spend a whole day in the historic and eclectic Tiong Bahru neighborhood. You’ll see beautiful old Art Deco architecture and enjoy hipster coffee houses and bakeries and superb street food.

    If economizing isn’t a concern, there are plenty of high-end establishments and activities to suit. Shop the extensive and acclaimed Orchard Road. Stay, play and dine in the upscale resort and entertainment centers. Golf at Singapore Island Country Club and enjoy a VIP seat at the night-time Singapore Grand Prix. Sip a $32,000 cocktail at Pangaea or dine at Waku Ghin; the sky’s the limit in Singapore.</summary><browserTitle>Relaxing after the long business class flight to Singapore | IFlyFirstClass Travel Tips</browserTitle><created_date>8/8/2016 9:54:25 AM</created_date><seo><description>Relaxing after the long business class flight to Singapore. More interesting information and travel tips at IFlyFirstClass.</description><keywords>Singapore business class flight </keywords></seo><images><image><alias>d0fcc0d164e74c5887d4da89fdf14b7a.png</alias><content_id>36</content_id><title>Book your tickets on business class to Singapore now.</title><queue>0</queue></image></images></item><item><travel_tips_id>37</travel_tips_id><title>Experiencing Australia Is Worth a Business Class Flight</title><alias>experiencing-australia-is-worth-a-business-class-flight</alias><summary>Australia is a sensational mix of beaches, rainforests, deserts, grasslands, wetlands and coral reefs. This massive island continent also boasts hundreds of breathtaking islands, perfect for a seaside holiday. With the 12th largest economy in the world, Australia is also an excellent location to pursue business interests.

    This Oceanic country is rich in thrilling, world-class cities. Sydney, on Australia’s east coast, is a bustling metropolis known for its exciting bridge, gorgeous Opera House, popular beaches and thriving industries. Melbourne is a cultural paradise, teeming with fashion, art, theater, dining and recreation venues. In the country&#39;s interior, you’ll find an enchanting outback filled with incredible natural wonders that are uniquely Australian. On the west coast, Perth is a robust city in its own right with dozens of cultural, entertainment, recreation and business options. To the north, Darwin offers beautiful beaches, access to amazing national parks, a busy port and convenient transport to Southeast Asia.

    Getting to this immense country is convenient with international airports operating in most of its large cities. On the nation’s east coast, you can book business class tickets to Sydney, Brisbane, the Gold Coast and Cairns. On the south coast, use Melbourne or Adelaide international airports. For Western Australia destinations, Perth is a good option, and Darwin is your northern airport option.

    Whatever destination you choose in Australia, be sure to schedule some time to experience some of the sites that you’ll only find in this picturesque country.
</summary><browserTitle>Experiencing Australia Is Worth a Business Class Flight | IFlyFirstClass Travel Tips</browserTitle><created_date>8/8/2016 11:05:21 AM</created_date><seo><description>Experiencing Australia Is Worth a Business Class Flight. More interesting information and travel tips at IFlyFirstClass.</description><keywords>Experiencing Australia Is Worth a Business Class Flight</keywords></seo><images><image><alias>483042158e304e1ba322d9de5723aeb7.png</alias><content_id>37</content_id><title>Experiencing Australia Is Worth a Business Class Flight</title><queue>0</queue></image></images></item><item><travel_tips_id>38</travel_tips_id><title>Find incredible last minute business class deals to France today</title><alias>find-incredible-business-class-deals-to-france-today</alias><summary>France is an international powerhouse, known for its many cultural and economic contributions to Western civilization. Whether you’re traveling first class to France for business or pleasure, there are many delightful towns waiting to be explored.

    Of course, Paris is the ultimate destination. In fact, the city’s 15 million visitors each year make Paris the fifth most popular destination in the world. While the city can get crowded during peak travel season, its treasures are well worth the wait. You can tour the Louvre, Eiffel Tower, Arc d’Triomphe, Notre Dame, Sacré-Cœur and Montmarte. You can shop along the glamorous Champs-Élysées, wander through the Latin Quarter and browse in countless museums and gardens.

    There’s more to France than Paris though. There are sun-soaked beaches and posh resorts on the Mediterranean. There are warm and picturesque wine regions on the southwest, and cooler, scenic locales along the Atlantic coast. To the south, the Pyrenees offer bountiful recreation and to the east, beautiful cities like Strasbourg and ranges like the Alps dominate.</summary><browserTitle>Find incredible last minute business class deals to France | IFlyFirstClass Travel Tips</browserTitle><created_date>8/10/2016 11:26:42 AM</created_date><seo><description>Find incredible last minute business class deals to France today. More interesting information and travel tips at IFlyFirstClass.</description><keywords>Find incredible business class deals to France today</keywords></seo><images><image><alias>63bb08afcf074e76a779dbc697ca1b81.png</alias><content_id>38</content_id><title>Cheap last minute business class deals to France today</title><queue>0</queue></image></images></item><item><travel_tips_id>39</travel_tips_id><title>Venice is the best of your first stops in Italy. With the best business class flight </title><alias>dream-and-get-business-class-flight-to-venice</alias><summary>Once its own republic governed by a powerful doge, Venice is now one of Italy’s most popular destinations. The city is actually made up of many islands connected by canals and bridges. Opulently built palaces line the city’s canals and provide a glimpse of its intriguing history. Cars aren’t allowed in most areas of the city, which only enhances Venice’s mystique and grandeur.

    This picturesque city overflows with historic, must-see landmarks. You could spend weeks just browsing through its museums. Some of the most popular museums include Gallerie dell’Accademia, the Peggy Guggenheim Collection and Museo Correr. You won’t find art only in Venice museums though. Its palaces, churches and civic buildings are also filled with masterpieces. If you love the works of Titian, Bellini and Donatello, you’ll treasure your time in Santa Maria Gloriosa dei Frari. You’ll find more masterpieces by Bellini, Bartolomeo Bon, Veronese and Alvise Vivarini at Saint Giovanni e Paolo.

    Nearly 20 million people visit this City of Bridges each year, so flights to nearby Marco Polo Airport are abundant. This bountiful number of flights to Marco Polo often means that you can snag good deals on business class flights to the city. You’ll want to spend ample time and money in elegant Venice, so saving money on luxury airfare is a necessary perk.</summary><browserTitle>Venice is the best of your first stops in Italy. | IFlyFirstClass Travel Tips</browserTitle><created_date>8/12/2016 12:09:00 PM</created_date><seo><description>Venice is the best of your first stops in Italy. With the best business class flight. More interesting information and travel tips at IFlyFirstClass.</description><keywords>Venice is the best of your first stops in Italy. With the best business class flight </keywords></seo><images><image><alias>5e208d8042764e81aa51d544ae3f9fbb.png</alias><content_id>39</content_id><title>Venice is the best of your first stops in Italy with  business class flight </title><queue>0</queue></image></images></item><item><travel_tips_id>40</travel_tips_id><title>Business Class to Japan Offers Unique Cultural Experience</title><alias>book-and-travel-to-japan-with-discounted-business-class-deals-today</alias><summary>Traveling to the exciting Land of the Rising Sun is a goal of many travelers, and it’s easy to understand why. The many islands of Japan offer up experiences to suit just about every interest. There are vast forests and mountains in the north islands. Chic cities on the main island keep travelers of all ages entertained. Tropical paradises in the south showcase unique cultures and fabulous beaches.

    Of course, the country is also known for its captivating history, culture and religion. Many of Japan’s Buddhist temples and Shinto shrines display all three elements, making them entrancing sites to tour. Traditional Japanese culture also abounds in the cities and the small, historic villages. Any place you travel in Japan, you’re likely to see a feature of traditional art, architecture, dance, theater, literature, music or military customs.

    Even today, Japan plays an important role in world culture, art, theater and fashion. Japan has contributed to popular cultural phenomena such as manga comic books and anime films and shows. It has created a whole music industry around J-Pop and “idol” groups. Cosplaying and fashion subcultures like Lolita and Kawaii have also made their mark on world trends. You can enjoy this art, music and fashion around the world, but Japan is the only authentic experience. The best place for exploring these trends is in Japan’s large cities like Tokyo, Osaka and Kawasaki.

    The tastes of Japan are similarly delightful and iconic. From world-class sushi and miso soups to playful maid, manga and cat cafes, eating in Japan is a joy.

    Whether you fly into Osaka or you book your business class tickets for Tokyo, a world of fascinating experiences are found in Japan.
</summary><browserTitle>Business Class to Japan Offers Unique Cultural Experience | IFlyFirstClass Travel Tips</browserTitle><created_date>8/18/2016 10:28:34 AM</created_date><seo><description>Business Class to Japan Offers Unique Cultural Experience. More interesting information and travel tips at IFlyFirstClass.</description><keywords>Book discounted business class deals today.

</keywords></seo><images><image><alias>c849a362abf14d19a994922d4874e015.png</alias><content_id>40</content_id><title>Business Class to Japan Offers Unique Cultural Experience</title><queue>0</queue></image></images></item><item><travel_tips_id>41</travel_tips_id><title>The Netherlands: First Class Flights and Sights</title><alias>booking-discounted-business-class-tickets-to-netherlands</alias><summary>Famously open-minded and forthright, the Netherlands is one of Europe’s most delightful countries. Its picturesque rivers, canals and waterfront are productive and scenic. They also provide countless opportunities for transportation and recreation.

    While you may think of giant wooden windmills and tulip fields when you think of the Netherlands, the country has so much more to explore. Its agricultural industry thrives and is one of the world’s biggest exporters. Several of its medieval towns remain carefully preserved and were lucky enough to escape the destruction of World War II. It is home to Europe’s largest port, the port of Rotterdam, and it’s the headquarters for Europol and five international courts.

    You could easily spend weeks exploring the country’s biggest cities: Amsterdam, Rotterdam or The Hague. To truly experience all of the Netherland’s cultures, history and attractions, though, you need to head to the outlying areas and smaller villages.

    The Netherlands shares borders with Belgium and Germany, and it’s just across the North Sea from England. This location gives travelers many destination options when booking discounted business class tickets to the region. While Amsterdam Airport Schiphol is the country’s major international airport, there are several smaller airports within the country. Travelers can also use airports near Brussels and Dusseldorf. If you plan to take a broader tour of Europe, you can also fly into London, ferry to Belgium and take a train to Netherlands’ larger cities.</summary><browserTitle>The Netherlands: First Class Flights and Sights | IFlyFirstClass Travel Tips</browserTitle><created_date>8/18/2016 10:58:18 AM</created_date><seo><description>The Netherlands: First Class Flights and Sights. More interesting information and travel tips at IFlyFirstClass.</description><keywords>Book your deals on business class seats today.
</keywords></seo><images><image><alias>369f4593f29e40e0b9cd2b2494596f3b.png</alias><content_id>41</content_id><title>Choosing the best business class tickets to  Netherlands </title><queue>0</queue></image></images></item><item><travel_tips_id>42</travel_tips_id><title>Business Class Flights to Russia Are the Ultimate Luxury</title><alias>getting-luxury-business-class-flights-to-russia</alias><summary>Gorgeous, vast Russia offers all the delights you could hope for in a travel destination. It has a long and intriguing history, spectacular and unique architecture and incredible cultural contributions. It is home to the immense Ural and Caucasus mountains, the volcanoes of Kamchatka Peninsula and the permafrost of Siberia. There are dozens of national parks and nature reserves and nearly 23,000 miles of coastline. With all of Russia’s natural and cultural abundance, there is always something to see or experience here.

    The best Russian itinerary mixes some of the country’s big, historic cities with some of its outlying villages and towns. If this is your first visit, Moscow and St. Petersburg should top your list. Leave time to explore other treasures, though, such as the historic city of Novgorod or ancient Suzdal and other Golden Ring towns. A ride along the TransSiberian Railway or a cruise along the Volga River will give you a chance to see many of Russia’s most beautiful landscapes and cities too.

    Traveling to Russia is convenient and easy. Although the country spans nearly 6.6 million square miles, there are enough international airports to put you within easy reach of your ultimate destination. Flights to St. Petersburg and Moscow are the most plentiful, so you’re most likely to find business class deals to Pulkovo, Domodedovo, Sheremetyevo or Vnukovo international airports.
</summary><browserTitle>Business Class Flights to Russia Are the Ultimate Luxury | IFlyFirstClass Travel Tips</browserTitle><created_date>8/20/2016 12:07:16 PM</created_date><seo><description>Business Class Flights to Russia Are the Ultimate Luxury. More interesting information and travel tips at IFlyFirstClass.</description><keywords>Business Class Flights to Russia </keywords></seo><images><image><alias>a52dcbba6b1d476f9eec547b41b329fc.png</alias><content_id>42</content_id><title>Business Class tickets to Russia</title><queue>0</queue></image></images></item><item><travel_tips_id>43</travel_tips_id><title> Luxuriate in Business Class Seats to Switzerland</title><alias>getting-the-best-in-business-class-flight-to-switzerland</alias><summary>Charming villages, glamorous cities and chic Alpine ski resorts make Switzerland a popular destination. Its hundreds of lakes and rivers merely add to the country’s tremendous appeal.

    Nestled between Italy, France, Austria, Lichtenstein and Germany, it would be easy for this small nation to lose its national character. It remains unique, however, using its cultural and language mixtures to create an internationally beloved European country. These influences also create one-of-a-kind Swiss destinations. In the west, you can visit the country’s French-influenced region. In the south, you’ll find Italian influences. In the southeast, Romanish is spoken in the Graubünden area.

    Switzerland is also deliciously known for its chocolates and cheeses. Most towns and cities offer both delicacies in a wonderous display of options. Its cuisine is also distinct, offering up fondue, raclette and rosti as traditional dishes.

    You’ll find spectacular recreation in the Swiss Alps, Jura Mountains and on the bountiful lakes and rivers of Switzerland. In addition to the incredible natural landmarks, you’ll also find many world-class cities. Geneva and Zurich are best known for their international importance, but there are many other towns worth visiting. If you have plenty of time in the country, visit Lugano, Lucerne, Bern, Lausanne and Zermatt. You’ll find each is a distinct destination with ample activities and attractions. The country has several excellent international airports, so it’s easy to find discounted business class tickets to the region.</summary><browserTitle> Luxuriate in Business Class Seats to Switzerland | IFlyFirstClass Travel Tips</browserTitle><created_date>8/23/2016 1:16:44 PM</created_date><seo><description> Luxuriate in Business Class Seats to Switzerland. More interesting information and travel tips at IFlyFirstClass.</description><keywords> Luxuriate in Business Class Seats to Switzerland</keywords></seo><images><image><alias>439a522e16664fbe86ddd4740ea05e83.png</alias><content_id>43</content_id><title>Luxuriate in First Class Seats to Switzerland</title><queue>0</queue></image></images></item><item><travel_tips_id>44</travel_tips_id><title> First Class Adventures Are On Tap in England</title><alias>planing-first-class-adventures-are-on-tap-in-england</alias><summary>With a history that reaches back thousands of years, England is a treasure trove of attractions. There are so many appealing places to visit in the United Kingdom that it’s tough to choose a manageable few.

    You could spend weeks just exploring the bustling neighborhoods and suburbs of London. As a destination base, London is perfectly situated. Staying in the city makes it easy to explore Greenwich and outlying areas such as Stonehenge, Cambridge and Bath. If you’re taking a cruise, London puts you within easy driving distance of the port at Southampton. If you want to explore the country’s Harry Potter connections, London is just an hour’s drive from the movies’ Leavesden studios. When you stay in London, you also have prime access to the city’s abundant historic, cultural and recreational attractions. You can tour famed Buckingham Palace, admire the view from the London Eye and catch a fun musical in the West End. London is one of the most popular destinations in the world, and it’s home to six thriving airports. As a result, you’ll find plenty of business class flight deals to the city.

    There’s more to England than London though. From quaint seaside towns to grand national parks, England has it all.
</summary><browserTitle> First Class Adventures Are On Tap in England | IFlyFirstClass Travel Tips</browserTitle><created_date>8/24/2016 10:30:41 AM</created_date><seo><description> First Class Adventures Are On Tap in England. More interesting information and travel tips at IFlyFirstClass.</description><keywords> First Class Adventures Are On Tap in England</keywords></seo><images><image><alias>f06b8c6a40204ba9b9f44661d0f2f722.png</alias><content_id>44</content_id><title>Amazing  First Class Adventures to England</title><queue>0</queue></image></images></item><item><travel_tips_id>45</travel_tips_id><title>Business Class to Belgium Blends Luxury with Fun</title><alias>business-class-to-belgium-blends-luxury-with-fun</alias><summary>
    Beautiful Belgium is a microcosm of what makes Europe so enticing. It boasts incredibly charming medieval cities, exciting modern metropolises and appealing scenic rivers. It holds some of the region’s most important government centers and commercial enterprises. It has amusement parks, nature reserves and thousands of museums. The only difficulty you’ll have while visiting Belgium is deciding how to spend your limited time here.

    In all likelihood, you’ll travel to some of the country’s most popular towns such as Brussels, Ghent, Bruges and Antwerp. If you can spare the time, the nation’s lesser-known towns such as Spa, Liege, Namur and Mons are also well-worth a visit.

    You’ll most enjoy Belgium if you make an effort to experience its unique cultural, culinary and historic features. Visit a local festival and rent a bike to cycle around town and the countryside. Sample several of the region’s legendary beers, and nibble on its scrumptious chocolates. Commit to trying a Belgian specialty with each meal, whether it’s mussels, stoemp potatoes, Jambon d&#39;Ardennes or caricoles seafood. Relax in one of the country’s famous spas or salt caves, and explore the country’s modern history.

    As an important global country, Belgium is blessed with many international travel options. There are several international airports in the country with amazing business class deals for travelers. Eurostar trains stop in most of the country’s major cities, so you can also easily fly into other nearby countries and take the train into Belgium. </summary><browserTitle>Business Class to Belgium Blends Luxury with Fun | IFlyFirstClass Travel Tips</browserTitle><created_date>8/29/2016 11:28:53 AM</created_date><seo><description>Business Class to Belgium Blends Luxury with Fun. More interesting information and travel tips at IFlyFirstClass.</description><keywords>Business Class to Belgium Blends Luxury with Fun</keywords></seo><images><image><alias>2f2f137ddd6c4f559d4a379281540651.png</alias><content_id>45</content_id><title>Business Class to Belgium Blends Luxury with Fun</title><queue>0</queue></image></images></item><item><travel_tips_id>46</travel_tips_id><title>Combine holiday activities with a business class flight to Germany.</title><alias>best-holiday-with-business-class-tickets-to-germany</alias><summary>A beacon of history, culture, industry and education in Europe, Germany is a top travel destination. Whether you’re fascinated by historic architecture, rich cuisine, exciting recreation or heart-warming traditions, Germany satisfies.

    If this is your first visit to Germany, you’ll likely head to one of the country’s big cities. Traveling to Berlin is especially fulfilling since you can tour medieval sites and contemporary locales. You can admire the old Bradenburg Gate then explore more recent history at the Berlin Wall. Museum Island, Spree River recreation, the Reichstag building and dozens of historic sites will keep you busy throughout your stay.

    Germany’s many regions also have delectable culinary traditions. In Germany’s southern region, you’ll find scrumptious Bavarian delights. You can feast on many familiar dishes like bratwurst, pretzels, potato salad and sauerkraut. You can also sample less-familiar dishes such as Regensburger Knackersemmel, a snack filled with sausage, and Schweinsbraten pork. In the north, you can try seafood-based soups like Hamburger Aalsuppe, and beef-based Bremer Labskaus.

    Many of the country’s most treasured events also offer up stellar regional dishes. If your first class flight to Germany is booked for the fall, try to find one of the local Oktoberfests to enjoy. Germany is also known for its incredible Christmas markets. Most cities, large and small, have some form of Christmas market, and they’re perfect for mingling with locals, eating well and enjoying the season’s bonhomie.
</summary><browserTitle>Combine holiday activities with a business class flight | IFlyFirstClass Travel Tips</browserTitle><created_date>8/30/2016 1:19:59 PM</created_date><seo><description>Combine holiday activities with a business class flight to Germany. More interesting information and travel tips at IFlyFirstClass.</description><keywords>Business class flight to Germany</keywords></seo><images><image><alias>b7176de14be24e5e8b23af099a513cde.png</alias><content_id>46</content_id><title>Combine holiday activities with a business class flight to Germany.</title><queue>0</queue></image></images></item><item><travel_tips_id>47</travel_tips_id><title>Search for discounted business class tickets to South Korea today</title><alias>searching-for-best-business-class-flight-to-south-korea</alias><summary>The Republic of Korea, or South Korea, is a thriving, cosmopolitan country. Its capital, Seoul, operates the world’s fourth largest economy, and it&#39;s home to 25 million people. This booming economy encompasses dozens of industries, but its electronics, appliance and auto industries are especially robust.

    While Korea is filled with many cosmopolitan cities and cutting-edge companies, the country honors its rich history too. There are dozens of ancient sites to visit while in Korea, from 1,500-year-old temple ruins to ancient observatories. Exploring the country’s cultural traditions and heritage creates a truly distinctive holiday. If you’re in Seoul in May, be sure to attend the spectacular lantern festivals celebrating Buddha’s birth. Search out local Korean folk, court or mask dance performances. Head to a cultural museum to view their Korean heritage exhibits and enjoy special events.

    Of course, Korea’s inventive citizens have also contributed to many modern cultural trends that are fun to explore too. Attend a K-pop concert or taekwondo competition. Visit one of the country’s many theme parks, and ride the convenient speedy bullet trains. Immersing yourself in Korean life will make your trip more memorable, no matter what activity you choose.

    Getting to Korea is relatively easy and inexpensive. As a top destination, business class flights to the country are plentiful and often discounted. There are also many international airports to choose from so you can head to the Korean region of your choice.</summary><browserTitle>Search for discounted business class tickets | IFlyFirstClass Travel Tips</browserTitle><created_date>8/31/2016 1:25:37 PM</created_date><seo><description>Search for discounted business class tickets to South Korea today. More interesting information and travel tips at IFlyFirstClass.</description><keywords>Cheapest business class to South Korea </keywords></seo><images><image><alias>4f76d9fe617f42cfbb820519a873bff8.png</alias><content_id>47</content_id><title>Search for discounted business class tickets to South Korea today</title><queue>0</queue></image></images></item><item><travel_tips_id>48</travel_tips_id><title> Revel in Kiwi Adventures with Business Class Flights</title><alias>cheapest-business-class-tickets-to-new-zealand</alias><summary>Say “hello,” or haere mae, to the gorgeous adventures awaiting in the Land of the Long White Cloud. New Zealand, known in Maori as Aotearoa, is famous for its jaw-dropping scenery and adrenaline-inducing recreation.

    The country is a delightful blend of Maori and European cultures. Rugby, or footy, is big here, particularly the national All Blacks team. You have “tea” instead of dinner, take a flying fox instead of a zipline and abseil rather than rappel. Personal responsibility and modesty are important in this beautiful country. Maori songs are known and sung by locals of every heritage. Above all, it is a welcoming, forward-thinking country that routinely celebrates its history and culture.

    Part of that celebration involves a deep connection to the land. Its grand fjords in the south are world-famous for their majesty and beauty. The beaches are frequented for their recreation and relaxation. There are incredible waterfalls, seaside cliffs, geothermal springs and startling blowholes. There are lush pastures, impressive caves and volcanic craters.

    There’s no end to the fun and excitement to be found in the country’s big, contemporary cities such as Auckland. Its outlying areas are just as dynamic. To enjoy all of the nation’s thrills, make the long journey across the Pacific easier on yourself. Book discounted business class tickets to any of the country’s major metropolitan airports. It’s the ultimate luxury adventure.</summary><browserTitle> Revel in Kiwi Adventures with Business Class Flights | IFlyFirstClass Travel Tips</browserTitle><created_date>9/2/2016 10:31:35 AM</created_date><seo><description> Revel in Kiwi Adventures with Business Class Flights. More interesting information and travel tips at IFlyFirstClass.</description><keywords>Business Class Tickets to New Zealand</keywords></seo><images><image><alias>5e6651932e084fc08914a6dd72ef2457.png</alias><content_id>48</content_id><title> Revel in Kiwi Adventures with Business Class Flights</title><queue>0</queue></image></images></item><item><travel_tips_id>49</travel_tips_id><title>South Africa&#39;s Exciting Attractions Are A First Class Flight Away</title><alias>find-last-minute-deals-on-first-class-flights-to-the-south-africa</alias><summary>On the southernmost tip of the African continent, South Africa is a lively country. Its history is unique, considered the birthplace of humankind. Its extensive history dates back three million years to Australopithecus africanus. As a result, South Africa is rich in archeological sites and museums displaying compelling fossils and artefacts.

    With so much coastline, South Africa is also a sports-lover’s dream. You can dive with great white sharks, snorkel with seahorses and sea kayak in the Western Cape. You can surf incredible waves and scuba dive on the Eastern Cape. In the interior, you can whitewater raft the country’s rivers and hike up majestic mountains. You can skydive or bungee jump, or you can take casual bike rides through wine country.

    The country has many fascinating landmarks and attractions too. Explore the country’s struggle with and eventual triumph over apartheid in many locales. Visit Robben Island near Cape Town to experience the sites where anti-apartheid leaders were imprisoned. Tour the Apartheid Museum in Johannesburg. See the District Six Museum, and browse the Nelson Mandela Museum.

    While in South Africa you should also take some time to discover the country’s cultural heritage. Admire the ancient rock art in Ukhahlamba-Drakensberg Park and take the Soweto Heritage Trail. Attend cultural performances at Eshowe in Zululand. It’s all part of South Africa’s unique experience.

    With many metropolitan cities, business class deals to South Africa are usually easy to find.
</summary><browserTitle>South Africa&#39;s Exciting Attractions Are A First Class | IFlyFirstClass Travel Tips</browserTitle><created_date>9/6/2016 3:28:01 AM</created_date><seo><description>South Africa's Exciting Attractions Are A First Class Flight Away. More interesting information and travel tips at IFlyFirstClass.</description><keywords>Find last minute deals on first class flights to the Pretoria area</keywords></seo><images><image><alias>797fad05de094ade9895eefdec4db060.png</alias><content_id>49</content_id><title>South Africa's Exciting Attractions Are A First Class Flight Away</title><queue>0</queue></image></images></item><item><travel_tips_id>50</travel_tips_id><title>Take Taiwan by Storm with Business Class Deals</title><alias>buying-business-class-tickets-to-taiwan-today</alias><summary>
    Once known as the land of Formosa, Taiwan is a beautiful Pacific island nation. The main island holds the country’s largest cities, including Taipei and Tainan. Most of these metropolitan areas are located on the western plateaus of the island. Central and eastern island areas boast rugged mountain ridges, imposing sea cliffs and quiet beaches.

    The country is a manufacturing, design and technology powerhouse. This success shows in the hundreds of skyscrapers dotting Taiwanese city skylines. Its advanced systems are also highlighted in the country’s high-speed train system. These bullet trains link Taipei in the north to Kaohsiung in the south at speeds of 186 miles an hour.

    Baseball is a national pastime in Taiwan, and it’s always fun to experience a local game. Another popular activity throughout the nation is to shop and dine at night markets. Night markets are the perfect places to experience local foods and regional wares. They’re usually busy and colorful and full of lively sights, aromas and sounds.

    As you would expect from an industrialized country, Taiwan is home to several international airports. This is good news for travelers since discounted business class tickets are frequently available.
</summary><browserTitle>Take Taiwan by Storm with Business Class Deals | IFlyFirstClass Travel Tips</browserTitle><created_date>9/7/2016 11:45:41 PM</created_date><seo><description>Take Taiwan by Storm with Business Class Deals. More interesting information and travel tips at IFlyFirstClass.</description><keywords>Business Class Deals to Taiwan</keywords></seo><images><image><alias>9664ba4c96824240a3499618d4d10a1c.png</alias><content_id>50</content_id><title>Take Taiwan by Storm with Business Class Deals</title><queue>0</queue></image></images></item><item><travel_tips_id>51</travel_tips_id><title> Beaches Retreats and City Showcases: Book Business Class to the U.S.</title><alias>searching-to-book-business-class-to-the-united-states</alias><summary>The United States is a big, diverse country spanning 2,700 to 2,800 from coast to coast. On the East Coast, you’ll find some of the country’s oldest cities. You’ll also find the country’s most populous city, New York. Affectionately known as the Big Apple, New York is a global city leading the way in industry, fashion, media and finance. It’s home to many famous landmarks, from Ellis Island and the Statue of Liberty to the 9/11 Memorial. The city embraces people from all countries and cultures around the world, and it shows in the many ethnic neighborhoods.

    At the southeastern edge of the country, Miami boasts an ambiance that is vastly different from New York. Once the land of Native American tribes, Miami is enlivened by Caribbean and Latin American cultures. It is known for its beaches, colorful Art Deco architecture and grand manors. It is also famous for its skyscrapers, cruise terminals and Cuban cuisine.

    The center of the country is considered the Heartland, home to farms and industry. Along the south, you can find Gulf Coast towns leading to warm, sprawling Texas, New Mexico and Arizona cities. Along the north, you can find Great Lakes gems leading to Big Sky country and legendary Idaho recreation.

    On the West Coast, you’ll find Washington’s unique flavor of northwestern Native American cultures. It’s also the spot for many flourishing industries, from tech and online retailing to coffeehouses. Heading south, you’ll find a recreation lover’s paradise in Oregon and Northern California. Coastal California includes icons like San Francisco, Silicon Valley and Los Angeles. The state’s massive interior, the Great Central Valley, is America’s breadbasket.

    Explore the country’s many delightful cities, national parks and inviting cultural distinctions. It’s easy when you book last minute business class deals to any major U.S. City.
</summary><browserTitle> Beaches Retreats and City Showcases | IFlyFirstClass Travel Tips</browserTitle><created_date>9/9/2016 2:28:30 PM</created_date><seo><description> Beaches Retreats and City Showcases: Book Business Class to the U.S.. More interesting information and travel tips at IFlyFirstClass.</description><keywords>buying a business class tickets
</keywords></seo><images><image><alias>5f8982db5dd64553a673ddcc5d403ef6.png</alias><content_id>51</content_id><title> Beaches Retreats and City Showcases: Book Business Class to the U.S.</title><queue>0</queue></image></images></item><item><travel_tips_id>52</travel_tips_id><title>Chinese Adventures Await Your Business Class Flight</title><alias>traveling-around-with-business-class-to-china</alias><summary>Immense, captivating and culturally rich, China is a magnificent travel destination. It boasts some of the world’s biggest cities, most of them along the country’s East Coast. Shanghai has the largest urban population, with 24 million residents. It’s known for its Yangtze River, historic Bund riverwalk and gleaming skyline. Beijing is only the third largest city in China, but it supports a population of 21 million. It’s also the country’s capital city, home to the Forbidden City, Tiananmen Square and the Temple of Heaven.

    There are other cities and provinces worth visiting in China. From the western Shaanxi province to the eastern Tianjin, China overflows with amazing towns. Many of these destinations have ancient temples and archeological sites and ultra-modern conveniences. This inviting mix of sites makes visiting China a pleasurable experience.

    While in China, it’s easy to become overwhelmed with all of the places to see and the things to do. Be sure to take a few moments each day to plan time to engage in some of the local cultural experiences too. Hop on a high-speed bullet train. Attend one of the many local festivals such as the Dai ethnic Water Splashing Festival. Take in a traditional Chinese dance performance.

    Traveling to China can be affordable and luxurious when you search for discounted business class tickets to any of China’s international airports. Most of the country’s major cities have international airports and an abundance of flight and airline options.</summary><browserTitle>Chinese Adventures Await Your Business Class Flight | IFlyFirstClass Travel Tips</browserTitle><created_date>9/12/2016 10:12:02 PM</created_date><seo><description>Chinese Adventures Await Your Business Class Flight. More interesting information and travel tips at IFlyFirstClass.</description><keywords>Cheapest Chinese Business Class Tickets </keywords></seo><images><image><alias>bff46e590f7f4b8ca3f9dc2bc27d22ce.png</alias><content_id>52</content_id><title>Cheapest Business Class Tickets to Chinese Adventures </title><queue>0</queue></image></images></item><item><travel_tips_id>53</travel_tips_id><title>Trek to India with Business Class Deals</title><alias>trekking-to-india-with-cheapest-business-tickets</alias><summary>Big, diverse and dynamic, India is a destination worth discovering. It sports Arabian beaches on the west, Indian Ocean delights on the east and the Himalayas to the north. Its vast interior is home to lively cities and a wealth of historical, cultural and culinary treasures.

    Mumbai is its largest city, home to an incredible waterfront and ancient temples carved into caves. While in the country, consider visiting Udaipur, often called Venice of the East for its many waterways. Munnar, the land of tea plantations, is also a beautiful place to experience Indian culture. Other cities of interest include Chennai, Pune, Amritsar, Hyderabad and Kolkata. India is so vast and has so many superb destinations that it takes several trips to visit them all.

    India has many distinct regions, and one of the best ways to enjoy this diversity is through its food. Of course, you can sample all of the familiar Indian foods. Delectable meats and flatbreads cooked in tandoor ovens and rice and lentil dishes are constant favorites. In the north, you’ll find dimsum-like momos with red chutney dipping sauce and rajma kidney beans. In the south, sample Idli rice and lentil patties and dosa.

    With all of the big cities spread throughout the country, there are plenty of business class deals to Indian airports. This is particularly true during the off-peak seasons from February to May and September to October.</summary><browserTitle>Trek to India with Business Class Deals | IFlyFirstClass Travel Tips</browserTitle><created_date>9/14/2016 5:26:25 PM</created_date><seo><description>Trek to India with Business Class Deals. More interesting information and travel tips at IFlyFirstClass.</description><keywords>Business Class Deals to India</keywords></seo><images><image><alias>b146abfbb49f4f9c8d62d545d839820e.png</alias><content_id>53</content_id><title>Trek to India with Business Class Deals</title><queue>0</queue></image></images></item><item><travel_tips_id>54</travel_tips_id><title>First Class to Luxury in Kuala Lumpur</title><alias>the-very-best-first-class-tickets-to-kuala-lumpur</alias><summary>Kuala Lumpur is the capital city of Malaysia, a gleaming, cosmopolitan city on the Malay Peninsula. Affectionately known as KL, the city is an economic powerhouse full of luxuries and high-end amenities. For all of its upscale glamor, though, KL has some affordable highlights. It abounds with first class flight deals, and it’s known for having the world’s cheapest five-star resorts. Visitors to the city can relish additional luxuries with incredible fine dining and chic shopping.

    While KL is undoubtedly high-tech and high-style, its roots are in its quaint mining-town sensibilities. Over the decades since its creation, KL experienced an influx of Chinese, British and Indian cultures. This diverse cultural blend is seen in the city’s early buildings. It sports Moghul-style shops, ornate mosques, Art Deco structures and tropical colonial sites. With all this architecture and culture to take it, KL is a visual feast.

    Although the city is large and sprawling, getting around is relatively convenient. The city’s monorail and metro rail systems link most of the major city districts with outlying areas.

    While in KL, you’ll find plenty of cultural adventures. Street food, curry houses and markets are plentiful and popular here. The variety and abundance of inexpensive food at these traditional eateries makes every meal and snack memorable. KL cuisine incorporates Chinese, Indian and Malay influences along with many southeast Asian favorites. Be sure to try the coconut milk-infused rice, Nasi Lemak and roti canai</summary><browserTitle>First Class to Luxury in Kuala Lumpur | IFlyFirstClass Travel Tips</browserTitle><created_date>9/16/2016 3:50:50 PM</created_date><seo><description>First Class to Luxury in Kuala Lumpur. More interesting information and travel tips at IFlyFirstClass.</description><keywords>First Class to Luxury in Kuala Lumpur</keywords></seo><images><image><alias>7de56558cceb4ae993b62bf8b614327c.png</alias><content_id>54</content_id><title>Luxurious First Class Flight to Kuala Lumpur</title><queue>0</queue></image></images></item><item><travel_tips_id>55</travel_tips_id><title> Fly Last Minute for Thrilling Philippine Holidays</title><alias>enjoy-last-minute-deals-to-the-philippines</alias><summary>More than 7,000 islands make up the Philippines, so it&#39;s a wonderland of tropical beaches. The country offers a little something for every travel preference. Whether you enjoy mountainous terrain and traditional villages or chic nightlife, the Philippines thrills.

    The country’s many international influences are evident in daily life here. Spanish, Chinese, Malay, Islamic and Indian traditions are all incorporated into the country’s identity. This is especially and delightfully true of Philippino cuisine. The mix of Polynesian, Spanish, Asian and American foods creates a unique local palate. While in the country, sample a few of the local culinary options. Visitor favorites include the sweet drink halo-halo, Spanish-inspired paella and lumpia spring rolls.

    The Philippines’ main and biggest island is Luzon, home to capital Manila and bustling metropolis Quezon City. Since the Philippines is part of the Ring of Fire, you can expect to see a variety of inactive and active volcanoes here. Extinct volcanoes and lava tubes create a fascinating cave system, and they’re worth exploring.

    With several cosmopolitan cities and world-famous travel destinations, several large airports are available here. One of the biggest international airports in the country is Manila’s Ninoy Aquino Airport. Mactan-Cebu and Davao International Airport are also busy, offering plenty of business class deals. </summary><browserTitle> Fly Last Minute for Thrilling Philippine Holidays | IFlyFirstClass Travel Tips</browserTitle><created_date>9/20/2016 11:34:39 AM</created_date><seo><description> Fly Last Minute for Thrilling Philippine Holidays. More interesting information and travel tips at IFlyFirstClass.</description><keywords>Get the Last Minute tickets  for Thrilling Philippine Holidays
</keywords></seo><images><image><alias>0f48fad828ef4bfdb12f9f789e274401.jpg</alias><content_id>55</content_id><title>Explore the unique history of the Philippines</title><queue>0</queue></image></images></item><item><travel_tips_id>56</travel_tips_id><title>Revel in Thai Delights with Last Minute Flights</title><alias>revel-in-thai-delights-with-last-minute-flights</alias><summary>Exploring the land that was once Siam is a fascinating exploration of history, culture and religion. You’ll see grand Thai palaces, spectacular temples and remnants of World War II. There are modern, crowded cities and quiet, mountainside villages. Lively beach resorts give way to tropical beach retreats. It’s all here in magnificent Thailand, and you can explore at your leisure with last minute flights.

    Whether you’ve chosen a beach holiday or a cosmopolitan city vacation, take time to explore the culture. This country is known for its hospitality and generosity, and locals are usually happy to share their traditions with visitors. You’ll find a unique mix of Lao, Chinese, Burmese, Indian and Cambodian influences here. These influences permeate much of Thailand’s cuisine, history, architecture and sports.

    While Thai cuisine is a favorite throughout the world, it’s a special experience to sample it here. Wherever you go in Thailand, be sure to eat as often as you can in local restaurants that offer authentic cuisine. From simple jasmine rice to intricate sauces, Thai food is a treat.

    Thailand is an extremely popular destination, so there are many discount flight options. For the best deals, search for last minute business class bargains. You’re likely to find terrific savings, and enjoy the long flight to Thailand that much more.</summary><browserTitle>Revel in Thai Delights with Last Minute Flights | IFlyFirstClass Travel Tips</browserTitle><created_date>9/26/2016 9:02:30 PM</created_date><seo><description>Revel in Thai Delights with Last Minute Flights. More interesting information and travel tips at IFlyFirstClass.</description><keywords>Last Minute Flights</keywords></seo><images><image><alias>b1acd069f2674381a59cbca00b7576ca.jpg</alias><content_id>56</content_id><title>Renowned tropical beaches and last minute flight deals create the perfect holiday.</title><queue>0</queue></image></images></item><item><travel_tips_id>57</travel_tips_id><title>Business Class Deals to the Unique United States</title><alias>united-states-business-class-deals</alias><summary>Sandwiched between Canada and Mexico, the United States is diverse and industrious. Less than 250 years old, the U.S. is nevertheless filled with important historic sites. On the East Coast, you’ll find some of the country’s oldest cities with British colonial roots. On the West Coast, you’ll find cities with a long Spanish and Mexican history.

    Throughout the nation, visitors also find a spectacular array of storied national parks. In California, Yosemite’s granite mountains, waterfalls and woods are irresistible. In South Dakota, you’ll discover famous Mt. Rushmore’s presidential mountainside. In Wyoming, the geysers and fascinating thermal springs of Yellowstone are breathtaking. In Arizona, Grand Canyon is awe-inspiring, and in Florida, the Everglades are compelling. There are 53 other magnificent national parks to explore and enjoy, so get out there and play.

    Some travelers believe the best way to experience an area is to sample its cuisine. The U.S. has many regional specialties, from New England seafood to Tex-Mex in the southwest. Try southern barbeque, Philly cheesesteak and Chicago deep dish pizza. Sample smoke Pacific salmon in Seattle, plate lunches in Hawaii and low country boils in South Carolina. The U.S. has a rich food culture, and your trip will be more pleasurable if you relish local dishes.

    More than 30 cities in the U.S. have more than 500,000 people, and most are served by major airports. This makes finding a deal on business class flights near your destination very likely. That’s a bonus, since saving on your flight allows you to spend more budget on exploring the country.</summary><browserTitle>Business Class Deals to the Unique United States | IFlyFirstClass Travel Tips</browserTitle><created_date>9/29/2016 10:24:44 AM</created_date><seo><description>Business Class Deals to the Unique United States. More interesting information and travel tips at IFlyFirstClass.</description><keywords> United States business class deals
</keywords></seo><images><image><alias>f280dc7f8c7d48ac9e1b25371594c584.jpg</alias><content_id>57</content_id><title> Last minute business class deals enrich travel in the U.S.</title><queue>0</queue></image></images></item><item><travel_tips_id>58</travel_tips_id><title> Book Last Minute Flights to Explore Ancient Egypt</title><alias>best-last-minut-flights-to-egypt</alias><summary>With the Mediterranean Sea to its north and the Red Sea on its east, Egypt is scenic and fruitful. From spectacular pyramids to majestic mosques, Egypt is astonishing in its magnificence.

    Of course, you should visit some of the country’s most well-known metropolises. Cairo, Giza, Alexandria and Luxor are amazing cities that will captivate you. There are other, smaller towns that are also worth a visit. This is particularly true of cities along the Red Sea. Visit the posh beaches of Sharm el-Sheikh for five-star experiences. The Red Sea&#39;s Hurghada is known for its stellar scuba sites, and Marsa Alam is a dolphin lover&#39;s delight. On the Arabian Gulf, Dahab is another favorite locale for windsurfing.

    Inland, you’ll find the country’s compelling desert and Bahariya mountains. This area is rich in history and recreation, from Deir Abu Makar monastery to dune adventures. You can take a camel ride in the desert to marvel at breathtaking sunsets. You can relax in Bir Sigam hot springs and climb English Mountain for remarkable Black Desert views. For a truly spectacular experience, visit the Farafra Oasis. There, you’ll find the beautiful White Desert and Djarra Caves.

    Egypt is home to several international airports. For most northern cities, it may be easiest to book last minute business class deals Cairo Airport.</summary><browserTitle> Book Last Minute Flights to Explore Ancient Egypt | IFlyFirstClass Travel Tips</browserTitle><created_date>9/30/2016 2:09:16 PM</created_date><seo><description> Book Last Minute Flights to Explore Ancient Egypt. More interesting information and travel tips at IFlyFirstClass.</description><keywords>Last Minute Flights to Egypt</keywords></seo><images><image><alias>c1a09059400c4760847d7efcb633a3e6.jpg</alias><content_id>58</content_id><title>Find last minute deals to Egypt to explore an oasis of history, culture and incredible architecture.</title><queue>0</queue></image></images></item><item><travel_tips_id>59</travel_tips_id><title>Business Class to Italy Defines Luxury Travel</title><alias>comfy-business-class-deals-to-italy</alias><summary>From its earliest days, Italy has influenced Western art, culture, cuisine and civilization. The country beams with incredible cities, from historic Rome to fashionable Milan. It also boasts amazing regions, including Tuscany, Umbria, Calabria and Piedmont.

    These regions offer their own delights, traditions and cuisines. In fact, eating and drinking your way through Italy is a great way to learn about Italy&#39;s regions. In Tuscany, simple dishes are the best, from Zuppa di Fagioli soup to tagliatelle al Tartufo. Sate your thirst throughout your Tuscan meal by sipping local Chianti. In the Piedmont region, the food is a little richer and creamier. Here, egg-based tajarin pasta often takes center stage for the main meal, and Alba white truffle is abundant. In the southern Calabria region, you’ll find vegetables packed in oil and a variety of fish.

    Give yourself more budget to spend on Italian culinary adventures by slashing your flight costs. Italy boasts several international airports offering hundreds of flights. With this variety comes many discounted business class tickets. Summer is peak travel season in Italy, so flying in spring and fall offers better deals.</summary><browserTitle>Business Class to Italy Defines Luxury Travel | IFlyFirstClass Travel Tips</browserTitle><created_date>10/3/2016 12:25:04 PM</created_date><seo><description>Business Class to Italy Defines Luxury Travel. More interesting information and travel tips at IFlyFirstClass.</description><keywords>Book Business Class to Remarkable Rome
</keywords></seo><images><image><alias>836e53195da244e688a304d2fd736359.jpg</alias><content_id>59</content_id><title>The luxuries of Italy include business class flights to the heart of Western civilization.</title><queue>0</queue></image></images></item><item><travel_tips_id>60</travel_tips_id><title>First Class Luxury in Malaysia</title><alias>first-class-to-malaysia</alias><summary>An interesting mixture of Malay, Chinese and Indian cultures, Malaysia is enticing. Part of the country is located on the Malay Peninsula and part is on the island of Borneo. The country is known for its posh cities, thriving economy, tropical beaches and lush rainforests. Its blend of cultures also extends to its mix of religions. Although Islam is technically the state religion, most other world religions are practiced here without conflict.

    This multiculturalism is also evident in the country’s cuisine. Many of the favorite local dishes feature flavors and techniques of other culinary traditions. While you’re in Malaysia, try some of these dishes to see if you can pick up the cultural origins. Favorite Malaysian dishes include the stir-fried noodles of mee goreng and rice-based nasi lemak. You should also try rendang beef or chicken, popiah basah and laksa.

    The country has many world-class cities, including its capital Kuala Lumpur. Other large cities in Malaysia include Johor Bahru, Ipoh, Shah Alam and Petaling Jaya. All have more than 600,000 residents, and all have captivating histories. The country also sports interesting small villages that are worth a visit.

    Kuala Lumpur International Airport is the country’s largest airport. You’ll likely find numerous discounted first class tickets to this bustling airport. Other large international airports in Malaysia include Kota Kinabalu, Penang and Kuching.</summary><browserTitle>First Class Luxury in Malaysia | IFlyFirstClass Travel Tips</browserTitle><created_date>10/5/2016 12:53:35 PM</created_date><seo><description>First Class Luxury in Malaysia. More interesting information and travel tips at IFlyFirstClass.</description><keywords>First Class Luxury in Malaysia</keywords></seo><images><image><alias>610f032b6d9f427c829a88d14f057086.jpg</alias><content_id>60</content_id><title> Revel in luxurious destinations with last minute first class flights to Malaysia.</title><queue>0</queue></image></images></item><item><travel_tips_id>61</travel_tips_id><title>Find Your Desert Oasis with Business Class to Qatar</title><alias>business-class-to-qatar-booking-today</alias><summary>A bastion of education, art and industry, Qatar is a thriving country on the Persian Gulf. Doha, on the country’s central east coast, is the capital of the country and its biggest city. It’s a chic, trend-setting metropolis with many shopping centers, resorts and restaurants. You can get to most other Qatari cities within a few hours’ drive of Doha.

    Although Qatar is appealingly modern in many ways, it retains some conservative Islamic values. Bringing alcohol into the country is illegal, and purchasing it at a store requires documentation. It’s much easier for visitors to purchase cocktails in hotel nightclubs.

    Dining throughout Qatar is a delight, with a variety of culinary styles and high-end restaurants. Qatari food is based on Arabic flavors with Indian, Persian and North African influences. You’ll find succulent roast lamb, flavorful rice dishes and rich stews for main courses. Fresh fruits, dates and Middle Eastern pastries are frequent dessert choices. If you want to explore local dishes in an authentic atmosphere, head to Doha’s Souq Waqif. The souq has many food stalls, and you’ll get to enjoy cultural performances while dining.

    To travel to Qatar, you’ll likely find the best business class deals to Hamad International Airport. The airport is located in Doha, so it’s convenient to most of Qatar’s most spectacular sites.</summary><browserTitle>Find Your Desert Oasis with Business Class to Qatar | IFlyFirstClass Travel Tips</browserTitle><created_date>10/6/2016 1:42:32 PM</created_date><seo><description>Find Your Desert Oasis with Business Class to Qatar. More interesting information and travel tips at IFlyFirstClass.</description><keywords> Business Class to Qatar</keywords></seo><images><image><alias>6035896135994929898c6089ca46c10d.jpg</alias><content_id>61</content_id><title>Luxuriate in the history and glamor of Qatar.</title><queue>0</queue></image></images></item><item><travel_tips_id>62</travel_tips_id><title>Business Class to Sweden Reveals Treasures Big and Small</title><alias>enjoy-sweden-with-business-class-tickets-to-gotland</alias><summary>
    Nestled between Finland and Norway, Sweden is a Scandinavian treasure. It’s rich in history, art, architecture and recreation. Even better, it has preserved many of its historic villages so that you can enjoy them to the fullest.

    Stockholm is Sweden’s biggest city and capital, and it is home to countless attractions. Gothenburg is about a third of the size of Stockholm but still a vibrant, bustling city. Most other towns and villages in Sweden are smaller and equally delightful. You&#39;ll find some of your most memorable experiences touring these small towns.

    Famously neutral in its international relations, Sweden performs highly by modern standards. Its economy, educational system, government and civil liberties all rate superbly. It’s also famously the home of the 70s musical group ABBA. In fact, if you feel like releasing your inner disco dancer, the ABBA Museum is a must-see.

    The country is also known for its fresh and rich cuisine. You can eat all you want at traditional smorgasbord buffets. Sample Swedish meatballs and gravy, lingonberry jam, local pancakes, pastries and boiled potatoes. Wash it all down with local coffee or the distilled Akvavit.

    Sweden abounds with experiences you won’t find in more land-locked nations. Book discounted business class tickets to any of its international airports today.
</summary><browserTitle>Business Class to Sweden Reveals Treasures Big and Small | IFlyFirstClass Travel Tips</browserTitle><created_date>10/10/2016 10:52:42 PM</created_date><seo><description>Business Class to Sweden Reveals Treasures Big and Small. More interesting information and travel tips at IFlyFirstClass.</description><keywords>Business Class to Sweden </keywords></seo><images><image><alias>95e444d6242b4260b50d313b872470d3.jpg</alias><content_id>62</content_id><title>Fresh, vibrant and culinarily rich Sweden is a dream destination.</title><queue>0</queue></image></images></item><item><travel_tips_id>63</travel_tips_id><title>Last Minute to Turkey: Modern Life Among Ancient Ruins</title><alias>last-minute-deals-to-turkey-are-incredible</alias><summary>A popular cruise departure point and destination, Turkey is a growing tourism center. Its location bridging Europe and Asia is part of its immense charm. It boasts marvelous Mediterranean, Black and Aegean Sea beaches. It is home to the economically and geopolitically important Turkish Straits. It sports thrilling rivers, the wonderful Mount Ararat and beautiful Lake Van. These rivers, seas and lakes played a large role in the country’s history. Today, they are often tremendous sources of recreation and industry.

    Turkey teems with interesting and exciting cities and villages. There’s the big, vibrant capital city Ankara, with its many important museums. There’s the seaside resort city of Side, which was once occupied by Alexander the Great. There are the incredible rock formations of Capodoccia and the beaches and ruins of Bodrum. Wherever you go in Turkey, it seems there’s a breathtaking ancient site or magnificent modern attraction.

    The country’s growing tourism industry is served by several convenient airports. If you’re traveling to Istanbul, you’ll likely use Atatürk International Airport. If your destination is Ankara, you’ll probably find Esenboğa Airport most convenient. There are also last minute flights available to Antalya Airport. If you’re visiting Europe first, book your flights to Europe, then take the TransBalkan train from Budapest to Turkey</summary><browserTitle>Last Minute to Turkey: Modern Life Among Ancient Ruins | IFlyFirstClass Travel Tips </browserTitle><created_date>10/10/2016 11:17:47 PM</created_date><seo><description>Last Minute to Turkey: Modern Life Among Ancient Ruins. More interesting information and travel tips at IFlyFirstClass.</description><keywords>Last Minute to Turkey</keywords></seo><images><image><alias>59cc12cfc1054467a7f3cf2ecd86339e.jpg</alias><content_id>63</content_id><title>Modern recreation and ancient ruins enliven your last minute first class flights to Turkey.</title><queue>0</queue></image></images></item><item><travel_tips_id>64</travel_tips_id><title>Snag First Class Flight Deals to Vietnam</title><alias>first-class-to-vietnam</alias><summary>With the passage of time, Vietnam has mostly shed its wartime past and become a popular destination. This appealing country is irresistible. It boasts beautiful temples and pagodas and gorgeous mountains. It sports lively town markets and delectable cuisine. It has beaches, islands, waterfalls and river deltas. If you’re looking for a romantic honeymoon spot, an adventure or a history lesson, Vietnam is the place to go.

    In the north, Hanoi is the country’s capital city. To the south, Ho Chi Minh City is the country’s largest metropolis. In between, the country teems with culture-filled towns, charming villages and historic sites. Some popular towns and rural areas to visit in Vietnam include Nha Trang, Phu Quoc, Sa Pa, Danang and Dalat. Ha Long Bay is particularly appealing with its unique limestone pillars scattered within the bay water.

    Vietnamese cuisine is distinctive and delicious, and it’s easy to build an entire trip around its culinary offerings. You can expect many dishes to feature typical flavors of lemongrass, fish sauce, mint, ginger and lime. With so much coastline, you can also expect a wide variety of fresh fish and other seafood. Rice is, of course, featured at nearly every meal. You’ll also find many variations of steamed rice cakes and rolls, or bánh, and noodle soups.

    The country is served by three geographically convenient international airports. As a result, you’ll find plenty of discounted first class tickets to Vietnam. These first class flights give you the perfect entry to a Vietnamese holiday.
</summary><browserTitle>Snag First Class Flight Deals to Vietnam | IFlyFirstClass Travel Tips</browserTitle><created_date>10/13/2016 9:05:11 PM</created_date><seo><description>Snag First Class Flight Deals to Vietnam. More interesting information and travel tips at IFlyFirstClass.</description><keywords>First Class to Vietnam</keywords></seo><images><image><alias>899a8e985072494eaf9273e67713bb4c.jpg</alias><content_id>64</content_id><title>Revel in the stellar sights, sounds and history of Vietnam.</title><queue>0</queue></image></images></item><item><travel_tips_id>65</travel_tips_id><title>Last Minute Flights to the Coastal Delights of Adelaide</title><alias>great-last-minute-flights-to-adelaide</alias><summary>The capital of South Australia, Adelaide is a fetching coastal city on St. Vincent Gulf. The city’s vibrant port was responsible for its initial appeal in the 19th century. Its countless cultural attractions, thriving industries and spectacular recreation are its modern lures. In fact, Adelaide is a popular destination for all travelers, drawing 2.7 million people each year.

    The city’s location is a dream for travelers who want to explore and enjoy nature. The picturesque River Torrens runs through the city. Its riverbanks create some of Adelaide’s best event venues and awesome recreation. To the west of Adelaide, the region offers excellent beaches, interesting islands and a vast St. Vincent Gulf. To the east are Mount Lofty range mountains and hills.

    No doubt buoyed by living in such a beautiful city, Adelaide residents are welcoming and fun. You can enjoy the city’s bountiful hospitality at world-class events such as Adelaide Festival. The annual event hosts performers, artists and writers from around the world each March. Other popular events include Adelaide Fashion Festival, Adelaide Fringe and WOMAdelaide.

    Getting to this enchanting city is also a breeze. Adelaide International Airport is just a few miles west of the city center and very accessible. You’ll likely find a number of available last minute business class deals to the city throughout the year.
</summary><browserTitle>Last Minute Flights to the Coastal Delights of Adelaide | IFlyFirstClass Travel Tips</browserTitle><created_date>10/17/2016 7:35:04 PM</created_date><seo><description>Last Minute Flights to the Coastal Delights of Adelaide. More interesting information and travel tips at IFlyFirstClass.</description><keywords>Last minute flights to Adelaide</keywords></seo><images><image><alias>fec0ad6c0cdb40ed9e40a3abd1d9df82.jpg</alias><content_id>65</content_id><title>Revel in Adelaide’s galleries, shopping, wineries and beaches with last minute deals to Australia.</title><queue>0</queue></image></images></item><item><travel_tips_id>66</travel_tips_id><title>Barcelona: Beaches, Buildings and Business Class Seats</title><alias>business-class-to-barcelona</alias><summary>Barcelona is a world-class destination, drawing millions of visitors to its sunny Mediterranean climate. It’s a city with a long history of producing renowned artists, writers and architects. It has spectacular beaches, a popular cruise port and notable gardens. It is warm and inviting, chic and innovative and always eventful.

    Barcelona is actually the heart of Catalonia. This culturally rich region offers plenty of traditions, art and customs to explore. You may notice many of the locals speaking Catalan, and most signage is in Catalan. Even so, you likely won’t have problems understanding locals or getting around Barcelona. That’s especially true in tourist-serving areas where you can usually find more than a few English-speakers. On the other hand, it’s always a good idea to learn a few Catalan words and phrases before you go.

    There are few experiences you should seek out while in Barcelona. The evening tradition of tapas is particularly appealing. The late night small-plate foods encourage you to stroll from one eatery to the next. This restaurant-hopping is a great way to sample many foods and enjoy the Barcelonan community. It may seem trite, but go ahead and book tickets to a Flamenco performance too. The colorful dance and traditional music is enriching and memorable. Spain and Catalonia are also known for their many festivals. Check before you go to see if your visit coincides with a festival or event. Visiting one of the local celebrations is a delightful way to experience Barcelona.
</summary><browserTitle>Barcelona: Beaches, Buildings and Business Class | IFlyFirstClass Travel Tips</browserTitle><created_date>10/20/2016 1:13:57 AM</created_date><seo><description>Barcelona: Beaches, Buildings and Business Class Seats. More interesting information and travel tips at IFlyFirstClass.</description><keywords>Business class to Barcelona </keywords></seo><images><image><alias>f67f8c256983434ca849be41f6895900.jpg</alias><content_id>66</content_id><title>Revel in Barcelona’s treasures with discounted business class tickets.</title><queue>0</queue></image></images></item><item><travel_tips_id>67</travel_tips_id><title>Revel in Business Class Deals to Johannesburg</title><alias>business-class-deals-to-johannesburg</alias><summary>Sprawling Johannesburg is large, urban and cosmopolitan. It’s often described as the heart of South Africa’s fashion and art scene, but it has so much more to offer. One of its most appealing features is its role in South Africa’s gold rush. In fact, the city arose from the late 19th century gold mining boom. There are several sites in the area that allow you to explore this history. These sites include the Kromdraai Gold Mine and other gold reef establishments. The city’s extensive amusement park, Gold Reef City, even celebrates the region’s golden history.

    Long before gold was discovered in the Johannesburg highveld, the region was the site of early man’s development. The Cradle of Humankind is about an hour outside of town, the excavation site of man’s birthplace. It offers a fascinating museum and discovery center and 13 important archaeological sites.

    Johannesburg also played an important role in South Africa’s path to racial equality and democracy. The Apartheid Museum tells the moving story of the fight for freedom, and the Mandela Family Museum continues the discussion. Constitution Hill is an important site for the past and present. It reveals the prisons that once incarcerated freedom fighters and houses today’s constitutional court that protects racial equality.

    As an urban center, Johannesburg also boasts rousing nightlife, popular sports venues and many cultural and scientific centers. It sports an amenity-filled airport, O.R. Tambo International Airport. For the best deals, search for discounted business class tickets to Johannesburg.
</summary><browserTitle>Revel in Business Class Deals to Johannesburg | IFlyFirstClass Travel Tips</browserTitle><created_date>10/27/2016 4:08:23 PM</created_date><seo><description>Revel in Business Class Deals to Johannesburg. More interesting information and travel tips at IFlyFirstClass.</description><keywords>business class deals to Johannesburg</keywords></seo><images><image><alias>35aa31567b8043f19d2759c71158cd10.jpg</alias><content_id>67</content_id><title>Enjoy comfortable business class flights to Johannesburg to explore the birthplace of humankind.</title><queue>0</queue></image></images></item><item><travel_tips_id>68</travel_tips_id><title>Last Minute Deals to Milan Lead to Exquisite Art, Architecture</title><alias>last-minute-tickets-to-milan</alias><summary>Famously progressive on social issues, Amsterdam is a welcoming, fun city. In spite of its laidback reputation, the city has plenty of exciting activities and thrills. You don’t even have to visit Amsterdam’s Red Light District to find them either.

    The Leidseplein is the place to go for after-dark fun. This lively square is known for its nightclubs and restaurants, but it’s also a vibrant square during the day. In the summer, you can expect to find a variety of festivals, events and performances on the square. In the winter, it’s converted to a vibrant outdoor ice skating rink.

    If you’re looking for a quiet, relaxing trip to the city, you’re in luck too. Enjoy a peaceful cruise on the canals. Pick a neighborhood and explore it on a rented bicycle. Find a cozy sidewalk cafe and watch the passersby, or explore local history with a visit to the Resistance Museum. The city is full of appealing neighborhoods with canals, street markets, food stalls and shops to explore.</summary><browserTitle>Last Minute Deals to Milan Lead to Exquisite Art | IFlyFirstClass Travel Tips</browserTitle><created_date>10/27/2016 4:23:01 PM</created_date><seo><description>Last Minute Deals to Milan Lead to Exquisite Art, Architecture. More interesting information and travel tips at IFlyFirstClass.</description><keywords>last minute tickets to Milan
</keywords></seo><images><image><alias>559e6bbc00ba4e088f65a05f0c5b45f8.jpg</alias><content_id>68</content_id><title>Revel in Milan’s artistry with cheap last minute tickets to Milan.</title><queue>0</queue></image></images></item><item><travel_tips_id>69</travel_tips_id><title> Save Big on Discounted Business Class Tickets to Osaka</title><alias>osaka-discounted-business-class-tickets</alias><summary>Immense, commercial and historic, Osaka is home to 2.5 million people and many more million in nearby suburbs. This sprawling bayside city has many exciting and electric commercial districts. From downtown Kita to busy Minami, there’s never a shortage of nightlife and entertainment here. On the city’s west, you’ll find thriving Osaka Bay with attractions like Tempozan Harbour Village and Universal Studios. There are dozens of small islands in this area, too, making ferry travel and bridges abundant.

    If you look a little deeper, beyond the skyscrapers and giant electronic signs, you’ll discover Osaka’s rich history. Dating back to the 5th century B.C.E., Osaka has been a bustling port and town for centuries. Sadly, many of its historic sites were lost during the bombing raids of World War II. However, many of these buildings such as Osaka Castle have been lovingly and meticulously recreated.

    Transportation options to and around Osaka are abundant. As one of the country’s top destinations, discounted business class tickets to Osaka are readily available. The main international airport, Kansai, has two train stations on site for your convenience. In addition to local train transit, the city’s ferry and subway systems are extensive. To truly experience the city as a local, though, you’ll need to hop on a bike. The flat roads and plentiful sights make cycling around the city a good option.</summary><browserTitle> Save Big on Discounted Business Class Tickets | IFlyFirstClass Travel Tips</browserTitle><created_date>11/1/2016 3:39:24 PM</created_date><seo><description> Save Big on Discounted Business Class Tickets to Osaka. More interesting information and travel tips at IFlyFirstClass.</description><keywords>Osaka discounted business class tickets</keywords></seo><images><image><alias>af19864ff4154dea9043412ac40da00d.jpg</alias><content_id>69</content_id><title> Relish the beauty, industry and atmosphere of Osaka with discounted business class flights to the city.</title><queue>0</queue></image></images></item><item><travel_tips_id>70</travel_tips_id><title>Visit World-Class San Francisco with Business Class Deals</title><alias>san-francisco-business-class-deals</alias><summary>Gorgeous San Francisco is one of the top destinations in the U.S. Its hilly terrain, incredible landmarks, unique history and rich culture make it one-of-a-kind. It&#39;s rich with innovative restaurants, delightful shopping and thrilling theatrical performances.

    Some of San Francisco’s most memorable experiences are found in its inviting neighborhoods. Chinatown is one of the city’s most famous districts. You’ll find amazing restaurants, eclectic shops and a wide array of Chinese wares. In Union Square, you can shop for days, snag discount theater tickets and find high-end hotels. Alamo Square is best known for its Painted Ladies Victorian houses, and Japantown is a shopper’s delight. The Castro is known for its LGBTQ community, and Haight-Ashbury is known for its 60s counterculture. In North Beach, you can dine on authentic Italian food then giggle through a &#34;Beach Blanket Babylon&#34; performance.

    Getting around the city and the surrounding area is easier using BART. On the other hand, you’ll always find something new by walking around the city. Wear comfortable shoes, though, as you’ll be tackling some challenging hills. To get a good feel for the city, its history and its layout, you might consider taking a guided tour. This gives you some context of city&#39;s culture and neighborhoods you might otherwise miss. The city also has many food and neighborhood tours that give you more intimate knowledge of specific neighborhoods.

    With San Francisco’s popularity as a destination, you’ll find plenty of business class flight deals. San Francisco International Airport is located just a few miles south of the city and is the easiest entry point. </summary><browserTitle>Visit World-Class San Francisco with Business Class | IFlyFirstClass Travel Tips</browserTitle><created_date>11/1/2016 4:28:00 PM</created_date><seo><description>Visit World-Class San Francisco with Business Class Deals. More interesting information and travel tips at IFlyFirstClass.</description><keywords>San Francisco Business Class Deals</keywords></seo><images><image><alias>f9e0ea20ff914210b14faefe2e3398a9.jpg</alias><content_id>70</content_id><title>See San Francisco’s top sights with business class deals to the City by the Bay.</title><queue>0</queue></image></images></item><item><travel_tips_id>71</travel_tips_id><title>Relish Last Minute Deals to Sydney</title><alias>last-minute-deals-to-sydney</alias><summary>Beloved for its gorgeous sights and bustling metropolitan atmosphere, Sydney is a top destination. The city is the capital of Australia’s New South Wales, located on brilliant Sydney Harbour. While the Opera House and Harbour Bridge are its most recognizable structures, the city teems with spectacular sites. Walk through history in The Rocks, mingle with the masses at Bondi Beach. Tour historic ships, government buildings and parks. Thrill yourself with jaunts to theme parks, climbs up the bridge and walks around Sydney Tower&#39;s apex. You’ll find magnificent festivals, endless shopping and more museums and galleries than you can imagine. As a cosmopolitan city, Sydney is first rate.

    With its many harbors, islands and inlets, ferries make getting around Sydney and its suburbs simple. You’ll also find convenient transport on local commuter and light rail trains. These are especially helpful if you are reluctant to learn to drive on the left side of the road. You can access trains directly at Sydney Airport if that’s where your last minute deals take you.

    Dining in Sydney is a gastronomic delight. The city is full of upscale restaurants to delectable street food. With its British and Asian influences, many travelers mistakenly think Sydney offers typical fare. While it does have many of your favorite international culinary styles, it also has uniquely Oz flavors. Try a few of these local favorites like hamburgers with beetroot or barramundi and john dory fish. Kangaroo, crocodile and emu meat are also local meats you won’t easily find outside of Oceania. If you’re really adventurous, try the bush favorite of grubs. Even food can be a thrill in Sydney.</summary><browserTitle>Relish Last Minute Deals to Sydney | IFlyFirstClass Travel Tips</browserTitle><created_date>11/3/2016 2:27:57 PM</created_date><seo><description>Relish Last Minute Deals to Sydney. More interesting information and travel tips at IFlyFirstClass.</description><keywords>Last Minute Deals to Sydney</keywords></seo><images><image><alias>95559c24c98f4b55b8752bf9bea362c1.png</alias><content_id>71</content_id><title>Last minute business class deals to Sydney give you a chance to enjoy exciting city attractions and thrilling natural escapades.</title><queue>0</queue></image></images></item><item><travel_tips_id>72</travel_tips_id><title>Business Class to Amsterdam&#39;s Lively, Scenic Neighborhoods</title><alias>amsterdam-business-class</alias><summary>Famously progressive on social issues, Amsterdam is a welcoming, fun city. In spite of its laidback reputation, the city has plenty of exciting activities and thrills. You don’t even have to visit Amsterdam’s Red Light District to find them either. </summary><browserTitle>Find business class deals to Amsterdam </browserTitle><created_date>1/7/2017 12:08:35 AM</created_date><seo><description>Business class tickets are the perfect choice for traveling to Amsterdam's historic, culturally rich and picturesque sites. Call now for tickets.
</description><keywords>Business Class to Amsterdam</keywords></seo><images><image><alias>ed246bceeefd453983754eac465e84fa.jpg</alias><content_id>72</content_id><title>Find business class deals to Amsterdam so you </title><queue>0</queue></image></images></item><item><travel_tips_id>73</travel_tips_id><title>Zurich last minute business class</title><alias>zurich-last-minute-business-class</alias><summary>Zurich is known for its world-class financial institutions, high-end entertainment and gorgeous location. With all of its glittering amenities and sites, Zurich is a top global destination. The city abounds with history, industry, recreation and entertainment, so you have plenty of activity choices. You could spend a few weeks here and still not visit all of the city’s superb sites. Last minute business class deals help extend your travel budget, leaving you more time and money to spend in Zurich.

    One of your first stops should be to the city’s Old Town center. There, you’ll find many attractions worth your time. A guided walking tour of Old Town is a great way to start exploring the area. Some Old Town highlights include:
    Fraumunster,
    Grossmunster,
    Peter’s Church and
    Muhlesteg Footbridge.</summary><browserTitle>Last Minute Business Class to Zurich is Full-Time Fun  | IFlyFirstClass Travel Tips</browserTitle><created_date>1/7/2017 12:34:07 AM</created_date><seo><description>Historic churches, lively recreation and culturally rich pursuits make last minute business class deals to Zurich a joy. Book your deals today.</description><keywords> Last Minute to Zurich Business Class Deals</keywords></seo><images><image><alias>b6dbb32e782843ee969bb93387f2d21a.jpg</alias><content_id>73</content_id><title>The glittering, global city of Zurich awaits your last minute business class flight.</title><queue>0</queue></image></images></item><item><travel_tips_id>74</travel_tips_id><title>First class deals to Beijing</title><alias>first-class-deals-to-beijing</alias><summary>The world’s third most populous city, Beijing is home to more than 21 million people. Its immense size is equaled only by its tremendous historic significance. It’s also very cosmopolitan, with plenty of high-end resorts, entertainment and dining to satisfy first class travelers.

    The city’s monuments and structures involved in China’s revolutionary and Communist history are often most fascinating to Westerners. Places such as Tiananmen Square and Memorial Hall of Chairman Mao are among these compelling sites.</summary><browserTitle>First Class to Beijing Reveals Spectacular Sights | IFlyFirstClass Travel Tips</browserTitle><created_date>1/7/2017 12:45:47 AM</created_date><seo><description> Ancient temples, royal palaces, imposing Great Wall gates and incredible landscapes reveal Beijing's flair. Book first class deals to Beijing today.</description><keywords>First class deals to Beijing</keywords></seo><images><image><alias>f61b96e8363b4d0d9580a49bc52b0493.jpg</alias><content_id>74</content_id><title>Book discounted first class tickets to Beijing to experience its grandeur, history and modern delights.</title><queue>0</queue></image></images></item><item><travel_tips_id>75</travel_tips_id><title>Cairo Business Class Deals</title><alias>cairo-business-class-deals</alias><summary>Capital city Cairo is full of magnificent sights and stellar Egyptian entertainment. Perched along the Nile River, this city teems with 10 million residents and countless businesses and cultural havens. The city’s rich history isn’t lost among these more modern features, though, making Cairo a delightful destination.

    If you’re a history buff, Cairo offers endless appeal. It is home to some of the oldest settled districts in all of Africa, including Coptic Cairo. It’s also the perfect jumping-off point for a day trip to see Egypt’s incredible pyramids. The Great Pyramids of Giza are just a 30-minute drive from the city. If you choose a window seat when booking your business class deals to Cairo, you’ll be able to see the pyramids upon landing. The pyramids and tombs of Saqqara are also just an hour away.</summary><browserTitle>A Luxurious Approach to Cairo Includes Business Class Deals | IFlyFirstClass Travel Tips</browserTitle><created_date>1/7/2017 1:00:04 AM</created_date><seo><description>Ancient artifacts, lively entertainment and gorgeous mosques enrich your visit to Cairo. Book business class deals to the city for a memorable trip.</description><keywords>Cairo Business Class Deals</keywords></seo><images><image><alias>bee3c110644a444da0dc8a8aa94e609a.jpg</alias><content_id>75</content_id><title>Revel in all of Cairo’s many treasures.</title><queue>0</queue></image></images></item><item><travel_tips_id>76</travel_tips_id><title>5 Business Class Lounges You Could Almost Live In</title><alias>top-five-business-class-lounges</alias><summary>The Cathay Pacific’s newly designed The Pier lounge in Hong Kong International Airport makes the list for its diversity. “Cathay Pacific’s Hong Kong lounge reappears on our list because it caters well to two types of travelers: those who want to relish the travel experience of the country and those who are rushing off to their next flight,” said Richie. The Pier lounge, fast-lane travelers can grab a quick bite or drink from self-service food kiosks, a coffee cart and a noodle bar. Those in the “slow lane” can relax in a peaceful teahouse, lounge area and customized Solo lounge chairs. Shower suites are comfortably accessorized, and a relaxation room provides additional rejuvenation.
    Turkish Airlines recently rebooted its Istanbul lounge, earning rave reviews, and not jus for its complimentary shoulder and neck massages. The newly redesigned lounge is spacious, covering two floors of the airport. The amenities include a reading room, computer stations, a billiards area, a movie room and ample dining and refreshment areas.
    For the passengers who tend to get home sick, Singapore Airlines’ Silver Kris lounge at Singapore’s Changi Airport offers a “home away from home” atmosphere. Passengers can relax in the living room area, fuel up in the dining room area and grab a snack in the kitchen area. The lounge also offers “productivity pods” for working.
    And finally a lounge that is right here in the US: United Airlines’ new Polaris Lounge in Chicago’s O’Hare Airport. Part of United’s new Polaris business class concept, the lounge is the first of many to be opened throughout 2017 and 2018. Travelers can enjoy premium wines, spirits and meals. The lounge also offers sleeping rooms and laundry service, showers and concierge services.
    More info: iflyfirstclass.com</summary><browserTitle>5 Business Class Lounges | IFlyFirstClass Travel Tips</browserTitle><created_date>1/28/2017 12:13:33 PM</created_date><seo><description>Dmitry Richie, the founder of the luxury travel agency IFlyFirstClass based in Chicago, shares his top 5 picks for the business class lounges for the travelers </description><keywords>Business Class Lounges</keywords></seo><images><image><alias>dddab66b58c24ad09f17353b672c44af.jpg</alias><content_id>76</content_id><title>5 Business Class Lounges </title><queue>0</queue></image></images></item></items>